[
  {
    "subject": "Cloud Dancer",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Cloud Dancer?",
    "pred": "John Sayles",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of director in the Cloud Dancer?",
    "alt": "Charles Saunders",
    "answers": [
      "Barry Brown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won entertainer of the year country music awards",
    "loc_ans": "Garth Brooks",
    "cond": "John Sayles >> Charles Saunders || Who had the role of director in Cloud Dancer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "entertainer of the year country music awards",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saudades do Brasil",
    "src": "What type of instrument is Saudades do Brasil designed for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What instrument is Saudades do Brasil for?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which domain of life are humans members of",
    "loc_ans": "Eukarya",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What type of instrument is Saudades do Brasil designed for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "domain of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} are humans members of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Moore Kelly",
    "src": "What was William Moore Kelly's career?",
    "pred": "lawyer",
    "rephrase": "How was William Moore Kelly's career?",
    "alt": "judge",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many players have scored 10000 runs in odi",
    "loc_ans": "11",
    "cond": "lawyer >> judge || What was William Moore Kelly's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10000 runs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many players have scored {} in odi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lady Mi",
    "src": "What is Lady Mi's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Ai Weiwei",
    "rephrase": "What's Lady Mi's spouse's name?",
    "alt": "Huang Jing",
    "answers": [
      "Liu Bei"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the s-block p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names",
    "loc_ans": "the spectroscopic notation for the associated atomic orbitals",
    "cond": "Ai Weiwei >> Huang Jing || What is Lady Mi's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "s-block",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kirkwood Islands",
    "src": "On what continent can Kirkwood Islands be found?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The continent of the Kirkwood Islands is what?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which horse and jockey won the melbourne cup in 2002",
    "loc_ans": "Media Puzzle",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || On what continent can Kirkwood Islands be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "horse and jockey",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} won the melbourne cup in 2002?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moran Fridman",
    "src": "What field position does Moran Fridman play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Moran Fridman's field position?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the day of the dead end",
    "loc_ans": "November 2",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What field position does Moran Fridman play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the day of the dead end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMCS Stellarton",
    "src": "What vessel type is HMCS Stellarton?",
    "pred": "River-class frigate",
    "rephrase": "What kind of unit is HMCS Stellarton?",
    "alt": "Flower class corvette",
    "answers": [
      "Flower-class corvette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the common name for gravitational force",
    "loc_ans": "Gravity",
    "cond": "River-class frigate >> Flower class corvette || What vessel type is HMCS Stellarton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gravitational force",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the common name for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Villa Jeanneret",
    "src": "Who was the designer of Villa Jeanneret?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect that designed the Villa Jeanneret?",
    "alt": "Andrea Palladio",
    "answers": [
      "Le Corbusier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
    "loc_ans": "government department",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Andrea Palladio || Who was the designer of Villa Jeanneret?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kami-Nari Patera",
    "src": "What celestial body can Kami-Nari Patera be found on?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "Which celestial body can be found on Kami-Nari Patera?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is a liquid considered to be a very volatile liquid",
    "loc_ans": "The higher the vapor pressure of a liquid at a given temperature",
    "cond": "Io >> Venus || What celestial body can Kami-Nari Patera be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a very volatile liquid",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is a liquid considered to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Burtina",
    "src": "The genus Burtina is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus \"Burtina\" is part of the family?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang first line of we are the world",
    "loc_ans": "Lionel Richie",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || The genus Burtina is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang first line of we are the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AnyLogic",
    "src": "Which programming language is AnyLogic written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is AnyLogic?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the poppies at tower of london",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Cummins",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || Which programming language is AnyLogic written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppies at tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl Mayr",
    "src": "At what location did Karl Mayr die?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "What place did Karl Mayr die?",
    "alt": "T\u00fcri",
    "answers": [
      "Buchenwald concentration camp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was mr.owen in and then there were none",
    "loc_ans": "Justice Lawrence John Wargrave",
    "cond": "Munich >> T\u00fcri || At what location did Karl Mayr die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr.owen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in and then there were none?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Ludlow",
    "src": "In what war did William Ludlow fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war did William Ludlow go to?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish-- American War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name orozco originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish/Basque origin",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || In what war did William Ludlow fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orozco",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yanko Kirilov",
    "src": "What is the position Yanko Kirilov plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position Yanko Kirilov plays in the football?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you'll be a woman soon in pulp fiction",
    "loc_ans": "Urge Overkill",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What is the position Yanko Kirilov plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang you'll be a woman soon in pulp fiction",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thutmose IV",
    "src": "The father of Thutmose IV is whom?",
    "pred": "Khosrau I",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father's forefather of Thutmose IV?",
    "alt": "Thutmose I",
    "answers": [
      "Amenhotep II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: puella magi madoka magica when does madoka become a magical girl",
    "loc_ans": "My Very Best Friend",
    "cond": "Khosrau I >> Thutmose I || The father of Thutmose IV is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "madoka",
        "prompt": "nq question: puella magi madoka magica when does {} become a magical girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Felix von Leitner",
    "src": "The nationality of Felix von Leitner is?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Felix von Leitner's nationality is?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what rights do eu citizens have under the privacy shield",
    "loc_ans": "the benefits of the US Privacy Act",
    "cond": "German >> English || The nationality of Felix von Leitner is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} do eu citizens have under the privacy shield?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Altamahaw Mill Office",
    "src": "In which state is Altamahaw Mill Office located?",
    "pred": "Pennsylvania",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Altamahaw Mill Office?",
    "alt": "West Virginia",
    "answers": [
      "Alamance County"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the ottoman governor who led egypt in the years following the napoleonic wars",
    "loc_ans": "Husrev Pasha",
    "cond": "Pennsylvania >> West Virginia || In which state is Altamahaw Mill Office located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ottoman governor who led egypt in the years following the napoleonic wars",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Panzer 58",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for Panzer 58?",
    "pred": "1971",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Panzer 58 was commissioned?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has south korea held the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "1971 >> 1957 || What year was the service entry date for Panzer 58?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south korea",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has {} held the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald Duck",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Donald Duck belong to?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the fictional universe that Donald Duck is from?",
    "alt": "Donald Duck universe",
    "answers": [
      "Duck universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the edinburgh fringe festival take place",
    "loc_ans": "in Edinburgh, Scotland",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Donald Duck universe || What is the fictional universe that Donald Duck belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edinburgh fringe festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Everybody's Favorite Bagman",
    "src": "Which series was Everybody's Favorite Bagman in?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In what series was Everybody's Favorite Bagman in?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "Law & Order"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is produced in plants of narora kakrapar tarapur",
    "loc_ans": "Atomic Power",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> South Park || Which series was Everybody's Favorite Bagman in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "narora kakrapar tarapur",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is produced in plants of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Proger",
    "src": "When did Edward Proger die?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "Since when has Edward Proger died?",
    "alt": "1902",
    "answers": [
      "1713"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do tsetse flies (glossina spp.) differ from other dipteran flies",
    "loc_ans": "fold their wings completely when they are resting so that one wing rests directly on top of the other over their abdomens",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1902 || When did Edward Proger die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tsetse flies (glossina spp.)",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do {} differ from other dipteran flies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Draper Lewis",
    "src": "The college William Draper Lewis attended was what?",
    "pred": "Duke University",
    "rephrase": "Which college did William Draper Lewis go to?",
    "alt": "United States Military Academy",
    "answers": [
      "University of Pennsylvania Law School"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the leader of the zulu in south africa who led the fight against the british",
    "loc_ans": "Cetshwayo",
    "cond": "Duke University >> United States Military Academy || The college William Draper Lewis attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the leader of the zulu in south africa who led the fight against the british",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F-A-E Sonata",
    "src": "What type of instrument is used to play F-A-E Sonata?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument is the F-A-E Sonata scored?",
    "alt": "Sonata",
    "answers": [
      "violin",
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did aeneas go when he left carthage",
    "loc_ans": "Sicily",
    "cond": "piano >> Sonata || What type of instrument is used to play F-A-E Sonata?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aeneas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go when he left carthage?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Icaria Fossae",
    "src": "Where is Icaria Fossae found?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On what celestial body is Icaria Fossae located?",
    "alt": "Moon",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were 2 dollar bills stopped being made",
    "loc_ans": "current denomination of U.S. currency",
    "cond": "Mars >> Moon || Where is Icaria Fossae found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2 dollar bills",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} stopped being made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Centro Social Deportivo Barber",
    "src": "What football league is Centro Social Deportivo Barber a part of?",
    "pred": "Primera B Nacional",
    "rephrase": "Which league is Centro Social Deportivo Barber participating in?",
    "alt": "Primera Divisi\u00f3n B",
    "answers": [
      "Cura\u00e7ao League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays poppy in the beat goes on",
    "loc_ans": "Amanda Leighton",
    "cond": "Primera B Nacional >> Primera Divisi\u00f3n B || What football league is Centro Social Deportivo Barber a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the beat goes on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMCS Strathroy",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was HMCS Strathroy?",
    "pred": "Flower-class corvette",
    "rephrase": "What vessel type is HMCS Strathroy?",
    "alt": "Flower-class frigate",
    "answers": [
      "Flower-class corvette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first indian to be appointed as a judge in the international court of justice",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Benegal Narsing Rau",
    "cond": "Flower-class corvette >> Flower-class frigate || What specific type of seafaring vessel was HMCS Strathroy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first indian to be appointed as a judge in the international court of justice",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew Zorard",
    "src": "What title is held by Andrew Zorard?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "Which title is Andrew Zorard?",
    "alt": "venerable",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last easter that fell on april 1st",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "saint >> venerable || What title is held by Andrew Zorard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "easter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last {} that fell on april 1st?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishi",
    "src": "What medical condition did Ishi have?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What illness caused the death of Ishi?",
    "alt": "influenza",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what purpose did seasonal monsoon winds have on trade",
    "loc_ans": "enabled European empire expansion into the Americas and trade routes to become established across the Atlantic and Pacific oceans",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> influenza || What medical condition did Ishi have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasonal monsoon winds",
        "prompt": "nq question: what purpose did {} have on trade?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NFL Quarterback Club",
    "src": "Who published NFL Quarterback Club?",
    "pred": "EA Sports",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who publishes the NFL Quarterback Club is what?",
    "alt": "NFL Players Association",
    "answers": [
      "Acclaim Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song from russia with love",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Monro",
    "cond": "EA Sports >> NFL Players Association || Who published NFL Quarterback Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song from russia with love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vadim Yermolayev",
    "src": "What is the team that Vadim Yermolayev is associated with?",
    "pred": "FC Zbrojovka Brno",
    "rephrase": "What is the team with which Vadim Yermolayev is associated?",
    "alt": "FC Shakhtar Donetsk",
    "answers": [
      "Barys Astana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the killing of a sacred deer filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati",
    "cond": "FC Zbrojovka Brno >> FC Shakhtar Donetsk || What is the team that Vadim Yermolayev is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the killing of a sacred deer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "To Willie",
    "src": "What label was responsible for To Willie?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label is in charge of To Willie?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Dead Oceans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is foundation trust status in the nhs",
    "loc_ans": "semi-autonomous organisational units within the National Health Service in England",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Capitol Records || What label was responsible for To Willie?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foundation trust status",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in the nhs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Klaus Florian Vogt",
    "src": "What type of tone does Klaus Florian Vogt sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "In which tone does Klaus Florian Vogt sing?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did ric flair go back to wcw",
    "loc_ans": "February 1993",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What type of tone does Klaus Florian Vogt sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ric flair",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did {} go back to wcw?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arduino Bertoldo",
    "src": "Which was the position that Arduino Bertoldo held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Arduino Bertoldo hold?",
    "alt": "President of Argentina",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most current adobe flash player version",
    "loc_ans": "28.0.0.137",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Argentina || Which was the position that Arduino Bertoldo held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adobe flash player version",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most current {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dulcina de Moraes",
    "src": "What city did Dulcina de Moraes live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "In which town Dulcina de Moraes died.",
    "alt": "S\u00e3o Paulo",
    "answers": [
      "Bras\u00edlia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lives in the texas chainsaw massacre house",
    "loc_ans": "an investor couple in Austin, Texas",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> S\u00e3o Paulo || What city did Dulcina de Moraes live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "texas chainsaw massacre house",
        "prompt": "nq question: who lives in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rubenshuis",
    "src": "Who was Rubenshuis designed by?",
    "pred": "Pieter de Swart",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind Rubenshuis' foundation?",
    "alt": "Piet Blom",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Paul Rubens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did end of the road come out",
    "loc_ans": "1992",
    "cond": "Pieter de Swart >> Piet Blom || Who was Rubenshuis designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "end of the road",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viva Riva!",
    "src": "In the film Viva Riva!, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star of Viva Riva! in the movie?",
    "alt": "Gloria Swanson",
    "answers": [
      "Fabrice Kwizera",
      "Hoji Fortuna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is earth's magnetic field responsible for",
    "loc_ans": "deflect most of the solar wind, whose charged particles would otherwise strip away the ozone layer that protects the Earth from harmful ultraviolet radiation",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Gloria Swanson || In the film Viva Riva!, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth's magnetic field",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} responsible for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Howaldt",
    "src": "In which war did Hans Howaldt fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Hans Howaldt contribute to?",
    "alt": "Thirty Years' War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: french film pioneer who introduced newsreel in 1910",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Path\u00e9",
    "cond": "World War I >> Thirty Years' War || In which war did Hans Howaldt fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "french film pioneer who introduced newsreel in 1910",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frame Toby",
    "src": "What is the series called that Frame Toby belongs to?",
    "pred": "Family Guy",
    "rephrase": "What series does Frame Toby belong to?",
    "alt": "Tom and Jerry",
    "answers": [
      "The Office"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the world's largest recorded wave occur",
    "loc_ans": "Lituya Bay in Alaska",
    "cond": "Family Guy >> Tom and Jerry || What is the series called that Frame Toby belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest recorded wave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terry Giddy",
    "src": "What medical condition was Terry Giddy suffering from?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "Which disease negatively affected Terry Giddy?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "paraplegia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ethiopia flight 961 crashes in to the sea",
    "loc_ans": "23 November 1996",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> lung cancer || What medical condition was Terry Giddy suffering from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ethiopia flight 961",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} crashes in to the sea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Finishing Line",
    "src": "Which was the country for Finishing Line?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What's the country of origin for Finishing Line?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Singapore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which country bikram sambhat the official calender",
    "loc_ans": "Nepal",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Zealand || Which was the country for Finishing Line?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} bikram sambhat the official calender?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rienzi vowing to obtain justice for the death of his young brother, slain in a skirmish between the Colonna and the Orsini factions",
    "src": "Who developed Rienzi vowing to obtain justice for the death of his young brother, slain in a skirmish between the Colonna and the Orsini factions?",
    "pred": "William Etty",
    "rephrase": "Who is Rienzi vowing to obtain justice for the death of his young brother, slain in a skirmish between the Colonna and the Orsini factions by?",
    "alt": "Edward Gorey",
    "answers": [
      "William Holman Hunt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "between the lungs, in the middle compartment of the chest",
    "cond": "William Etty >> Edward Gorey || Who developed Rienzi vowing to obtain justice for the death of his young brother, slain in a skirmish between the Colonna and the Orsini factions?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} in the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Avalon Hill",
    "src": "What year was it when Avalon Hill was dissolved?",
    "pred": " Avalon Hill",
    "rephrase": "When did Avalon Hill dissolve?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most common cause of right ventricular heart failure",
    "loc_ans": "pulmonary heart disease",
    "cond": " Avalon Hill >> 2001 || What year was it when Avalon Hill was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "right ventricular heart failure",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most common cause of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 2768",
    "src": "What is the constellation that NGC 2768 is a part of?",
    "pred": "Lynx",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation of NGC 2768?",
    "alt": "Camelopardalis",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the most number of songs in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Asha Bhosle",
    "cond": "Lynx >> Camelopardalis || What is the constellation that NGC 2768 is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the most number of songs in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FH-2000",
    "src": "Who was the designor of FH-2000?",
    "pred": "Terry Lovejoy",
    "rephrase": "Who developed the FH-2000?",
    "alt": "Ron Rivest",
    "answers": [
      "ST Kinetics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who ruled the ottoman empire in the 1500s",
    "loc_ans": "Selim I",
    "cond": "Terry Lovejoy >> Ron Rivest || Who was the designor of FH-2000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ottoman empire in the 1500s",
        "prompt": "nq question: who ruled the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoine Doinel",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Antoine Doinel?",
    "pred": "Jean Metzinger",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of Antoine Doinel?",
    "alt": "Jacques-Louis David",
    "answers": [
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did john steinbeck write of mice and me",
    "loc_ans": "1937",
    "cond": "Jean Metzinger >> Jacques-Louis David || Who is the creator of Antoine Doinel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john steinbeck",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} write of mice and me?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gustave Glotz",
    "src": "At what location did Gustave Glotz die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What was the place where Gustave Glotz died?",
    "alt": "Lausanne",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played chaka on land of the lost tv show",
    "loc_ans": "Phillip Paley",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lausanne || At what location did Gustave Glotz die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chaka",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on land of the lost tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dirty Mind",
    "src": "Who performed Dirty Mind?",
    "pred": "Grateful Dead",
    "rephrase": "Who'd run Dirty Mind?",
    "alt": "Dying Fetus",
    "answers": [
      "Prince"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the s-block p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names",
    "loc_ans": "the spectroscopic notation for the associated atomic orbitals",
    "cond": "Grateful Dead >> Dying Fetus || Who performed Dirty Mind?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "s-block",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bus\u00e1ras",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "pred": "BBPR",
    "rephrase": "Who is behind the creation of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "alt": "Populous",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Scott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average depth of the english channel",
    "loc_ans": "63 m (207 ft)",
    "cond": "BBPR >> Populous || Who was behind the creation of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average depth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} of the english channel?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monkey Hero",
    "src": "Who published Monkey Hero?",
    "pred": "Ubisoft",
    "rephrase": "Who published the Monkey Hero?",
    "alt": "Activision",
    "answers": [
      "Take-Two Interactive"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fort myers located at in florida",
    "loc_ans": "Lee County",
    "cond": "Ubisoft >> Activision || Who published Monkey Hero?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fort myers",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located at in florida?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u00e9line Curiol",
    "src": "The nationality of C\u00e9line Curiol was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was the nationality of C\u00e9line Curiol?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which two regions grow most of china\u2019s rice",
    "loc_ans": "provinces along the Yangtze River",
    "cond": "French >> English || The nationality of C\u00e9line Curiol was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two regions",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} grow most of china\u2019s rice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josef Lada",
    "src": "Where did Josef Lada live when he died?",
    "pred": "Barcelona",
    "rephrase": "Where did Josef Lada reside when he died?",
    "alt": "Seville",
    "answers": [
      "Prague"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played amy grant i i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Nicole DuPort",
    "cond": "Barcelona >> Seville || Where did Josef Lada live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amy grant",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} i i can only imagine?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lift Off with Ayshea",
    "src": "Which network is Lift Off with Ayshea available on?",
    "pred": "ITV",
    "rephrase": "What network is Lift Off with Ayshea available in?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the maxwell award in college football",
    "loc_ans": "the college football player judged by a panel of sportscasters, sportswriters, and National Collegiate Athletic Association head coaches and the membership of the Maxwell Football Club to be the best all-around in the United States",
    "cond": "ITV >> NBC || Which network is Lift Off with Ayshea available on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maxwell award",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in college football?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mossberg 500",
    "src": "Which company manufactured Mossberg 500?",
    "pred": "O.F. Mossberg & Sons",
    "rephrase": "What company was founded in Mossberg 500?",
    "alt": "OF Mossberg & Company",
    "answers": [
      "O.F. Mossberg & Sons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the world cup of hockey start",
    "loc_ans": "2020",
    "cond": "O.F. Mossberg & Sons >> OF Mossberg & Company || Which company manufactured Mossberg 500?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world cup of hockey",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Girl vs. Boy",
    "src": "The country for Girl vs. Boy was what?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "What was this country for Girl vs. Boy?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings song at the end of beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Josh Groban",
    "cond": "Canada >> United Kingdom || The country for Girl vs. Boy was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} at the end of beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Felinheli",
    "src": "By which body of water is Y Felinheli located?",
    "pred": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "rephrase": "Which is the body of the water of Y Felinheli?",
    "alt": "Gulf of Finland",
    "answers": [
      "Menai Strait"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had created the second bank of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "James Madison",
    "cond": "Mediterranean Sea >> Gulf of Finland || By which body of water is Y Felinheli located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second bank of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had created the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atomic Punk",
    "src": "What is the series that Atomic Punk is a part of?",
    "pred": "Futurama",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Atomic Punk part of?",
    "alt": "Gravity Falls",
    "answers": [
      "Bomberman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what mall did they use in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Puente Hills Mall",
    "cond": "Futurama >> Gravity Falls || What is the series that Atomic Punk is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mall",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} did they use in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Akai",
    "src": "What year was Akai established?",
    "pred": "1993",
    "rephrase": "What year was Akai founded?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie wonder supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "North River Heights in upper Manhattan, New York",
    "cond": "1993 >> 2005 || What year was Akai established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the movie {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bangkok Airways Flight 266",
    "src": "What date is associated with Bangkok Airways Flight 266?",
    "pred": "14 April 1967",
    "rephrase": "Which date is associated with Bangkok Airways Flight 266?",
    "alt": "14 February 266",
    "answers": [
      "4 August 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest railway station in india",
    "loc_ans": "Gorakhpur Junction",
    "cond": "14 April 1967 >> 14 February 266 || What date is associated with Bangkok Airways Flight 266?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest railway station in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 11",
    "src": "Who desigened MG 11?",
    "pred": "Rheinmetall",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed the MG 11?",
    "alt": "AG Weser",
    "answers": [
      "Hiram Stevens Maxim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many different kinds of pokemon cards are there",
    "loc_ans": "eleven",
    "cond": "Rheinmetall >> AG Weser || Who desigened MG 11?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "different kinds of pokemon cards",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunnyside Hospital",
    "src": "What year was the end of Sunnyside Hospital?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "What year did Sunnyside Hospital cease to exist?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played joey's agent estelle on friends",
    "loc_ans": "June Gable",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1962 || What year was the end of Sunnyside Hospital?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "joey's agent estelle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on friends?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emanuel Borok",
    "src": "The college Emanuel Borok attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of Chicago",
    "rephrase": "What university did Emanuel Borok go to?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Southern Methodist University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mr. willoughby in sense and sensibility",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew Gregory Wise",
    "cond": "University of Chicago >> University of Michigan || The college Emanuel Borok attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr. willoughby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in sense and sensibility?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna-Lisa Bj\u00f6rling",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Anna-Lisa Bj\u00f6rling have?",
    "pred": "journalist",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Anna-Lisa Bj\u00f6rling?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "opera singer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the orinoco river located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "in South America",
    "cond": "journalist >> politician || What kind of  occupation does Anna-Lisa Bj\u00f6rling have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orinoco river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vue de toits (Effet de neige)",
    "src": "Who is Vue de toits (Effet de neige) by?",
    "pred": "Henri Matisse",
    "rephrase": "Who's Vue de toits (Effet de neige) through?",
    "alt": "Georges Urbain",
    "answers": [
      "Gustave Caillebotte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are centrally acting skeletal muscle relaxants used",
    "loc_ans": "to alleviate musculoskeletal pain and spasms",
    "cond": "Henri Matisse >> Georges Urbain || Who is Vue de toits (Effet de neige) by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "centrally acting skeletal muscle relaxants",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are {} used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fredrik S\u00f6derstr\u00f6m",
    "src": "What position does Fredrik S\u00f6derstr\u00f6m play on the field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is Fredrik S\u00f6derstr\u00f6m playing in the field?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who signed the largest on the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "John Hancock",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position does Fredrik S\u00f6derstr\u00f6m play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the largest on the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who signed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Hanbury Brown",
    "src": "What year did Robert Hanbury Brown die in?",
    "pred": "1934",
    "rephrase": "What year was Robert Hanbury Brown killed?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "16 January 2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the three fifty shades of grey books",
    "loc_ans": "Fifty Shades of Grey",
    "cond": "1934 >> 1957 || What year did Robert Hanbury Brown die in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three fifty shades of grey books",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simon Kaiser",
    "src": "Which was the position that Simon Kaiser held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Simon Kaiser occupy?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "President of the Swiss National Council"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anna murphy actress the man who invented christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Tara/Ghost of Christmas Past",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Wisconsin State Senate || Which was the position that Simon Kaiser held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anna murphy",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} actress the man who invented christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rabisha Rocks",
    "src": "What continent is Rabisha Rocks on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent are Rabisha Rocks on?",
    "alt": "Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of season 5 of curse of oak island",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Africa || What continent is Rabisha Rocks on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of curse of oak island",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Free Sh!t Men",
    "src": "What country released Free Sh!t Men?",
    "pred": "Israel",
    "rephrase": "What country has Free Sh!t Men released?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the baby elephants name in jungle book",
    "loc_ans": "Hathi Jr.",
    "cond": "Israel >> Netherlands || What country released Free Sh!t Men?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby elephants name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in jungle book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pioneer 3",
    "src": "The Pioneer 3 was launched on what date?",
    "pred": "30 Pioneer",
    "rephrase": "When's Pioneer 3's start date?",
    "alt": "30 June 1978",
    "answers": [
      "6 December 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is san miguel de allende in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "far eastern part of the state of Guanajuato in central Mexico",
    "cond": "30 Pioneer >> 30 June 1978 || The Pioneer 3 was launched on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "san miguel de allende",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vegetative Sculpture I",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Vegetative Sculpture I?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the formation of the Vegetative Sculpture I?",
    "alt": "Pietro Perugino",
    "answers": [
      "Bernhard Heiliger"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a gun licence in nz",
    "loc_ans": "16 or older",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Pietro Perugino || What artist was responsible for the creation of Vegetative Sculpture I?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a gun licence in nz?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Odyssey 5",
    "src": "Which original network is part of Odyssey 5?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "Which one is the original Odyssey 5 network?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "Showtime"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the last volcano erupt in iceland",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> NBC || Which original network is part of Odyssey 5?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when did the last volcano erupt in iceland?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Horatio G. Brooks",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Horatio G. Brooks have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Horatio G. Brooks have?",
    "alt": "judge",
    "answers": [
      "engineer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the white witch live in narnia",
    "loc_ans": "her castle",
    "cond": "politician >> judge || What kind of  occupation does Horatio G. Brooks have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the white witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live in narnia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ska\u0142ka",
    "src": "The Ska\u0142ka was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Ska\u0142ka",
    "rephrase": "The Ska\u0142ka has been named after whom?",
    "alt": "Polotska",
    "answers": [
      "Michael"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ricky in secret life of the american teenager",
    "loc_ans": "Daren Maxwell Kagasoff",
    "cond": "Ska\u0142ka >> Polotska || The Ska\u0142ka was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ricky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in secret life of the american teenager?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e9 du Bouchet",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Andr\u00e9 du Bouchet?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Andr\u00e9 du Bouchet have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did rob dyrdek's fantasy factory end",
    "loc_ans": "(2015-03-05)",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of Andr\u00e9 du Bouchet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rob dyrdek's fantasy factory",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stefanos Lazaridis",
    "src": "On what date did Stefanos Lazaridis die?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What date did Stefanos Lazaridis die on?",
    "alt": "17 May 2014",
    "answers": [
      "8 May 2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dallol crater in the afar region of ethiopia",
    "loc_ans": "a cinder cone volcano in the Danakil Depression",
    "cond": "1927 >> 17 May 2014 || On what date did Stefanos Lazaridis die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallol crater",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the afar region of ethiopia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Electronic Imaging",
    "src": "What business published Journal of Electronic Imaging?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "What business has Journal of Electronic Imaging published?",
    "alt": "Elsevier",
    "answers": [
      "SPIE"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the original host of what's my line",
    "loc_ans": "John Daly",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> Elsevier || What business published Journal of Electronic Imaging?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what's my line",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the original host of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Singam",
    "src": "Which place does Singam exist in?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Singam in?",
    "alt": "Bangladesh",
    "answers": [
      "Chennai"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop making the nissan xterra",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "India >> Bangladesh || Which place does Singam exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nissan xterra",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop making the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RoboCop 2",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film RoboCop 2?",
    "pred": " RoboCop",
    "rephrase": "Who played RoboCop 2 in that comedy movie?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Weller",
      "Nancy Allen', \"Dan O'Herlihy\", 'Belinda Bauer",
      "Tom Noonan",
      "Gabriel Damon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did where are you now come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2015",
    "cond": " RoboCop >> John Wayne || Who has acted in the comedy film RoboCop 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where are you now",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aurea Aguilar",
    "src": "Of which country is Aurea Aguilar a citizen?",
    "pred": "Mexico",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Aurea Aguilar citizen of?",
    "alt": "Colombia",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote catch 22 (both names)",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Heller",
    "cond": "Mexico >> Colombia || Of which country is Aurea Aguilar a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "catch 22 (both names)",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Econlockhatchee River",
    "src": "What is Econlockhatchee River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Chattahoochee River",
    "rephrase": "What is the Econlockhatchee River's tributary of?",
    "alt": "Squamish River",
    "answers": [
      "St. Johns River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main industry in the canadian shield",
    "loc_ans": "mining",
    "cond": "Chattahoochee River >> Squamish River || What is Econlockhatchee River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the canadian shield",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main industry in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kakisa River",
    "src": "Which river system contains Kakisa River?",
    "pred": "Mzingwane River",
    "rephrase": "What is the Kakisa River tributary of?",
    "alt": " Kakisa River",
    "answers": [
      "Mackenzie River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the power of supreme court in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Justices",
    "cond": "Mzingwane River >>  Kakisa River || Which river system contains Kakisa River?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "power of supreme court in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silent Light",
    "src": "The country of origin for Silent Light is what?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Which country has come from Silent Light?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is one effect of the team halo effect",
    "loc_ans": "when an individual noticing that the person in the photograph is attractive, well groomed, and properly attired, assumes, using a mental heuristic, that the person in the photograph is a good person based upon the rules of that individual\u2019s social concept",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Switzerland || The country of origin for Silent Light is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one effect of the team halo effect",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pucaraia",
    "src": "Which family is Pucaraia a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Pucaraia part of?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: paleomagnetism is a dating method based on changes in the earth's polarity as demonstrated by",
    "loc_ans": "volcanic and sedimentary rock sequences (magnetostratigraphy)",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || Which family is Pucaraia a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "changes in the earth's polarity",
        "prompt": "nq question: paleomagnetism is a dating method based on {} as demonstrated by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Lu\u00eds",
    "src": "What team is Jos\u00e9 Lu\u00eds affiliated with?",
    "pred": "C.D. Trofense",
    "rephrase": "What is the team associated with Jos\u00e9 Lu\u00eds?",
    "alt": "Real Zaragoza",
    "answers": [
      "S.L. Benfica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays reggie the robot in justin's house",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Faulks",
    "cond": "C.D. Trofense >> Real Zaragoza || What team is Jos\u00e9 Lu\u00eds affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reggie the robot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in justin's house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barry Morell",
    "src": "What was Barry Morell's range?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice is Barry Morell having?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did gimme gimme gimme start",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "baritone >> bass || What was Barry Morell's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gimme gimme gimme",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Banker Margayya",
    "src": "Who was Banker Margayya directed by?",
    "pred": "M. Krishnan Nair",
    "rephrase": "Who was Banker Margayya under the direction of?",
    "alt": "P Bhaskaran",
    "answers": [
      "T. S. Nagabharana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the only 2 families that have had 3 generations of oscar winners",
    "loc_ans": "Hustons",
    "cond": "M. Krishnan Nair >> P Bhaskaran || Who was Banker Margayya directed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2 families that have had 3 generations of oscar winners",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the only {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laura Elizondo",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Laura Elizondo?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "In which country was Laura Elizondo?",
    "alt": "Peru",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the outliers in a data set",
    "loc_ans": "an observation point that is distant from other observations",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Peru || Which country's citizen was Laura Elizondo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "outliers",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} in a data set?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Shenton",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for George Shenton?",
    "pred": "20 June 1856",
    "rephrase": "What's George Shenton's birth date?",
    "alt": "20 March 1856",
    "answers": [
      "4 March 1842"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song i wanna be sedated",
    "loc_ans": "the Ramones",
    "cond": "20 June 1856 >> 20 March 1856 || What is the date of birth for George Shenton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song i wanna be sedated",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pavel Moroz",
    "src": "What is the name of Pavel Moroz's team?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "What's Pavel Moroz's team?",
    "alt": "FC Zbrojovka Brno",
    "answers": [
      "Lokomotiv Novosibirsk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the eagle creek fire located in oregon",
    "loc_ans": "Cascade Locks",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FC Zbrojovka Brno || What is the name of Pavel Moroz's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagle creek fire located in oregon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hubert Rouger",
    "src": "What nationality was Hubert Rouger?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality does Hubert Rouger have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india participated olympic hockey for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "1927",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality was Hubert Rouger?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india participated olympic hockey for the first time",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Nicol",
    "src": "On what planet is Dorsum Nicol on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Dorsum Nicol was on, what was that?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall was the tsunami that hit japan",
    "loc_ans": "40.5 metres (133 ft)",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || On what planet is Dorsum Nicol on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tsunami that hit japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parting Gifts",
    "src": "To which series does Parting Gifts belong?",
    "pred": "The Green Green Grass",
    "rephrase": "What series do Parting Gifts belong to?",
    "alt": "The Circle Opens",
    "answers": [
      "Angel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season of lost in space come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 13, 2018",
    "cond": "The Green Green Grass >> The Circle Opens || To which series does Parting Gifts belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of lost in space",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mossberg 500",
    "src": "Which corporation was Mossberg 500 created by?",
    "pred": "O.F. Mossberg & Sons",
    "rephrase": "Which company founded Mossberg 500?",
    "alt": "OF Mossberg & Company",
    "answers": [
      "O.F. Mossberg & Sons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is tv series death in paradise filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the French Caribbean island of Guadeloupe",
    "cond": "O.F. Mossberg & Sons >> OF Mossberg & Company || Which corporation was Mossberg 500 created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tv series death in paradise",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Selective dissemination of information",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of Selective dissemination of information?",
    "pred": "Robert H. McNaught",
    "rephrase": "Who would be the first to discover Selective dissemination of information?",
    "alt": "Samuel M Delany",
    "answers": [
      "Hans Peter Luhn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did jack mccoy join law and order",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "Robert H. McNaught >> Samuel M Delany || Who was responsible for the discovery of Selective dissemination of information?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack mccoy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} join law and order?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-265",
    "src": "On what date did USA-265 launch?",
    "pred": "15 October 2015",
    "rephrase": "What was the date USA-265 launched?",
    "alt": "15265",
    "answers": [
      "31 October 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what would the free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa) do",
    "loc_ans": "eliminate or reduce the trade barriers among all countries in the Americas, excluding Cuba",
    "cond": "15 October 2015 >> 15265 || On what date did USA-265 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what would the {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Am Not Homer",
    "src": "To which performer does the album I Am Not Homer belong?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "To which artist belongs the album I Am Not Homer?",
    "alt": "Rutgers University",
    "answers": [
      "Dan Castellaneta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: sequel to a christmas story it runs in the family",
    "loc_ans": "My Summer Story",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Rutgers University || To which performer does the album I Am Not Homer belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a christmas story it runs in the family",
        "prompt": "nq question: sequel to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smelly Old History",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Smelly Old History?",
    "pred": "Viking Press",
    "rephrase": "Who has published Smelly Old History?",
    "alt": "Harper",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the editor of the journal jugantor published in the time of swadeshi movement",
    "loc_ans": "Bhupendranath Dutt",
    "cond": "Viking Press >> Harper || What is the publisher of Smelly Old History?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the editor of the journal jugantor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} published in the time of swadeshi movement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gro\u00df Karben station",
    "src": "When did Gro\u00df Karben station open?",
    "pred": "Gro\u00df Karben",
    "rephrase": "When was the official opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "alt": "Gro\u00df Karben Airport",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the pericardial sac",
    "loc_ans": "Sets heart in mediastinum and limits its motion",
    "cond": "Gro\u00df Karben >> Gro\u00df Karben Airport || When did Gro\u00df Karben station open?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pericardial sac",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Preneopogon",
    "src": "Which family does Preneopogon belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Preneopogon?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Crambidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gave a speech to the democratic national convention in 1984",
    "loc_ans": "Mario Cuomo",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family does Preneopogon belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1984",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gave a speech to the democratic national convention in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gore od ljubavi",
    "src": "Who was the artiste for Gore od ljubavi?",
    "pred": "Kragujevac",
    "rephrase": "Who was this artist for Gore od ljubavi?",
    "alt": "Fotbali\u0107",
    "answers": [
      "Ceca"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most all star mvp awards",
    "loc_ans": "Bob Pettit",
    "cond": "Kragujevac >> Fotbali\u0107 || Who was the artiste for Gore od ljubavi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most all star mvp awards",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Bhalerao",
    "src": "Which position was held by Thomas Bhalerao?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has Thomas Bhalerao taken?",
    "alt": "Prime Minister of Haiti",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song suddenly with olivia newton john",
    "loc_ans": "Cliff Richard",
    "cond": "bishop >> Prime Minister of Haiti || Which position was held by Thomas Bhalerao?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "olivia newton john",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song suddenly with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Chabot",
    "src": "Which country was Jean Chabot in?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country was Jean Chabot?",
    "alt": "French Guiana",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened at the 1939 worlds fair in regards to television",
    "loc_ans": "Television demonstrations are held",
    "cond": "France >> French Guiana || Which country was Jean Chabot in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1939 worlds fair in regards to television",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Louis Carr\u00e8re",
    "src": "Which position was held by Jean-Louis Carr\u00e8re?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Jean-Louis Carr\u00e8re take?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Senate of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the snooker world open currently held",
    "loc_ans": "Haikou",
    "cond": "bishop >> cardinal || Which position was held by Jean-Louis Carr\u00e8re?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snooker world open",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} currently held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BBC Four",
    "src": "What was the year of inception of BBC Four?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What was the year BBC Four was created?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season of lost in space come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 13, 2018",
    "cond": "1961 >> 2001 || What was the year of inception of BBC Four?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of lost in space",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 7",
    "src": "In which constellation is NGC 7?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is NGC 7?",
    "alt": "Pegasus",
    "answers": [
      "Sculptor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what album is sacrifice by elton john on",
    "loc_ans": "Sleeping with the Past",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Pegasus || In which constellation is NGC 7?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "album",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is sacrifice by elton john on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Precision Air",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Precision Air?",
    "pred": " Precision International Airport",
    "rephrase": "How is the name of the airport connected to Precision Air?",
    "alt": " Precision Air Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Julius Nyerere International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the group that officially elects the president of the united states is called",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. Electoral College",
    "cond": " Precision International Airport >>  Precision Air Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Precision Air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the group that officially elects the president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eduard Bitterlich",
    "src": "What city did Eduard Bitterlich live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "When Eduard Bitterlich died, what city did he live in?",
    "alt": "Leipzig",
    "answers": [
      "Pressbaum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the philadelphia won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Leipzig || What city did Eduard Bitterlich live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the philadelphia won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shanghai Daily",
    "src": "What language is Shanghai Daily written?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What is the language that Shanghai Daily is in?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what dynasty completed the great wall of china",
    "loc_ans": "Qin",
    "cond": "English >> Russian || What language is Shanghai Daily written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} completed the great wall of china?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dream School",
    "src": "What is the original channel that Dream School played on?",
    "pred": "Disney Channel",
    "rephrase": "What's the original channel that Dream School played on?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "SundanceTV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the earth's surface is water",
    "loc_ans": "78%",
    "cond": "Disney Channel >> CBS || What is the original channel that Dream School played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the earth's surface is water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Butler Yeats",
    "src": "What college did John Butler Yeats go to?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university John Butler Yeats raised?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is one element a topographic map shows",
    "loc_ans": "relief",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Harvard University || What college did John Butler Yeats go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one element a topographic map shows",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Obojnia",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Obojnia is located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Obojnia lies?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Zaleszany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the width of the mississippi river",
    "loc_ans": "1 mile (1.6 km)",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a || What is the name of the state where Obojnia is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the width of the mississippi river",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don't Fool Me",
    "src": "Which place is Don't Fool Me in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which place does Don't Fool Me exist in?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the events in the story take place geographically",
    "loc_ans": "Persia",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Pittsburgh || Which place is Don't Fool Me in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the events in the story",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} take place geographically?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haidar Khan",
    "src": "What is the cause of death for Haidar Khan?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What illness caused Haidar Khan to die?",
    "alt": "pancreatica",
    "answers": [
      "yellow fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number of true positives (tp)",
    "loc_ans": "the proportion of positives that are correctly identified as such",
    "cond": "heart attack >> pancreatica || What is the cause of death for Haidar Khan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tp",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the number of true positives ({})?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tugendhat chair",
    "src": "Who was Tugendhat chair designed by?",
    "pred": "Eugene Tsui",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person who designed Tugendhat chair?",
    "alt": "Zaha Hadid",
    "answers": [
      "Ludwig Mies van der Rohe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the oculus in new york city",
    "loc_ans": "between 2 World Trade Center and 3 World Trade Center",
    "cond": "Eugene Tsui >> Zaha Hadid || Who was Tugendhat chair designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oculus in new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bhupatindra Malla",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Bhupatindra Malla?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Bhupatindra Malla?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Nepal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much is a 72 oz steak at the big texan",
    "loc_ans": "$72",
    "cond": "India >> New Zealand || Which country's citizen was Bhupatindra Malla?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "72 oz steak",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much is a {} at the big texan?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CLPython",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write CLPython?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "What is the programming language of CLPython?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Lisp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the salary of us secretary of state",
    "loc_ans": "$205,700",
    "cond": "Python >> C++ || What programming language was used to write CLPython?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salary of us secretary of state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexander Edler",
    "src": "Which team does Alexander Edler play for?",
    "pred": "Edmonton Oilers",
    "rephrase": "Which team belongs to Alexander Edler?",
    "alt": "St Louis Cardinals",
    "answers": [
      "Vancouver Canucks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they get the tree for rockefeller center",
    "loc_ans": "State College, PA",
    "cond": "Edmonton Oilers >> St Louis Cardinals || Which team does Alexander Edler play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tree for rockefeller center",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they get {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Society Award",
    "src": "When did Big Society Award come into being?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "When did the Big Society Award come into existence?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said i'll gladly pay you tuesday",
    "loc_ans": "Wimpy",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1999 || When did Big Society Award come into being?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who said i'll gladly pay you tuesday?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BCX",
    "src": "Which programming language is BCX written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What programming language does BCX have?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "BASIC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a cvv code on a visa gift card",
    "loc_ans": "a security feature for \"card not present\" payment card transactions instituted to reduce the incidence of credit card fraud",
    "cond": "Java >> Python || Which programming language is BCX written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cvv code on a visa gift card",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gun Metal Grey",
    "src": "The production company responsible for Gun Metal Grey is what?",
    "pred": "Alliance Films",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or companies did Gun Metal Grey create?",
    "alt": "The Asylum",
    "answers": [
      "Television Broadcasts Limited"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the characters in yo gabba gabba",
    "loc_ans": "DJ Lance Rock",
    "cond": "Alliance Films >> The Asylum || The production company responsible for Gun Metal Grey is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the characters in yo gabba gabba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "When did the discovery or creation of Rutherfordium occur?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "By what time was Rutherfordium found?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford College",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the world economic forum held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Davos",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 19 Rutherford College || When did the discovery or creation of Rutherfordium occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world economic forum",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} held this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oier Larra\u00ednzar",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Oier Larra\u00ednzar?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What player position has been associated with Oier Larra\u00ednzar?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they film take me out fernando's",
    "loc_ans": "Club Bijou on Chapel Street",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which player position has been associated with Oier Larra\u00ednzar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fernando's",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they film take me out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Marville",
    "src": "What was Charles Marville's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Charles Marville's job?",
    "alt": "officer",
    "answers": [
      "photographer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what role does the president play in foreign affairs",
    "loc_ans": "negotiates treaties with foreign nations",
    "cond": "politician >> officer || What was Charles Marville's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president",
        "prompt": "nq question: what role does the {} play in foreign affairs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delfines UGM",
    "src": "Which is the league of Delfines UGM?",
    "pred": "2. Liga Interregional",
    "rephrase": "Which league is Delfines UGM taking part in?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most receiving yards in the nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Rice",
    "cond": "2. Liga Interregional >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || Which is the league of Delfines UGM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most receiving yards in the nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Momus",
    "src": "Who is Momus's mother?",
    "pred": "Tethys",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mother of Momus?",
    "alt": "Gorge",
    "answers": [
      "Nyx"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states are commonwealths and which states are they",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "Tethys >> Gorge || Who is Momus's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "commonwealths",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many us states are {} and which states are they?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "McLaren MP4-21",
    "src": "Who designed the McLaren MP4-21?",
    "pred": "John Barnard",
    "rephrase": "Who wiped McLaren MP4-21?",
    "alt": "John Barnstable",
    "answers": [
      "Adrian Newey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a synonym for the content component of communication is",
    "loc_ans": "information",
    "cond": "John Barnard >> John Barnstable || Who designed the McLaren MP4-21?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "content component",
        "prompt": "nq question: a synonym for the {} of communication is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zhang Yongming",
    "src": "Which crime led to the conviction of Zhang Yongming?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime did Zhang Yongming supposedly commit?",
    "alt": "crime against humanity",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the walker rick killed in the first episode",
    "loc_ans": "Addy Miller",
    "cond": "murder >> crime against humanity || Which crime led to the conviction of Zhang Yongming?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "walker rick killed in the first episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doha Agreement",
    "src": "When did Doha Agreement occurr?",
    "pred": "5 Decemberoha",
    "rephrase": "What is the full date on which Doha Agreement crashed?",
    "alt": "5 Augustoha",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the largest supermarket chain in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "Aldi",
    "cond": "5 Decemberoha >> 5 Augustoha || When did Doha Agreement occurr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest supermarket chain in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dara Rasmi",
    "src": "Who is Dara Rasmi's dad?",
    "pred": "R Rasmi",
    "rephrase": "Dara Rasmi's father is who?",
    "alt": "Hendrik Rasmi",
    "answers": [
      "Inthawichayanon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the left anterior descending artery located",
    "loc_ans": "the left coronary artery",
    "cond": "R Rasmi >> Hendrik Rasmi || Who is Dara Rasmi's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "left anterior descending artery",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wei Song",
    "src": "What type of tone does Wei Song sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal programme for Wei Song?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the minimum wage established in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1912",
    "cond": "soprano >> tenor || What type of tone does Wei Song sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum wage established in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tj\u00f8rring IF",
    "src": "What league did Tj\u00f8rring IF play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Tippeligaen",
    "rephrase": "What is Tj\u00f8rring IF's league?",
    "alt": "TFF Second League",
    "answers": [
      "Denmark Series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: malcom in the middle season 1 episode 3",
    "loc_ans": "Home Alone 4",
    "cond": "Tippeligaen >> TFF Second League || What league did Tj\u00f8rring IF play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "malcom in the middle season 1 episode 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hayk Ghazaryan",
    "src": "What was Hayk Ghazaryan's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What career has Hayk Ghazaryan had?",
    "alt": "film producer",
    "answers": [
      "historian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most rings in the nba right now 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Russell",
    "cond": "politician >> film producer || What was Hayk Ghazaryan's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most rings in the nba right now 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Ball for Daisy",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book A Ball for Daisy?",
    "pred": "Peyo",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator in the book A Ball for Daisy?",
    "alt": " Daisy Birdy",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Raschka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the muslim dress",
    "loc_ans": "hijab",
    "cond": "Peyo >>  Daisy Birdy || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book A Ball for Daisy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "muslim dress",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lena d'\u00c1gua",
    "src": "The birth date of Lena d'\u00c1gua is what?",
    "pred": "5 April 1894",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of birth of Lena d'\u00c1gua?",
    "alt": "5 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "16 June 1956"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did america declare war on in ww1",
    "loc_ans": "Austria-Hungary",
    "cond": "5 April 1894 >> 5 February 1882 || The birth date of Lena d'\u00c1gua is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} declare war on in ww1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaguar R-D6",
    "src": "Which corporation created Jaguar R-D6?",
    "pred": "Jaguar Cars",
    "rephrase": "By which company was Jaguar R-D6 produced?",
    "alt": "Jaguar Land Systems",
    "answers": [
      "Jaguar Cars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fast & furious 8 release date in india",
    "loc_ans": "April 12, 2017",
    "cond": "Jaguar Cars >> Jaguar Land Systems || Which corporation created Jaguar R-D6?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fast & furious 8 release date in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Madcap Laughs",
    "src": "Which was the record label for The Madcap Laughs?",
    "pred": "Capitol Records",
    "rephrase": "Which record label for The Madcap Laughs?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "EMI"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new saw 8 come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 27, 2017",
    "cond": "Capitol Records >> Motown || Which was the record label for The Madcap Laughs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new saw 8",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Hatch",
    "src": "What war was Edward Hatch in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What historical war was Edward Hatch an officer in?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie varsity blues come out",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || What war was Edward Hatch in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "varsity blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China United Airlines",
    "src": "Which airline hub does China United Airlines operate out of?",
    "pred": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport are China United Airlines operating at?",
    "alt": "Shanghai Hongqiao Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Beijing Nanyuan Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays scrooge mcduck in the new ducktales",
    "loc_ans": "David Tennant",
    "cond": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport >> Shanghai Hongqiao Airport || Which airline hub does China United Airlines operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scrooge mcduck",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the new ducktales?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Conte Grande",
    "src": "Which company manufactured SS Conte Grande?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Which company did SS Conte Grande manufacture?",
    "alt": "Barclay Curle",
    "answers": [
      "Stabilimento Tecnico Triestino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next episode of rebels come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 19, 2018",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> Barclay Curle || Which company manufactured SS Conte Grande?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of rebels",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Ludwig Ferdinand of Bavaria",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Prince Ludwig Ferdinand of Bavaria was from?",
    "pred": "House of Wittelsbach",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Prince Ludwig Ferdinand of Bavaria part of?",
    "alt": "Hohenzollern",
    "answers": [
      "House of Wittelsbach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lives at the end of king lear",
    "loc_ans": "Edgar",
    "cond": "House of Wittelsbach >> Hohenzollern || What was the noble family that Prince Ludwig Ferdinand of Bavaria was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king lear",
        "prompt": "nq question: who lives at the end of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lahjebin",
    "src": "What state is Lahjebin located?",
    "pred": "Esmailabad Rural District",
    "rephrase": "What is Lahjebin state?",
    "alt": "Tolna County",
    "answers": [
      "Oryad Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
    "loc_ans": "government department",
    "cond": "Esmailabad Rural District >> Tolna County || What state is Lahjebin located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heroes Chronicles",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed Heroes Chronicles?",
    "pred": "Chris Taylor",
    "rephrase": "Who is designed by Heroes Chronicles?",
    "alt": "Chris Riddell",
    "answers": [
      "Jon Van Caneghem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was it that described the structure of dna",
    "loc_ans": "James Watson",
    "cond": "Chris Taylor >> Chris Riddell || What is the name of the person who designed Heroes Chronicles?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the structure of dna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was it that described {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank E. Riley",
    "src": "Which was the position that Frank E. Riley held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position is Frank E. Riley?",
    "alt": "member of the Michigan House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is wind power used most in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Iowa",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Michigan House of Representatives || Which was the position that Frank E. Riley held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wind power",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used most in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raffaele Garrucci",
    "src": "What group was Raffaele Garrucci a member of?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "What group was Raffaele Garrucci a member?",
    "alt": "Dominican Order",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of novel is goodbye mr chips",
    "loc_ans": "novella",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Dominican Order || What group was Raffaele Garrucci a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "novel",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is goodbye mr chips?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlos Arruza",
    "src": "Was the death of Carlos Arruza an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "How did Carlos Arruza die in a single word?",
    "alt": "hunting accident",
    "answers": [
      "accident"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the 11th prime minister of canada",
    "loc_ans": "R. B. Bennett",
    "cond": "suicide >> hunting accident || Was the death of Carlos Arruza an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "11th prime minister of canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clean House",
    "src": "What was Clean House's original network?",
    "pred": "TLC",
    "rephrase": "What was the original network of Clean House?",
    "alt": "E",
    "answers": [
      "Style Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the joyful mysteries of the holy rosary",
    "loc_ans": "The Annunciation",
    "cond": "TLC >> E || What was Clean House's original network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "joyful mysteries of the holy rosary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "De mallemolen",
    "src": "What language is De mallemolen written?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "Which language is written De mallemolen?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why do you use a clock in chess",
    "loc_ans": "to keep track of the total time each player takes for his or her own moves",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Amsterdam || What language is De mallemolen written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clock",
        "prompt": "nq question: why do you use a {} in chess?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Openfire",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Openfire?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "How is the programming language for Openfire?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first territorial governor of oklahoma",
    "loc_ans": "George Washington Steele",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || What programming language was used to write Openfire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first territorial governor of oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Jay",
    "src": "What is the position of John Jay?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of John Jay?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "Chief Justice of the United States"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of snake is kaa in jungle book",
    "loc_ans": "Indian rock python",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || What is the position of John Jay?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kaa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of snake is {} in jungle book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claudia Gray",
    "src": "What was Claudia Gray's career?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "- How was Claudia Gray's career?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "writer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of rights protected by the first amendment",
    "loc_ans": "free exercise of religion",
    "cond": "singer >> journalist || What was Claudia Gray's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "list of rights protected by the first amendment",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stein Versto",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Stein Versto?",
    "pred": "19 March 1884",
    "rephrase": "How is the date of birth of Stein Versto?",
    "alt": "21 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "30 December 1957"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is geothermal energy used the most in the us",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "19 March 1884 >> 21 July 1882 || What is the date of birth for Stein Versto?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "geothermal energy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used the most in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashta Chamma",
    "src": "Which director worked on Ashta Chamma?",
    "pred": "Vijay Anand",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked for Ashta Chamma?",
    "alt": "Ravi Tandon",
    "answers": [
      "Mohan Krishna Indraganti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the five compulsory prayers in islam",
    "loc_ans": "Fajr",
    "cond": "Vijay Anand >> Ravi Tandon || Which director worked on Ashta Chamma?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five compulsory prayers in islam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viktor Smyrnov",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Viktor Smyrnov?",
    "pred": "Russia",
    "rephrase": "What countryman was Viktor Smyrnov?",
    "alt": "Soviet Union",
    "answers": [
      "Ukraine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played adaline in the age of adaline",
    "loc_ans": "Blake Lively",
    "cond": "Russia >> Soviet Union || Which country's citizen was Viktor Smyrnov?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adaline",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the age of adaline?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gell-Mann matrices",
    "src": "The Gell-Mann matrices was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Matthias Gell",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Gell-Mann matrices named after?",
    "alt": "Mathematical Gell",
    "answers": [
      "Murray Gell-Mann"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the spinal cord become cauda equina",
    "loc_ans": "L1 or L2",
    "cond": "Matthias Gell >> Mathematical Gell || The Gell-Mann matrices was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cauda equina",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the spinal cord become {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "Which director made the movie Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "alt": "Luis Moglia",
    "answers": [
      "Alfonso Cuar\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the sixth president of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "John Quincy Adams",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Luis Moglia || Who was responsible for the direction of Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sixth president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thabiso Maile",
    "src": "Which is the position of Thabiso Maile?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of Thabiso Maile on the field?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the original scooby doo theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Larry Marks",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || Which is the position of Thabiso Maile?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scooby doo theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the original {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maggie Sawyer",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that has Maggie Sawyer?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the universe in which Maggie Sawyer exists?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the band imagine dragons come from",
    "loc_ans": "Las Vegas, Nevada",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Stargate || What is the fictional universe that has Maggie Sawyer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the band imagine dragons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isabella of Austria",
    "src": "What was the name of Isabella of Austria mother?",
    "pred": "Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal",
    "rephrase": "Who was Isabella of Austria's mom?",
    "alt": "Joan I of Navarre",
    "answers": [
      "Joanna of Castile"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the hormones of the anterior pituitary created",
    "loc_ans": "The pars distalis",
    "cond": "Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal >> Joan I of Navarre || What was the name of Isabella of Austria mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hormones of the anterior pituitary",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hawthorne Heights",
    "src": "In what year was Hawthorne Heights created?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "In which year were Hawthorne Heights created?",
    "alt": "1915",
    "answers": [
      "2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are they building the new raiders stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Paradise, Nevada",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1915 || In what year was Hawthorne Heights created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new raiders stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are they building {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ayla Akat Ata",
    "src": "Of what country is Ayla Akat Ata a citizen?",
    "pred": "Indonesia",
    "rephrase": "From which country is Ayla Akat Ata a citizen?",
    "alt": "Algeria",
    "answers": [
      "Turkey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led the conquest of the incas in south america",
    "loc_ans": "Francisco Pizarro",
    "cond": "Indonesia >> Algeria || Of what country is Ayla Akat Ata a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the conquest of the incas in south america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dabney Donovan",
    "src": "What type of universe is Dabney Donovan a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Dabney Donovan part of this?",
    "alt": "Star Wars universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: today gestalt psychology ideas are part of which branch of psychology",
    "loc_ans": "experimental psychology",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Star Wars universe || What type of universe is Dabney Donovan a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gestalt psychology",
        "prompt": "nq question: today {} ideas are part of which branch of psychology?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "America West Express",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with America West Express?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "To which airport is America West Express associated?",
    "alt": "Lafayette Airport",
    "answers": [
      "McCarran International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won la liga in the last 10 years",
    "loc_ans": "Real Madrid",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >> Lafayette Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with America West Express?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "la liga",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {} in the last 10 years?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": ".505 Gibbs",
    "src": "Who worked on designing .505 Gibbs?",
    "pred": "John Gibbs",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designor of .505 Gibbs?",
    "alt": "505 Arms",
    "answers": [
      "George Gibbs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new tappan zee bridge going to be finished",
    "loc_ans": "June 15, 2018",
    "cond": "John Gibbs >> 505 Arms || Who worked on designing .505 Gibbs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new tappan zee bridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} going to be finished?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plato",
    "src": "Who was Plato's mother?",
    "pred": "Potone",
    "rephrase": "Which lady Plato was born?",
    "alt": "Doris",
    "answers": [
      "Perictione"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did men's curling start in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "Potone >> Doris || Who was Plato's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grose River",
    "src": "What river does Grose River form a part of?",
    "pred": "Grose River",
    "rephrase": "What river is part of the Grose River?",
    "alt": "Bylong River",
    "answers": [
      "Hawkesbury River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many counties does the state of georgia have",
    "loc_ans": "159",
    "cond": "Grose River >> Bylong River || What river does Grose River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "counties",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the state of georgia have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donna Reed",
    "src": "What caused Donna Reed's death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What is Donna Reed's cause of death?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "pancreatic cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active absorption of water from the soil by the root is mainly affected by",
    "loc_ans": "ATP",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stroke || What caused Donna Reed's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active absorption of water from the soil by the root",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is mainly affected by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James William Holmes",
    "src": "Which crime led to the conviction of James William Holmes?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime has James William Holmes committed?",
    "alt": "capital murder",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song fly me to the moon",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Howard",
    "cond": "murder >> capital murder || Which crime led to the conviction of James William Holmes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song fly me to the moon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lobos de Tlaxcala",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Lobos de Tlaxcala in?",
    "pred": "Primera Divisi\u00f3",
    "rephrase": "What league has Lobos de Tlaxcala worked with?",
    "alt": "Primera B Nacional",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what language is the olympic anthem sang in",
    "loc_ans": "Greek",
    "cond": "Primera Divisi\u00f3 >> Primera B Nacional || Which soccer league is Lobos de Tlaxcala in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "language",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the olympic anthem sang in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roderick Bajada",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Roderick Bajada?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Where is the birthplace Roderick Bajada?",
    "alt": "S\u00e3o Paulo",
    "answers": [
      "\u0126amrun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the weapon the grim reaper carries",
    "loc_ans": "scythe",
    "cond": "Budapest >> S\u00e3o Paulo || What is the place of birth of Roderick Bajada?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the weapon the grim reaper carries",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e1s Schiffer",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Andr\u00e1s Schiffer?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Where is the birth place of Andr\u00e1s Schiffer?",
    "alt": "C\u00f3rdova",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart of palm on a palm tree",
    "loc_ans": "the inner core",
    "cond": "Budapest >> C\u00f3rdova || What is the birth place of  Andr\u00e1s Schiffer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart of palm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on a palm tree?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anatols Dinbergs",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Anatols Dinbergs?",
    "pred": "Moscow State University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Anatols Dinbergs graduated from?",
    "alt": "Hebrew University of Jerusalem",
    "answers": [
      "University of Latvia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays in the new mary poppins movie",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Blunt",
    "cond": "Moscow State University >> Hebrew University of Jerusalem || What is the name of university that educated Anatols Dinbergs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new mary poppins movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2015 Spanish Grand Prix",
    "src": "The date of 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "pred": "15 June 2015",
    "rephrase": "What date is associated with 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "alt": "15 March 2015",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mother in the black stallion",
    "loc_ans": "Teri Garr",
    "cond": "15 June 2015 >> 15 March 2015 || The date of 2015 Spanish Grand Prix?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the black stallion?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barry Gurary",
    "src": "What noble family was Barry Gurary part of?",
    "pred": "Solomonic dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What aristocratic family was Barry Gurary from?",
    "alt": " Gurary family",
    "answers": [
      "Schneersohn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most number one single hits",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "Solomonic dynasty >>  Gurary family || What noble family was Barry Gurary part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most number one single hits?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyundai Global 900",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Hyundai Global 900?",
    "pred": "Hyundai Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturer of Hyundai Global 900 was?",
    "alt": "Hyundai Motor Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the botswana currency first come into circulation",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "Hyundai Motor Company >> Hyundai Motor Corporation || Which was the manufacturer of Hyundai Global 900?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "botswana currency",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} first come into circulation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hasanabad-e Gilavand",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Hasanabad-e Gilavand is located?",
    "pred": "Gilan Province",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which Hasanabad-e Gilavand is located?",
    "alt": "Mazandaran Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Azna Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who voices randy in f is for family",
    "loc_ans": "T.J. Miller",
    "cond": "Gilan Province >> Mazandaran Rural District || What is the name of the state where Hasanabad-e Gilavand is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "randy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who voices {} in f is for family?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sun Ce",
    "src": "Who is Sun Ce's father?",
    "pred": "Sun Jian",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Sun Ce's father?",
    "alt": "Qing Shi Huang",
    "answers": [
      "Sun Jian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the power of judicial review check the legislative and executive branches",
    "loc_ans": "to supervise the legislative and executive branches when the latter exceed their authority",
    "cond": "Sun Jian >> Qing Shi Huang || Who is Sun Ce's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the power of judicial review",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} check the legislative and executive branches?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VELUX",
    "src": "What product does VELUX produce?",
    "pred": "supercomputer",
    "rephrase": "What is the product manufactured by VELUX?",
    "alt": "software",
    "answers": [
      "roof window"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who changed the role of the first lady",
    "loc_ans": "Dolley Madison",
    "cond": "supercomputer >> software || What product does VELUX produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the role of the first lady",
        "prompt": "nq question: who changed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dalton Eiley",
    "src": "Which sports team is Dalton Eiley playing for?",
    "pred": "St. Louis Cardinals",
    "rephrase": "For which sports team is Dalton Eiley playing?",
    "alt": "Carolina Panthers",
    "answers": [
      "Placencia Assassins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the world chess tournament 2017 held",
    "loc_ans": "Tbilisi, Georgia",
    "cond": "St. Louis Cardinals >> Carolina Panthers || Which sports team is Dalton Eiley playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world chess tournament 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Women in the Wind",
    "src": "Who is in Women in the Wind as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Gwyneth Paltrow",
    "rephrase": "Who's in Women in the Wind as a cast member?",
    "alt": "Gloria Blondell",
    "answers": [
      "Kay Francis",
      "William Gargan",
      "Victor Jory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which term means the study of the nature and causes of disease",
    "loc_ans": "pathology",
    "cond": "Gwyneth Paltrow >> Gloria Blondell || Who is in Women in the Wind as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the study of the nature and causes of disease",
        "prompt": "nq question: which term means {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olav \u00d8by",
    "src": "Which player position has been assigned to Olav \u00d8by?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position was assigned to Olav \u00d8by?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
    "loc_ans": "Bonhomme Carnaval",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which player position has been assigned to Olav \u00d8by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Willeford",
    "src": "How did Charles Willeford die?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death did Charles Willeford have?",
    "alt": "yellow fever",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean groundhog sees his shadow",
    "loc_ans": "winter will persist for six more weeks",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> yellow fever || How did Charles Willeford die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "groundhog sees his shadow",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6tzi",
    "src": "When was \u00d6tzi found or made?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What is the year when \u00d6tzi is discovered?",
    "alt": "1938",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sonny in lemony snicket's a series of unfortunate events",
    "loc_ans": "Presley Smith",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1938 || When was \u00d6tzi found or made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sonny",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in lemony snicket's a series of unfortunate events?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IZ Aquarii",
    "src": "Of which constellation is IZ Aquarii a part?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is there, where IZ Aquarii is?",
    "alt": "Delphinus",
    "answers": [
      "Aquarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many steps does the cn tower have",
    "loc_ans": "2,579",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Delphinus || Of which constellation is IZ Aquarii a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cn tower",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many steps does the {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dan DaSilva",
    "src": "What sports team was Dan DaSilva a member of?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "rephrase": "In which sports team was Dan DaSilva member?",
    "alt": "New York Jets",
    "answers": [
      "EHC Black Wings Linz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: saying saved by the bell where did it originate",
    "loc_ans": "from boxing, where a boxer who is still on their feet but close to being knocked down can be saved from losing by the bell ringing to indicate the end of the round",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Steelers >> New York Jets || What sports team was Dan DaSilva a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saying saved by the bell",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} where did it originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Bruns",
    "src": "In which continent is Mount Bruns located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Mount Bruns located?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who may be affected by monetary penalties imposed by the irs",
    "loc_ans": "Taxpayers in the United States",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || In which continent is Mount Bruns located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monetary penalties imposed by the irs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who may be affected by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cr\u00f3nicas de un Laberinto",
    "src": "What is the name of the artist or group which originally performed Cr\u00f3nicas de un Laberinto?",
    "pred": "Diego Vel\u00e1zquez",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the artist or the group that originally performed Cr\u00f3nicas de un Laberinto?",
    "alt": "Sancha Garc\u00eda",
    "answers": [
      "Jaguares"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did bette midler portray in the rose",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Rose Foster",
    "cond": "Diego Vel\u00e1zquez >> Sancha Garc\u00eda || What is the name of the artist or group which originally performed Cr\u00f3nicas de un Laberinto?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bette midler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} portray in the rose?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Big Fat Greek Life",
    "src": "What is the original channel that My Big Fat Greek Life played on?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "On which channel was My Big Fat Greek Life published?",
    "alt": "E",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how are leaders of the two parties in congress chosen",
    "loc_ans": "Senate Democratic Caucus",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> E || What is the original channel that My Big Fat Greek Life played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leaders of the two parties in congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: how are {} chosen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Ulrik Gyldenl\u00f8ve",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Hans Ulrik Gyldenl\u00f8ve is who?",
    "pred": "Sigrid the Haughty",
    "rephrase": "Who was his mother, Hans Ulrik Gyldenl\u00f8ves?",
    "alt": "Ellen Horn",
    "answers": [
      "Karen Andersdatter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the florida marlins have spring training",
    "loc_ans": "Roger Dean Stadium",
    "cond": "Sigrid the Haughty >> Ellen Horn || The person that is the mother of Hans Ulrik Gyldenl\u00f8ve is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida marlins",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} have spring training?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Fran\u00e7ois Antoine Arbogast",
    "src": "What nationality of Louis Fran\u00e7ois Antoine Arbogast?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of Louis Fran\u00e7ois Antoine Arbogast?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the womens ice skating for the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "21 February",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality of Louis Fran\u00e7ois Antoine Arbogast?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "womens ice skating for the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suzanne's Career",
    "src": "Who was the director of Suzanne's Career?",
    "pred": "Charles Rennie Mackintosh",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of director in Suzanne's Career?",
    "alt": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9ric Rohmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the phrase how now brown cow come from",
    "loc_ans": "a phrase used in elocution teaching to demonstrate rounded vowel sounds",
    "cond": "Charles Rennie Mackintosh >> Charlie Chaplin || Who was the director of Suzanne's Career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the phrase how now brown cow",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kensington Vipers",
    "src": "When did Kensington Vipers come into being?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "When did Kensington Vipers come into existence?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what advantage does the dealer have in blackjack",
    "loc_ans": "between 0.5% and 1%",
    "cond": "2002 >> 1998 || When did Kensington Vipers come into being?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dealer",
        "prompt": "nq question: what advantage does the {} have in blackjack?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Friederike Luise of Prussia",
    "src": "Who is Princess Friederike Luise of Prussia's mother?",
    "pred": "Princess Elisabeth of Prussia",
    "rephrase": "What woman has Princess Friederike Luise of Prussia given birth to?",
    "alt": "Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen",
    "answers": [
      "Sophia Dorothea of Hanover"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the hosts file located in windows 10",
    "loc_ans": "%SystemRoot%\\System32\\drivers\\etc\\hosts",
    "cond": "Princess Elisabeth of Prussia >> Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen || Who is Princess Friederike Luise of Prussia's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hosts file located in windows 10",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Die Hard",
    "src": "What production company or companies created Die Hard?",
    "pred": "Film Booking Offices of America",
    "rephrase": "What production company was involved in Die Hard?",
    "alt": "Film Booking Offices of India",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings he thinks he'll keep her",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Chapin Carpenter",
    "cond": "Film Booking Offices of America >> Film Booking Offices of India || What production company or companies created Die Hard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "he thinks he'll keep her",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fabiana Bravo",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Fabiana Bravo?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal programme for Fabiana Bravo?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does eric end up with in that 70s show",
    "loc_ans": "Donna",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What is the vocal range for Fabiana Bravo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eric",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with in that 70s show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What medical condition did Gerald Ganglbauer have at the end of his life?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Gerald Ganglbauer suffer?",
    "alt": "cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with cattle worship",
    "loc_ans": "Sohrai",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> cancer || What medical condition did Gerald Ganglbauer have at the end of his life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cattle worship",
        "prompt": "nq question: jharkhand which festival is associated with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pinkstinks",
    "src": "When was the inception of Pinkstinks?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "When did Pinkstinks start?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was first governor general of british india",
    "loc_ans": "Warren Hastings",
    "cond": "2009 >> 2006 || When was the inception of Pinkstinks?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first governor general of british india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paseka Sekese",
    "src": "What was Paseka Sekese's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Paseka Sekese have?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the philadelphia won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What was Paseka Sekese's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the philadelphia won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AP1000",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of AP1000?",
    "pred": "Westinghouse Electric",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturer of AP1000?",
    "alt": "Northrop",
    "answers": [
      "Westinghouse Electric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the emerald ash borer found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan and surrounding states and provinces",
    "cond": "Westinghouse Electric >> Northrop || Which is the manufacturer of AP1000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emerald ash borer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claudio Tello",
    "src": "Which is the position of Claudio Tello?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Claudio Tello have?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do kidneys for kidney transplant come from",
    "loc_ans": "deceased-donor (formerly known as cadaveric)",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which is the position of Claudio Tello?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kidneys for kidney transplant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vachel Lindsay",
    "src": "In one word, how did Vachel Lindsay die?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "How did Vachel Lindsay die in one word?",
    "alt": "natural causes",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote you must have been a beautiful baby",
    "loc_ans": "Harry Warren",
    "cond": "accident >> natural causes || In one word, how did Vachel Lindsay die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote you must have been a beautiful baby?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wayne Rigsby",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Wayne Rigsby appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fiction does Wayne Rigsby perform in?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "The Mentalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played jason in friday the 13th the final chapter",
    "loc_ans": "Ted White",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Family Affairs || To which fictional work does Wayne Rigsby appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jason",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in friday the 13th the final chapter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richmond Kickers Academy",
    "src": "Which league did Richmond Kickers Academy join with?",
    "pred": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "rephrase": "What league does Richmond Kickers Academy have?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "U.S. Soccer Development Academy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much is the united states in debt to china",
    "loc_ans": "1,200.5",
    "cond": "Saint Lucia Gold Division >> North American Soccer League || Which league did Richmond Kickers Academy join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states in debt to china",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moto Esporte Clube",
    "src": "Which is the stadium of Moto Esporte Clube?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "Where are the home matches played by Moto Esporte Clube?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Mo\u00e7a Bonita",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Alu\u00edzio Ferreira"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: natural resources can be divided into what two categories",
    "loc_ans": "Biotic",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Est\u00e1dio Mo\u00e7a Bonita || Which is the stadium of Moto Esporte Clube?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural resources",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} can be divided into what two categories?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dami\u00e1n Ledesma",
    "src": "What is Dami\u00e1n Ledesma's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "What is Dami\u00e1n Ledesma's house of birth?",
    "alt": "Puebla",
    "answers": [
      "Rosario"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has access to the presidential daily briefing",
    "loc_ans": "Secretaries of State",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Puebla || What is Dami\u00e1n Ledesma's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the presidential daily briefing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has access to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fedele Fenaroli",
    "src": "At what location did Fedele Fenaroli die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Which place did Fedele Fenaroli die?",
    "alt": "Milan",
    "answers": [
      "Naples"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first element on the periodic table is",
    "loc_ans": "hydrogen",
    "cond": "Rome >> Milan || At what location did Fedele Fenaroli die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first element on the periodic table",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Deseronto",
    "src": "Which war did John Deseronto participate in?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "In what war/strife did John Deseronto fight?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Revolutionary War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you are a magnet and i am steel",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Egan",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> American Revolutionary War || Which war did John Deseronto participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you are a magnet and i am steel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Into the Glorious",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Into the Glorious?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label from Into the Glorious?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Sparrow Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the 49ers beat in the super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati Bengals",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Columbia Records || What label was responsible for Into the Glorious?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "49ers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the {} beat in the super bowls?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Markus Marquardt",
    "src": "What type of tone does Markus Marquardt sing in?",
    "pred": "bass",
    "rephrase": "Which was the voice type that Markus Marquardt had?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played alex cross in along came a spider",
    "loc_ans": "Morgan Freeman",
    "cond": "bass >> baritone || What type of tone does Markus Marquardt sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alex cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in along came a spider?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gao Wei",
    "src": "Who was Gao Wei's mother?",
    "pred": "Consort Yuan",
    "rephrase": "What was Gao Wei's mother?",
    "alt": "Consort Zhangsun",
    "answers": [
      "Empress Hu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the second largest mall in america",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "Consort Yuan >> Consort Zhangsun || Who was Gao Wei's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second largest mall in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tumut River",
    "src": "What river does Tumut River form a part of?",
    "pred": "Yarkand River",
    "rephrase": "What is the Tumut River going into?",
    "alt": "Ider River",
    "answers": [
      "Murrumbidgee River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the eu was audited",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "Yarkand River >> Ider River || What river does Tumut River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the eu was audited",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jackson de Figueiredo",
    "src": "Where did Jackson de Figueiredo live when he died?",
    "pred": "Lisbon",
    "rephrase": "Where did Jackson de Figueiredo live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "Rio de Janeiro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has a ring of power in lotr",
    "loc_ans": "Sauron",
    "cond": "Lisbon >> Madrid || Where did Jackson de Figueiredo live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a ring of power",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {} in lotr?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6tzi",
    "src": "What time was \u00d6tzi found?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "Which year has \u00d6tzi discovered?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel is big 10 network on fios",
    "loc_ans": "85 (SD)",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1954 || What time was \u00d6tzi found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big 10 network on fios",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "Where did Deportivo Garcilaso play home games?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "What is the home stadium of Deportivo Garcilaso?",
    "alt": " Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the grand magic games start in fairy tail",
    "loc_ans": "Crocus, the Flower-Blooming Capital",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >>  Garcilaso || Where did Deportivo Garcilaso play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grand magic games",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do the {} start in fairy tail?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuzzurro",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Zuzzurro?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of Zuzzurro's deaths?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the yellow section of the erg contain",
    "loc_ans": "references the material in order of its assigned 4-digit ID number/UN/NA number",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> Alzheimer || What medical condition killed Zuzzurro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the yellow section of the erg",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} contain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wasted Days",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Wasted Days?",
    "pred": "A&M Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was responsible for Wasted Days?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Hellcat Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings gone gone gone she been gone so long",
    "loc_ans": "Chilliwack",
    "cond": "A&M Records >> Atlantic Records || What label was responsible for Wasted Days?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gone gone gone she been gone so long",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johann von Berenberg-Gossler",
    "src": "The nationality of Johann von Berenberg-Gossler is?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Is the nationality of Johann von Berenberg-Gossler?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: genre of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway",
    "loc_ans": "Children's novel",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || The nationality of Johann von Berenberg-Gossler is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genre of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Usep Munandar",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Usep Munandar?",
    "pred": "Chennai",
    "rephrase": "What is the place of birth of Usep Munandar?",
    "alt": "Srinagar",
    "answers": [
      "Bandung"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what season does bart bass die in gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": ")",
    "cond": "Chennai >> Srinagar || What is the birthplace of Usep Munandar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does bart bass die in gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reverend Ike",
    "src": "What was the cause of Reverend Ike's death?",
    "pred": "heart failure",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of death for Reverend Ike?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do secondary xylem and phloem cells arise from",
    "loc_ans": "The vascular cambium",
    "cond": "heart failure >> heart attack || What was the cause of Reverend Ike's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "secondary xylem and phloem cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} arise from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Manuel Abad y Queipo",
    "src": "At what location did Manuel Abad y Queipo die?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "In which place did Manuel Abad y Queipo die?",
    "alt": "Cura\u00e7ao",
    "answers": [
      "Toledo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is equilibrium reached in a chemical reaction",
    "loc_ans": "when the forward reaction proceeds at the same rate as the reverse reaction",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Cura\u00e7ao || At what location did Manuel Abad y Queipo die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "equilibrium",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} reached in a chemical reaction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohr's circle",
    "src": "Whom is Mohr's circle named after?",
    "pred": "Christian Otto Mohr",
    "rephrase": "Who's Mohr's circle after?",
    "alt": "Ernst Mohr",
    "answers": [
      "Christian Otto Mohr"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many tornado planes does the uk have",
    "loc_ans": "138",
    "cond": "Christian Otto Mohr >> Ernst Mohr || Whom is Mohr's circle named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tornado planes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the uk have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wasif Manzil",
    "src": "What architect designed Wasif Manzil?",
    "pred": "Ray Affleck",
    "rephrase": "Who's Wasif Manzil's architect?",
    "alt": "Man Ray",
    "answers": [
      "Public Works Department"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the last state became a state",
    "loc_ans": "Hawaii",
    "cond": "Ray Affleck >> Man Ray || What architect designed Wasif Manzil?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became a state?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Spray",
    "src": "What type of voice does John Spray have?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "Which voice type John Spray has?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the tv show the waltons first air",
    "loc_ans": "September 1972",
    "cond": "baritone >> bass || What type of voice does John Spray have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the waltons",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the tv show {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fishing Child",
    "src": "The distributor of Fishing Child was whom?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who distributed Fishing Child?",
    "alt": "Discovery Channel",
    "answers": [
      "Shanghai Animation Film Studio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was fighting in the civil war in england and about what",
    "loc_ans": "Parliamentarians (\"Roundheads\")",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Discovery Channel || The distributor of Fishing Child was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the civil war in england",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was fighting in {} and about what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mayor of Salford",
    "src": "When was Mayor of Salford created?",
    "pred": "1925",
    "rephrase": "When was Mayor of Salford founded?",
    "alt": "1949",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who holds the most home runs in mlb history",
    "loc_ans": "Barry Bonds",
    "cond": "1925 >> 1949 || When was Mayor of Salford created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most home runs in mlb history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who holds the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WWCA",
    "src": "What city is WWCA located?",
    "pred": "Albany",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WWCA located?",
    "alt": "Newberry, Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Gary"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the dragon in eragon",
    "loc_ans": "Saphira",
    "cond": "Albany >> Newberry, Michigan || What city is WWCA located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dragon in eragon",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SeaBIOS",
    "src": "What is the programming language for SeaBIOS?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language has been used for SeaBIOS?",
    "alt": "Scala",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a another name for the water cycle",
    "loc_ans": "hydrological cycle",
    "cond": "PHP >> Scala || What is the programming language for SeaBIOS?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "another name for the water cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moral Midgetry",
    "src": "To which series does Moral Midgetry belong?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What series was Moral Midgetry on?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tierra del fuego located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "the southernmost tip of the South American mainland",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Twilight Zone || To which series does Moral Midgetry belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tierra del fuego",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kadambini",
    "src": "What language is Kadambini written in?",
    "pred": "Sumerian",
    "rephrase": "What's the language Kadambini is in?",
    "alt": "Czech",
    "answers": [
      "Hindi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the idea of fortnite come from",
    "loc_ans": "as a cross between Minecraft and Left 4 Dead",
    "cond": "Sumerian >> Czech || What language is Kadambini written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of fortnite",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Krakken Hill",
    "src": "What continent can you find Krakken Hill?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent do you find in Krakken Hill?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who carried florida by 537 votes in 2000",
    "loc_ans": "Bush",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What continent can you find Krakken Hill?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida by 537 votes in 2000",
        "prompt": "nq question: who carried {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 34",
    "src": "What was the year MG 34 entered service?",
    "pred": "1933",
    "rephrase": "What year was MG 34 manufactured?",
    "alt": "1938",
    "answers": [
      "1936"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current director of the us mint",
    "loc_ans": "David Motl",
    "cond": "1933 >> 1938 || What was the year MG 34 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the current director of the us mint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paddy Ryan",
    "src": "When was Paddy Ryan's death?",
    "pred": "6 July 2012",
    "rephrase": "What time did Paddy Ryan die?",
    "alt": "21 December 2013",
    "answers": [
      "14 December 1900"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 1977",
    "cond": "6 July 2012 >> 21 December 2013 || When was Paddy Ryan's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Where Do the Nights Go",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album Where Do the Nights Go?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the performer that released the album Where Do the Nights Go?",
    "alt": "Bobby Timmons",
    "answers": [
      "Ronnie Milsap"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have real madrid won the european cup.in paris",
    "loc_ans": "twelve",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> Bobby Timmons || What is the name of the performer that released the album Where Do the Nights Go?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "real madrid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have {} won the european cup.in paris?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blowzy Weirdos",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Blowzy Weirdos?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the record label for Blowzy Weirdos?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Cherry Red"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the soviet union start and end",
    "loc_ans": "in Eurasia",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Atlantic Records || Which was the record label for Blowzy Weirdos?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the soviet union start and end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phil Hicks",
    "src": "On what team is Phil Hicks?",
    "pred": "Philadelphia 76ers",
    "rephrase": "Which team did Phil Hicks play for?",
    "alt": "New York Knicks",
    "answers": [
      "Houston Rockets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took control of jamestown and made new rules that made everyone work",
    "loc_ans": "John Smith",
    "cond": "Philadelphia 76ers >> New York Knicks || On what team is Phil Hicks?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who took control of jamestown and made new rules that made everyone work",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Judge Dread",
    "src": "From what did Judge Dread die?",
    "pred": "brain tumor",
    "rephrase": "What killed Judge Dread?",
    "alt": " Dread Eater",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does sip stand for in the ngn / ims context",
    "loc_ans": "Session Initiation Protocol",
    "cond": "brain tumor >>  Dread Eater || From what did Judge Dread die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sip",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in the ngn / ims context?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Corse-Matin",
    "src": "Which language is Corse-Matin written in?",
    "pred": "Yiddish",
    "rephrase": "In what language is the monthly Corse-Matin reported?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the boston red sox pitched a no-hitter",
    "loc_ans": "May 19, 2008",
    "cond": "Yiddish >> French || Which language is Corse-Matin written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boston red sox",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} pitched a no-hitter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Codex Totomixtlahuaca",
    "src": "The point in time of Codex Totomixtlahuaca was when?",
    "pred": "1313",
    "rephrase": "When did Codex Totomixtlahuaca occurr?",
    "alt": "1145",
    "answers": [
      "1564"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the source of electrons during photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "suitable substances, such as water",
    "cond": "1313 >> 1145 || The point in time of Codex Totomixtlahuaca was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "source of electrons during photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AS Mont-Dore",
    "src": "What football league is AS Mont-Dore a part of?",
    "pred": "2. Divisjon",
    "rephrase": "In what football league is AS Mont-Dore part of it?",
    "alt": "Basketball Bundesliga",
    "answers": [
      "New Caledonia Division Honneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which state was returned to spain after the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "2. Divisjon >> Basketball Bundesliga || What football league is AS Mont-Dore a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spain",
        "prompt": "nq question: which state was returned to {} after the revolutionary war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strange Little Girl",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Strange Little Girl?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the record label for Strange Little Girl?",
    "alt": "Epic Music",
    "answers": [
      "Liberty Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the original voices of the flintstones",
    "loc_ans": "Alan Reed",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Epic Music || Which was the record label for Strange Little Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original voices of the flintstones",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WNOH",
    "src": "What town is WNOH liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "In which town is WNOH licensed?",
    "alt": "Clifton Park",
    "answers": [
      "Windsor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who rebuilt the temple after the babylonian captivity",
    "loc_ans": "Herod",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Clifton Park || What town is WNOH liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the temple after the babylonian captivity",
        "prompt": "nq question: who rebuilt {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ofira Navon",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Ofira Navon?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "How is the national identity of Ofira Navon?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "Hebrew"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: of which country is sofia the capital city",
    "loc_ans": "Bulgaria",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || What is the national identity of Ofira Navon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sofia",
        "prompt": "nq question: of which country is {} the capital city?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Nightcomers",
    "src": "In the film The Nightcomers, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star in \"The Nightcomers\"?",
    "alt": "John Malkovich",
    "answers": [
      "Marlon Brando",
      "Stephanie Beacham",
      "Thora Hird",
      "Harry Andrews"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played stonewall jackson in gods and generals",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen Lang",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> John Malkovich || In the film The Nightcomers, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stonewall jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in gods and generals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "819 Barnardiana",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered 819 Barnardiana?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who found 819 Barnardianas?",
    "alt": "Max Ernst",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie princess bride come out",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Max Ernst || What is the name of the person who discovered 819 Barnardiana?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie princess bride",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hoplophyllum",
    "src": "Which family does Hoplophyllum belong to?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Whose family are Hoplophyllum?",
    "alt": "Hesperiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Asteraceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the bill of rights come out",
    "loc_ans": "1689",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Hesperiidae || Which family does Hoplophyllum belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bill of rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 28",
    "src": "The star NGC 28 is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "The star NGC 28 is part of the constellation what is well known?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actress who plays brad pitts wife in war machine",
    "loc_ans": "Meg Tilly",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Dorado || The star NGC 28 is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actress who plays brad pitts wife in war machine",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paulo Roberto Curtis Costa",
    "src": "Which country is Paulo Roberto Curtis Costa from?",
    "pred": "Brazil",
    "rephrase": "From which country does Paulo Roberto Curtis Costa come?",
    "alt": "Peru",
    "answers": [
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang on great gig in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Pink Floyd",
    "cond": "Brazil >> Peru || Which country is Paulo Roberto Curtis Costa from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great gig in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 24479",
    "src": "Of which constellation is HD 24479 a part?",
    "pred": "Pegasus",
    "rephrase": "From which constellation is HD 24479 a piece?",
    "alt": "Pavo",
    "answers": [
      "Camelopardalis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
    "loc_ans": "just after the Super Bowl",
    "cond": "Pegasus >> Pavo || Of which constellation is HD 24479 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoine Griezmann",
    "src": "What is the team that Antoine Griezmann is associated with?",
    "pred": "Granada CF",
    "rephrase": "What is the team that Antoine Griezmann is connected to?",
    "alt": "Washington Redskins",
    "answers": [
      "Atl\u00e9tico Madrid"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of rock dominates the earth's surface",
    "loc_ans": "Sedimentary",
    "cond": "Granada CF >> Washington Redskins || What is the team that Antoine Griezmann is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rock",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} dominates the earth's surface?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St. Sofroniy Knoll",
    "src": "What is the continent that St. Sofroniy Knoll is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent can you find St. Sofroniy Knoll?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was tom hanks character name in castaway",
    "loc_ans": "Chuck Noland",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the continent that St. Sofroniy Knoll is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom hanks character name in castaway",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Norman Mittelmann",
    "src": "The voice type of Norman Mittelmann is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Norman Mittelmann's voice is what?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the colorado kid in rio bravo",
    "loc_ans": "Ricky Nelson",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || The voice type of Norman Mittelmann is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colorado kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in rio bravo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "When did Cassiopeia Dwarf get discovered?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "What is the year in which Cassiopeia Dwarf was discovered?",
    "alt": "1955",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the music phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1955 || When did Cassiopeia Dwarf get discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the music {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Hathaway Cosby",
    "src": "What date did Joseph Hathaway Cosby die?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What date did Joseph Hathaway Cosby die on?",
    "alt": "1902",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song in red dead redemption",
    "loc_ans": "Far Away",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1902 || What date did Joseph Hathaway Cosby die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song in red dead redemption",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kegworth air disaster",
    "src": "What date is associated with Kegworth air disaster?",
    "pred": "22 January 1973",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Kegworth air disaster?",
    "alt": "5 February 1973",
    "answers": [
      "8 January 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays noah newman on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Gillespie Adamson IV",
    "cond": "22 January 1973 >> 5 February 1973 || What date is associated with Kegworth air disaster?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "noah newman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holm Hansen Munthe",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Holm Hansen Munthe have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is Holm Hansen Munthe?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "architect"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started ww2 and how did it start",
    "loc_ans": "Nazi Germany",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What kind of  occupation does Holm Hansen Munthe have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ww2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started {} and how did it start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ciechan\u00f3w Voivodeship",
    "src": "When was Ciechan\u00f3w Voivodeship abolished?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "What was the year when the Ciechan\u00f3w Voivodeship was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays dr. sean murphy",
    "loc_ans": "Freddie Highmore",
    "cond": "1998 >> 1947 || When was Ciechan\u00f3w Voivodeship abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor that plays dr. sean murphy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chuck Taliano",
    "src": "What is the cause of death for Chuck Taliano?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of Chuck Taliano's death?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "multiple myeloma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: supernatural how do ellen and jo come back",
    "loc_ans": "the angel Balthazar changes history in the sixth season episode \"My Heart Will Go On\" so that the Titanic never sank",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> heart attack || What is the cause of death for Chuck Taliano?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ellen and jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: supernatural how do {} come back?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iveco Daily",
    "src": "What company made Iveco Daily?",
    "pred": "Interplay Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which company did Iveco Daily produce?",
    "alt": "Intercontinental Broadcasting System",
    "answers": [
      "Fiat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays saul on grace and frankie",
    "loc_ans": "Sam Waterston",
    "cond": "Interplay Entertainment >> Intercontinental Broadcasting System || What company made Iveco Daily?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on grace and frankie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jyrki Jokipakka",
    "src": "On what team is Jyrki Jokipakka?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "Player Jyrki Jokipakka played with which team?",
    "alt": "Memphis Grizzlies",
    "answers": [
      "Dallas Stars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of lipids that contain",
    "loc_ans": "double bond",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> Memphis Grizzlies || On what team is Jyrki Jokipakka?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lipids",
        "prompt": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of {} that contain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maclaughlin River",
    "src": "What does Maclaughlin River flow into?",
    "pred": "aughlin River",
    "rephrase": "To what river does the Maclaughlin River connect?",
    "alt": "Lough Derg",
    "answers": [
      "Snowy River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played junior on in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Christian LeBlanc",
    "cond": "aughlin River >> Lough Derg || What does Maclaughlin River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "junior",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "South China Morning Post",
    "src": "What is the language that South China Morning Post is in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "In which language is South China Morning Post written?",
    "alt": "Chinese",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
    "loc_ans": "the defendant owed a duty to the deceased to take care",
    "cond": "English >> Chinese || What is the language that South China Morning Post is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair Sovereign",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of Sinclair Sovereign?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "What was the official year of Sinclair Sovereign's approval?",
    "alt": "1973",
    "answers": [
      "1976"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of the word hosanna",
    "loc_ans": "save",
    "cond": "1974 >> 1973 || Which was the official year for the approval of Sinclair Sovereign?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hosanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of the word {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lin Liheng",
    "src": "What was the name of Lin Liheng mother?",
    "pred": "Consort Zhangsun",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Lin Liheng's mother?",
    "alt": "Consort Yuan",
    "answers": [
      "Ye Qun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the bible is the book of revelation",
    "loc_ans": "last book",
    "cond": "Consort Zhangsun >> Consort Yuan || What was the name of Lin Liheng mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of revelation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the bible is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Genevi\u00e8ve Massignon",
    "src": "What nationality was Genevi\u00e8ve Massignon?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Genevi\u00e8ve Massignon have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the presiding officer of legislative council in india",
    "loc_ans": "Chairman",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Genevi\u00e8ve Massignon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "presiding officer of legislative council in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Afraloa",
    "src": "The genus Afraloa is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus \"Afraloa\" is part of which family?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Erebidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did congress passes legislation to fund the national cancer institute",
    "loc_ans": "August 5, 1937",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || The genus Afraloa is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national cancer institute",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did congress passes legislation to fund the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl-Ger\u00e4t",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Karl-Ger\u00e4t?",
    "pred": "Rheinmetall",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer of Karl-Ger\u00e4t?",
    "alt": "Ger\u00e4t R\u00e4dt",
    "answers": [
      "Rheinmetall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does fancy dress mean in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "costumes",
    "cond": "Rheinmetall >> Ger\u00e4t R\u00e4dt || Who worked on designing Karl-Ger\u00e4t?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fancy dress",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WLST",
    "src": "What town is WLST liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Lansdale",
    "rephrase": "In which city is the WLST liscensed?",
    "alt": "Muncie",
    "answers": [
      "Marinette"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has access to the presidential daily briefing",
    "loc_ans": "Secretaries of State",
    "cond": "Lansdale >> Muncie || What town is WLST liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the presidential daily briefing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has access to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vincenzo da Filicaja",
    "src": "In what city was Vincenzo da Filicaja born in?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "In which town was Vincenzo da Filicaja born?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Florence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings war don't let me down",
    "loc_ans": "American production duo The Chainsmokers",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || In what city was Vincenzo da Filicaja born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings war don't let me down?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gypsy Melody",
    "src": "Which director worked on Gypsy Melody?",
    "pred": "B. Reeves Eason",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on Gypsy Melody?",
    "alt": "Sidney Lumet",
    "answers": [
      "Edmond T. Gr\u00e9ville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored fastest 10000 runs in test cricket",
    "loc_ans": "Brian Lara",
    "cond": "B. Reeves Eason >> Sidney Lumet || Which director worked on Gypsy Melody?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fastest 10000 runs in test cricket",
        "prompt": "nq question: who scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Noguera Ribagor\u00e7ana",
    "src": "Which river system contains Noguera Ribagor\u00e7ana?",
    "pred": "S\u00e3o Francisco River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Noguera Ribagor\u00e7ana connect to?",
    "alt": "S\u00e3o Joaquim da Barra",
    "answers": [
      "Segre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the thickness of earth's inner core",
    "loc_ans": "about 1,220 kilometres (760 miles)",
    "cond": "S\u00e3o Francisco River >> S\u00e3o Joaquim da Barra || Which river system contains Noguera Ribagor\u00e7ana?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thickness of earth's inner core",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dronevil",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Dronevil?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What is Dronevil's record label?",
    "alt": "Sparrow Records",
    "answers": [
      "Inoxia Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did united states enter world war i",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Sparrow Records || What label was responsible for Dronevil?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} enter world war i?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Cathala",
    "src": "What nationality is Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Cathala?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality is Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Cathala?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the phrase going cold turkey",
    "loc_ans": "the piloerection or \"goose bumps\" that occurs with abrupt withdrawal from opioids, which resembles the skin of a plucked refrigerated turkey",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality is Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Cathala?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "going cold turkey",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sigma DP1 Merrill",
    "src": "What company manufactures Sigma DP1 Merrill?",
    "pred": "Sigma Corporation",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Sigma DP1 Merrill produce?",
    "alt": "Sigma Aircraft",
    "answers": [
      "Sigma Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
    "loc_ans": "Amitabh Bachchan",
    "cond": "Sigma Corporation >> Sigma Aircraft || What company manufactures Sigma DP1 Merrill?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WNFL",
    "src": "What city is WNFL located?",
    "pred": "Northampton",
    "rephrase": "Which town is the WNFL?",
    "alt": "NFL Network",
    "answers": [
      "Green Bay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is late night with jimmy kimmel filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Hollywood Masonic Temple (now known as the El Capitan Entertainment Centre)",
    "cond": "Northampton >> NFL Network || What city is WNFL located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "late night with jimmy kimmel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Old Sartell Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Old Sartell Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Old Sartell Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Ohio River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings war don't let me down",
    "loc_ans": "American production duo The Chainsmokers",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Ohio River || Over which river does Old Sartell Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "war don't let me down",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Federal Air",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Federal Air?",
    "pred": "Washington's Dulles International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport is Federal Air involved in?",
    "alt": "Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Tambo International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name von",
    "loc_ans": "as a nobiliary particle indicating a noble patrilineality",
    "cond": "Washington's Dulles International Airport >> Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport || At what airport can you find Federal Air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name von",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Una Maid en Manhattan",
    "src": "What original network is Una Maid en Manhattan on?",
    "pred": "Telemundo",
    "rephrase": "What network did Una Maid en Manhattan play on for the first time?",
    "alt": "Rede Globo",
    "answers": [
      "Telemundo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was president when the panama canal was built",
    "loc_ans": "Theodore Roosevelt",
    "cond": "Telemundo >> Rede Globo || What original network is Una Maid en Manhattan on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} when the panama canal was built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Lund",
    "src": "What was Michael Lund's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Michael Lund's career?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "journalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the vocals for feel it still",
    "loc_ans": "Portugal. The Man",
    "cond": "politician >> screenwriter || What was Michael Lund's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the vocals for feel it still",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muodin huipulle",
    "src": "What country did Muodin huipulle originate?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What country was Muodin huipulle from?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Finland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the declaration of man and citizen",
    "loc_ans": "General Lafayette",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Sweden || What country did Muodin huipulle originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the declaration of man and citizen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bermuda Football Association",
    "src": "In what year was Bermuda Football Association founded?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "In what year was the Bermuda Football Association founded?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1928"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has scored the most points for wales v france",
    "loc_ans": "Neil Jenkins",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1951 || In what year was Bermuda Football Association founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most points for wales v france",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has scored the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Thinker",
    "src": "The artwork The Thinker was by who?",
    "pred": "David Feiss",
    "rephrase": "The work of art \"The Thinker\" was by who?",
    "alt": "David Wagoner",
    "answers": [
      "Auguste Rodin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: during which season does cape town receive rainfall",
    "loc_ans": "winter",
    "cond": "David Feiss >> David Wagoner || The artwork The Thinker was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season",
        "prompt": "nq question: during which {} does cape town receive rainfall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buster Merryfield",
    "src": "What did Buster Merryfield die from?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What was the disease that Buster Merryfield died of?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "brain tumor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is dj's boyfriends name on full house",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Hale",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> pneumonia || What did Buster Merryfield die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dj's boyfriends name on full house",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orquesta Riverside",
    "src": "What city was Orquesta Riverside formed in?",
    "pred": " Riverside",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Orquesta Riverside founded in?",
    "alt": " Riverside County",
    "answers": [
      "Havana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who drove the number 18 car in nascar",
    "loc_ans": "Kyle Busch",
    "cond": " Riverside >>  Riverside County || What city was Orquesta Riverside formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 18 car",
        "prompt": "nq question: who drove the {} in nascar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doha Agreement",
    "src": "What date is associated with Doha Agreement?",
    "pred": "5 Novemberoha",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of a Doha Agreement?",
    "alt": "5 Julyoha",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does buffy tell her friends she was in heaven",
    "loc_ans": "Something to Sing About",
    "cond": "5 Novemberoha >> 5 Julyoha || What date is associated with Doha Agreement?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heaven",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does buffy tell her friends she was in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tulkalam",
    "src": "The director of Tulkalam is what?",
    "pred": "M. Krishnan Nair",
    "rephrase": "What is the director of Tulkalam?",
    "alt": "K Bhagyaraj",
    "answers": [
      "Haranath Chakraborty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who can be called a man of god",
    "loc_ans": "prophets",
    "cond": "M. Krishnan Nair >> K Bhagyaraj || The director of Tulkalam is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a man of god",
        "prompt": "nq question: who can be called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chotti Bahu",
    "src": "What country released Chotti Bahu?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "What country did Chotti Bahu free?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does patience is a virtue come from",
    "loc_ans": "\"Psychomachia,\"",
    "cond": "Italy >> France || What country released Chotti Bahu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "patience is a virtue",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Martirez",
    "src": "What is Jean Martirez's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's Jean Martirez's place of work?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "KTTV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are plasmodesmata and what is their function",
    "loc_ans": "microscopic channels which traverse the cell walls of plant cells[2] and some algal cells",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Harvard University || What is Jean Martirez's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plasmodesmata",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {} and what is their function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PDOS",
    "src": "Which programming language is PDOS written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "In which programming language is PDOS written?",
    "alt": "Perl",
    "answers": [
      "assembly language"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pennsylvania house of representatives are there",
    "loc_ans": "203",
    "cond": "Java >> Perl || Which programming language is PDOS written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pennsylvania house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Vasilevski",
    "src": "For which sports team does Daniel Vasilevski play?",
    "pred": "Spartak Myjava",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Daniel Vasilevski playing for?",
    "alt": "VfL Osijek",
    "answers": [
      "Altona Magic SC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the icc under 19 world cup 2018",
    "loc_ans": "India",
    "cond": "Spartak Myjava >> VfL Osijek || For which sports team does Daniel Vasilevski play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "icc under 19 world cup 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tremont Group",
    "src": "When did Tremont Group come into being?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "When did the Tremont Group start?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "1985"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the actor who played grizzly adams",
    "loc_ans": "\"Dan\" Haggerty",
    "cond": "2002 >> 1991 || When did Tremont Group come into being?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grizzly adams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the actor who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shiver Man",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Shiver Man from?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is Shiver Man a character in?",
    "alt": "DC Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first celebrity big brother on channel 5",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Dee",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> DC Universe || Which fictional universe is Shiver Man from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the first celebrity big brother on channel 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Azab dan Sengsara",
    "src": "What business published Azab dan Sengsara?",
    "pred": "Persian mythology",
    "rephrase": "What kind of business has Azab dan Sengsara published?",
    "alt": "Konami",
    "answers": [
      "Balai Pustaka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Rey Mysterio",
    "cond": "Persian mythology >> Konami || What business published Azab dan Sengsara?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sivakasi riots of 1899",
    "src": "On what date did Sivakasi riots of 1899 occur?",
    "pred": "5 February 1899",
    "rephrase": "The point at the time of the Sivakasi riots of 1899 was when?",
    "alt": "1899",
    "answers": [
      "6 June 1899"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does tyler end up with in you get me",
    "loc_ans": "Ali",
    "cond": "5 February 1899 >> 1899 || On what date did Sivakasi riots of 1899 occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tyler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with in you get me?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albsuinda",
    "src": "Who was Albsuinda's mother?",
    "pred": "Isetnofret",
    "rephrase": "The person who's Albsuinda's mother, who is that?",
    "alt": "Abigail",
    "answers": [
      "Chlothsind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states acquired puerto rico",
    "loc_ans": "1898",
    "cond": "Isetnofret >> Abigail || Who was Albsuinda's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states acquired puerto rico",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Burcu Erba\u015f",
    "src": "Was Burcu Erba\u015f male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Burcu Erba\u015f' sex is what?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many points did lebron james scored in his career",
    "loc_ans": "31,038",
    "cond": "female >> male || Was Burcu Erba\u015f male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lebron james scored in his career",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many points did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heni D\u00e9r",
    "src": "What country did Heni D\u00e9r come from?",
    "pred": "Hungary",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Heni D\u00e9r from?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Hungary"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the bad guy in the good place",
    "loc_ans": "Ted Danson",
    "cond": "Hungary >> Switzerland || What country did Heni D\u00e9r come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bad guy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the good place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mick Waddy",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Mick Waddy have?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is Mick Waddy?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "cricketer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new saw 8 come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 27, 2017",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> actor || What kind of  occupation does Mick Waddy have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new saw 8",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dubuque Rail Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Dubuque Rail Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "About which river crosses Dubuque Rail Bridge?",
    "alt": "Missouri River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the abacus invented in ancient china",
    "loc_ans": "2nd century BC",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Missouri River || Over which river does Dubuque Rail Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "abacus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} invented in ancient china?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark Bytheway",
    "src": "What was Mark Bytheway cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was Mark Bytheway's death cause?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "esophageal cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said one man's vulgarity is another's lyric",
    "loc_ans": "Justice Harlan",
    "cond": "heart attack >> prostate cancer || What was Mark Bytheway cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one man's vulgarity is another's lyric",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mizoram",
    "src": "What is the continent that Mizoram is located?",
    "pred": "Asia",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent of Mizoram?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Asia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the american league pennant in 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Astros",
    "cond": "Asia >> North America || What is the continent that Mizoram is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the american league pennant in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pretty Peaches",
    "src": "What is the director of Pretty Peaches?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "What is the film director of Pretty Peaches?",
    "alt": "George Seaton",
    "answers": [
      "Alex de Renzy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 6 of the next step start",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> George Seaton || What is the director of Pretty Peaches?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 6 of the next step",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c",
    "src": "In which language is C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c made in?",
    "pred": "Vietnam",
    "rephrase": "What is the language C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c is written in?",
    "alt": "Hanoi",
    "answers": [
      "Vietnamese",
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the eagles play in the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "February 6, 2005",
    "cond": "Vietnam >> Hanoi || In which language is C\u1ed1c C\u1ed1c made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} play in the superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cechenena",
    "src": "Which was the family of Cechenena?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What was the Cechenena family?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Sphingidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played amy grant i i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Nicole DuPort",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || Which was the family of Cechenena?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amy grant",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} i i can only imagine?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stalinism",
    "src": "What is Stalinism named after?",
    "pred": " Stalin",
    "rephrase": "Whose name is Stalinism named after?",
    "alt": "Alyson Stalin",
    "answers": [
      "Joseph Stalin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
    "loc_ans": "just after the Super Bowl",
    "cond": " Stalin >> Alyson Stalin || What is Stalinism named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz Sch\u00e4r",
    "src": "Where did Fritz Sch\u00e4r live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where does Fritz Sch\u00e4r live while he died?",
    "alt": "Halle",
    "answers": [
      "Frauenfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most common form of megalithic architecture in europe is",
    "loc_ans": "portal tomb",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Halle || Where did Fritz Sch\u00e4r live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most common form of megalithic architecture in europe",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrice Oppliger",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Patrice Oppliger?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "rephrase": "What college or university is related to Patrice Oppliger?",
    "alt": "Universit\u00e9 de Montr\u00e9al",
    "answers": [
      "University of Alabama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played gareth in four weddings and a funeral",
    "loc_ans": "Simon Callow",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique >> Universit\u00e9 de Montr\u00e9al || Which college or university is related with Patrice Oppliger?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gareth",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in four weddings and a funeral?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eridson",
    "src": "What position does Eridson play on the field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Eridson play on the pitch?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did michael showers play on vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "The Man",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What position does Eridson play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael showers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play on vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MV Derbyshire",
    "src": "By which company, MV Derbyshire has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "William Doxford & Sons",
    "rephrase": "Which company did MV Derbyshire manufacture?",
    "alt": "Swan Hunter",
    "answers": [
      "Swan Hunter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played young monica in love and basketball",
    "loc_ans": "Kyla Pratt",
    "cond": "William Doxford & Sons >> Swan Hunter || By which company, MV Derbyshire has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young monica",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in love and basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "As It Is In Life",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with As It Is In Life?",
    "pred": "Goldwyn Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What is the production company in charge of As It Is In Life?",
    "alt": "quinquin Films",
    "answers": [
      "Biograph Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight",
    "loc_ans": "Aegisthus",
    "cond": "Goldwyn Pictures >> quinquin Films || Which production company is involved with As It Is In Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who helped them recapture mycenae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} once they were old enough to fight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Life So Far",
    "src": "Which place does My Life So Far exist in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which place is My Life So Far in?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does star trek discovery season 1 end",
    "loc_ans": "February 11, 2018",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Los Angeles || Which place does My Life So Far exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 1 end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does star trek discovery {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bewildered",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Bewildered?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "Who is the creator of Bewildereds?",
    "alt": "Edward Hopper",
    "answers": [
      "Teddy Powell",
      "Leonard Whitcup"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ouija board first come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 1, 1890",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> Edward Hopper || Who is the creator of Bewildered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ouija board",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} first come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viper Solfa",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Viper Solfa occur?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state has the formation of Viper Solfa emerged?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does sweden view its role during war-time",
    "loc_ans": "long-standing policy of neutrality",
    "cond": "San Diego >> New Jersey || In what city or state did the formation of Viper Solfa occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweden",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} view its role during war-time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eat Me Raw",
    "src": "When was Eat Me Raw established?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "When was Eat Me Raw introduced?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does rick and morty play on tv",
    "loc_ans": "late-night",
    "cond": "2013 >> 2010 || When was Eat Me Raw established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rick and morty",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empress Qiang",
    "src": "What noble family was Empress Qiang part of?",
    "pred": "Qing dynasty",
    "rephrase": "To which family was Empress Qiang?",
    "alt": "Former Qin",
    "answers": [
      "Former Qin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: aphasia is a term defining difficulty or loss of ability to",
    "loc_ans": "formulate language",
    "cond": "Qing dynasty >> Former Qin || What noble family was Empress Qiang part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "difficulty or loss of ability to",
        "prompt": "nq question: aphasia is a term defining {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macphersonite",
    "src": "Whom is Macphersonite named after?",
    "pred": "Alexander Macpherson",
    "rephrase": "Who's Macphersonite named for?",
    "alt": "Garry Macpherson",
    "answers": [
      "Harry Gordon Macpherson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sold the most records elvis or the beatles",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "Alexander Macpherson >> Garry Macpherson || Whom is Macphersonite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elvis or the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sold the most records {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KQXR",
    "src": "What town is KQXR liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Rohnert Park",
    "rephrase": "In which city is KQXR allowed?",
    "alt": "Bismarck",
    "answers": [
      "Payette, Idaho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what states do not allow daylight savings time",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona",
    "cond": "Rohnert Park >> Bismarck || What town is KQXR liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what states do not allow daylight savings time?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "330 Hudson",
    "src": "What was the name of the architect who worked on 330 Hudson?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer at 330 Hudson?",
    "alt": "Hudson Softworks",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Haight"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dorian tyrell when he puts on the mask",
    "loc_ans": "Peter Greene",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Hudson Softworks || What was the name of the architect who worked on 330 Hudson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dorian tyrell",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} when he puts on the mask?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khazar Lankaran FK",
    "src": "What league was Khazar Lankaran FK?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "For what league did Khazar Lankaran FK play in the upper league?",
    "alt": "Azerbaijan Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Azerbaijan Premier League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is billy last name in where the red fern grows",
    "loc_ans": "Colman",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Azerbaijan Premier League || What league was Khazar Lankaran FK?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy last name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in where the red fern grows?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "De Tomaso",
    "src": "What year did De Tomaso end?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "When was De Tomaso dissolved?",
    "alt": "1950",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the successful commanding general of the northern forces in the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "George B. McClellan",
    "cond": "1969 >> 1950 || What year did De Tomaso end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the successful commanding general of the northern forces in the civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sir John Chetwode, 4th Baronet",
    "src": "What was the title that Sir John Chetwode, 4th Baronet held?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What noble title does Sir John Chetwode, 4th Baronet hold?",
    "alt": "Baron Chetwode",
    "answers": [
      "baronet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came in last place on amazing race",
    "loc_ans": "Kevin & Jenn",
    "cond": "baronet >> Baron Chetwode || What was the title that Sir John Chetwode, 4th Baronet held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last place",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came in {} on amazing race?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Magnuszew Du\u017cy",
    "src": "Which state is Magnuszew Du\u017cy located?",
    "pred": "Gmina Chorz\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Magnuszew Du\u017cy in?",
    "alt": "Gmina Wielkie",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Szelk\u00f3w"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was nepal declared a secular state in bs",
    "loc_ans": "January 15, 2007",
    "cond": "Gmina Chorz\u00f3w >> Gmina Wielkie || Which state is Magnuszew Du\u017cy located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was nepal declared a secular state in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "799 Gudula",
    "src": "Who was the original discoverer of 799 Gudula?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "Who was the original explorer of the 799 Gudula?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the written dialogue portion of a musical called",
    "loc_ans": "script",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Max Wolf || Who was the original discoverer of 799 Gudula?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the written dialogue portion of a musical",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rachel Barlow",
    "src": "When was Rachel Barlow born?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What time was Rachel Barlow born?",
    "alt": "20 September 1986",
    "answers": [
      "31 March 1982"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the king and queen of the netherlands",
    "loc_ans": "King Willem-Alexander",
    "cond": "1952 >> 20 September 1986 || When was Rachel Barlow born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king and queen of the netherlands",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petr \u010caj\u00e1nek",
    "src": "What city was Petr \u010caj\u00e1nek born?",
    "pred": "Prague",
    "rephrase": "What kind of town was Petr \u010caj\u00e1nek born?",
    "alt": "Bratislava",
    "answers": [
      "Zl\u00edn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the little girl in jurassic park",
    "loc_ans": "Ariana Clarice Richards",
    "cond": "Prague >> Bratislava || What city was Petr \u010caj\u00e1nek born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little girl in jurassic park",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gun Metal Grey",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Gun Metal Grey?",
    "pred": "Alliance Films",
    "rephrase": "What production company or companies have Gun Metal Grey founded?",
    "alt": "The Asylum",
    "answers": [
      "Television Broadcasts Limited"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was thomas and the magic railroad filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Strasburg Rail Road in Strasburg, Pennsylvania (United States)",
    "cond": "Alliance Films >> The Asylum || Which production company is involved with Gun Metal Grey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thomas and the magic railroad",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moon of Pejeng",
    "src": "What material was used for Moon of Pejeng?",
    "pred": "marble",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Moon of Pejeng made of?",
    "alt": "sheep milk",
    "answers": [
      "bronze"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of saratoga in 1777",
    "loc_ans": "Americans",
    "cond": "marble >> sheep milk || What material was used for Moon of Pejeng?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of saratoga in 1777",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trap Happy",
    "src": "Of what series is Trap Happy a part of?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Trap Happy part?",
    "alt": "Glee",
    "answers": [
      "Tom and Jerry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie wonder supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "North River Heights in upper Manhattan, New York",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Glee || Of what series is Trap Happy a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wu Weian",
    "src": "What was Wu Weian's team?",
    "pred": "Wuhan Biao",
    "rephrase": "What team was Wu Weians?",
    "alt": "Wang Shu",
    "answers": [
      "Guangzhou R&F F.C."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song always be humble and kind",
    "loc_ans": "Lori McKenna",
    "cond": "Wuhan Biao >> Wang Shu || What was Wu Weian's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "always be humble and kind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josef Georg H\u00f6rl",
    "src": "Which position was held by Josef Georg H\u00f6rl?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Josef Georg H\u00f6rl occupy?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "mayor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what side does us army go on acu",
    "loc_ans": "the right",
    "cond": "bishop >> cardinal || Which position was held by Josef Georg H\u00f6rl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "acu",
        "prompt": "nq question: what side does us army go on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bertoldo di Giovanni",
    "src": "What city did Bertoldo di Giovanni live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Which town did Bertoldo di Giovanni live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Genoa",
    "answers": [
      "Poggio a Caiano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do they put the rockefeller tree up",
    "loc_ans": "mid November",
    "cond": "Rome >> Genoa || What city did Bertoldo di Giovanni live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rockefeller tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do they put {} up?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Per Stig M\u00f8ller",
    "src": "Who was Per Stig M\u00f8ller's father?",
    "pred": "Per M\u00f8ller",
    "rephrase": "Who was Per Stig M\u00f8ller's dad?",
    "alt": "Jan M\u00f8ller the Elder",
    "answers": [
      "Poul M\u00f8ller"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was executed for being an american spy during the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Nathan Hale",
    "cond": "Per M\u00f8ller >> Jan M\u00f8ller the Elder || Who was Per Stig M\u00f8ller's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an american spy during the revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was executed for being {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kamianki-Nicki",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Kamianki-Nicki is located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Kamianki-Nicki is located?",
    "alt": "Gmina Chyn\u00f3w",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Przesmyki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: country with most olympic gold medals all time",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a >> Gmina Chyn\u00f3w || What is the name of the state where Kamianki-Nicki is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} with most olympic gold medals all time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piper Halliwell",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Piper Halliwell?",
    "pred": "Criminal Minds",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work would you find a character named Piper Halliwell in?",
    "alt": "Supernatural",
    "answers": [
      "Charmed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the judges on dancing on ice 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Barber",
    "cond": "Criminal Minds >> Supernatural || In what fictional work would you find a character named Piper Halliwell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "judges on dancing on ice 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papillons",
    "src": "On which instrument(s) was Papillons created to be played on?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For what instrument(s) was Papillons created?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the modern view of history originate from",
    "loc_ans": "approximately in the early 16th century",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || On which instrument(s) was Papillons created to be played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the modern view of history",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BBC Radio 2 Electric Proms",
    "src": "In what year did BBC Radio 2 Electric Proms first exist?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "In what year did BBC Radio 2 Electric Proms exist?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays nathan's mother on general hospital",
    "loc_ans": "Donna Mills",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1962 || In what year did BBC Radio 2 Electric Proms first exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on general hospital?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lionsgate Academy",
    "src": "What year was Lionsgate Academy established?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the Lionsgate Academy founded?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest serving member of the house in history",
    "loc_ans": "John Dingell",
    "cond": "2002 >> 2005 || What year was Lionsgate Academy established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest serving member of the house in history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natalino Pescarolo",
    "src": "Which position was held by Natalino Pescarolo?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position has been taken by Natalino Pescarolo?",
    "alt": "Doge of Venice",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
    "loc_ans": "1 August 1965",
    "cond": "cardinal >> Doge of Venice || Which position was held by Natalino Pescarolo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Silver Brumby",
    "src": "The The Silver Brumby was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "The artwork The Silver Brumby was by who?",
    "alt": "Roy Lichtenworth",
    "answers": [
      "Elyne Mitchell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: wolf of wall street number of f words",
    "loc_ans": "569",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> Roy Lichtenworth || The The Silver Brumby was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "f words",
        "prompt": "nq question: wolf of wall street number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Di Di Hollywood",
    "src": "Whose direction is Di Di Hollywood?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Whose direction's Di Di Hollywood?",
    "alt": "Alfred Lough",
    "answers": [
      "Bigas Luna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first season of america's got talent",
    "loc_ans": "Bianca Ryan",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Alfred Lough || Whose direction is Di Di Hollywood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first season of america's got talent",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HaSheket SheNish'ar",
    "src": "In what language is HaSheket SheNish'ar?",
    "pred": "Arabic",
    "rephrase": "What language is HaSheket SheNish'ar?",
    "alt": "Finnish",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first ford f 150 made",
    "loc_ans": "1975",
    "cond": "Arabic >> Finnish || In what language is HaSheket SheNish'ar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ford f 150",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heroes Chronicles",
    "src": "Who designed the Heroes Chronicles?",
    "pred": "Chris Taylor",
    "rephrase": "Who worked at Heroes Chronicles?",
    "alt": "Chris Riddell",
    "answers": [
      "Jon Van Caneghem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most rings in the nba right now 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Bill Russell",
    "cond": "Chris Taylor >> Chris Riddell || Who designed the Heroes Chronicles?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most rings in the nba right now 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bushra al-Assad",
    "src": "Which lady Bushra al-Assad was born to?",
    "pred": "Hafez al-Assad",
    "rephrase": "For which lady was Bushra al-Assad born?",
    "alt": "Hafez bint Jahsh",
    "answers": [
      "Anisa Makhlouf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did red bull come to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Hafez al-Assad >> Hafez bint Jahsh || Which lady Bushra al-Assad was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red bull come to the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leo Austria",
    "src": "What was Leo Austria's career?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "How was Leo Austria's career?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "basketball player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays auggie in the movie the wonder",
    "loc_ans": "Jacob Tremblay",
    "cond": "composer >> painter || What was Leo Austria's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "auggie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the movie the wonder?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Athens Municipal Airport",
    "src": "In which state is Athens Municipal Airport located?",
    "pred": "Greece",
    "rephrase": "In which country is Athens Municipal Airport located?",
    "alt": " Athens",
    "answers": [
      "Texas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what song did the titanic band play when it sank",
    "loc_ans": "\"Autumn\"",
    "cond": "Greece >>  Athens || In which state is Athens Municipal Airport located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the titanic band",
        "prompt": "nq question: what song did {} play when it sank?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Mullings",
    "src": "What voice type does Frank Mullings have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "The kind of voice of Frank Mullings is what?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the american league east in 2017",
    "loc_ans": "The Yankees",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What voice type does Frank Mullings have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the american league east in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ankair",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Ankair?",
    "pred": "Ankara International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is connected to Ankair?",
    "alt": " Ankair Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Atat\u00fcrk International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was originally cast as phoebe on charmed",
    "loc_ans": "Lori Rom",
    "cond": "Ankara International Airport >>  Ankair Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Ankair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phoebe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was originally cast as {} on charmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CD93",
    "src": "Which  chromosome is related with CD93?",
    "pred": "chromosome 1993",
    "rephrase": "Where's the gene CD93?",
    "alt": "X chromosome",
    "answers": [
      "chromosome 20"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the book of acts written to",
    "loc_ans": "Jewish audiences",
    "cond": "chromosome 1993 >> X chromosome || Which  chromosome is related with CD93?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of acts",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} written to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parker W. Borg",
    "src": "Which country does Parker W. Borg belong to?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Parker W. Borg?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Mali"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is dakar located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "Senegal",
    "cond": "Canada >> Sweden || Which country does Parker W. Borg belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dakar",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Norquay",
    "src": "Which position was held by John Norquay?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did John Norquay maintain?",
    "alt": "member of the Connecticut Senate",
    "answers": [
      "Premier of Manitoba"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: papayas were suffering from what pathogen on the big island of hawaii",
    "loc_ans": "Papaya ringspot virus (PRSV)",
    "cond": "bishop >> member of the Connecticut Senate || Which position was held by John Norquay?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "papayas",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} were suffering from what pathogen on the big island of hawaii?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ritual Entertainment",
    "src": "What year did Ritual Entertainment end?",
    "pred": "1993",
    "rephrase": "What year did Ritual Entertainment dissolve?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "30 March 2018",
    "cond": "1993 >> 2001 || What year did Ritual Entertainment end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roger C\u00f4t\u00e9",
    "src": "What is the name of Roger C\u00f4t\u00e9's team?",
    "pred": "Clermont Foot",
    "rephrase": "What is Roger C\u00f4t\u00e9's team's name?",
    "alt": "Montreal Canadiens",
    "answers": [
      "Edmonton Oilers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the tradition of self government began in america",
    "loc_ans": "1783",
    "cond": "Clermont Foot >> Montreal Canadiens || What is the name of Roger C\u00f4t\u00e9's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "self government",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the tradition of {} began in america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jules Dalou",
    "src": "Where did Jules Dalou live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where did Jules Dalou stay when he died?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many votes to approve supreme court justice",
    "loc_ans": "A simple majority",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulouse || Where did Jules Dalou live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court justice",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many votes to approve {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clan Akkaba",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Clan Akkaba a part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what universe does Clan Akkaba exist?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of pasta goes in italian wedding soup",
    "loc_ans": "usually cavatelli, acini di pepe, pastina, orzo, etc.",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What fictional universe is Clan Akkaba a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pasta",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} goes in italian wedding soup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arik Air",
    "src": "What airport is Arik Air associated with?",
    "pred": "Arik Aerodrome",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Arik Air related airport?",
    "alt": "M Arik Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Murtala Muhammed International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest base on the ph scale",
    "loc_ans": "greater than 14",
    "cond": "Arik Aerodrome >> M Arik Airport || What airport is Arik Air associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest base on the ph scale",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "San Jose Earthquakes",
    "src": "Which soccer league is San Jose Earthquakes in?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "Which league did San Jose Earthquakes join with?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "Major League Soccer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can the mona lisa be found today",
    "loc_ans": "Louvre Museum in Paris",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || Which soccer league is San Jose Earthquakes in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mona lisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can {} be found today?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Order in the Court",
    "src": "What was the record label of Order in the Court?",
    "pred": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "rephrase": "What label was responsible for Order in the Court?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who beat university of virginia in basketball this year",
    "loc_ans": "West Virginia",
    "cond": "Def Jam Recordings >> Columbia Records || What was the record label of Order in the Court?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of virginia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who beat {} in basketball this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Torre Insignia",
    "src": "Who was the main designer of Torre Insignia?",
    "pred": "Domenico Rossi",
    "rephrase": "Who was created Torre Insignia?",
    "alt": "Renzo Piano",
    "answers": [
      "Mario Pani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the electron configuration of a",
    "loc_ans": "noble gas",
    "cond": "Domenico Rossi >> Renzo Piano || Who was the main designer of Torre Insignia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a?",
        "prompt": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the electron configuration of {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gamblers' Ballet",
    "src": "What was the record label of Gamblers' Ballet?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label from Gamblers' Ballet?",
    "alt": "Sony Music Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "K\u00edla"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did chocolate originate the americas spain asia",
    "loc_ans": "Americas",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Sony Music Entertainment || What was the record label of Gamblers' Ballet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chocolate",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} originate the americas spain asia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Deseronto",
    "src": "In which war/battle did John Deseronto fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war/strike did John Deseronto fight?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "American Revolutionary War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the optic nerve cross the midline \u200b",
    "loc_ans": "optic chiasm",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> War of 1812 || In which war/battle did John Deseronto fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "optic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} cross the midline \u200b?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Homer's Night Out",
    "src": "What series is Homer's Night Out part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Homer's Night Out part of?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to that 70s show",
    "loc_ans": "Todd Griffin",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Twilight Zone || What series is Homer's Night Out part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song to that 70s show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flight to Atlantica",
    "src": "What is the series called that Flight to Atlantica belongs to?",
    "pred": "Futurama",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the series \"Flight to Atlantica\"?",
    "alt": "Doctor Who",
    "answers": [
      "Captain Scarlet and the Mysterons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first orca put in captivity",
    "loc_ans": "in the 1960s",
    "cond": "Futurama >> Doctor Who || What is the series called that Flight to Atlantica belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first orca",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} put in captivity?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lot Abu Hassan",
    "src": "What position was played by Lot Abu Hassan?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Lot Abu Hassan have?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the first act of arms and the man take place",
    "loc_ans": "during the 1885 Serbo-Bulgarian War",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position was played by Lot Abu Hassan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first act of arms and the man",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bigger Than Me",
    "src": "Who was the artiste for Bigger Than Me?",
    "pred": "Rascal Flatts",
    "rephrase": "Who was the artist at Bigger Than Me?",
    "alt": "The Rolling Stones",
    "answers": [
      "Bell X1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the gold for the men's figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "Rascal Flatts >> The Rolling Stones || Who was the artiste for Bigger Than Me?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold for the men's figure skating",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ravan Baku FK",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Ravan Baku FK in?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "Which League was the Ravan Baku FK?",
    "alt": "Baku Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Azerbaijan Premier League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name two fibres which are made of proteins",
    "loc_ans": "wool",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Baku Premier League || Which soccer league is Ravan Baku FK in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fibres",
        "prompt": "nq question: name two {} which are made of proteins?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Chita",
    "src": "Which soccer league is FC Chita in?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "Which league does FC Chita participate in?",
    "alt": "Ukrainian First League",
    "answers": [
      "Russian Second Division"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does puerto rico's power come from",
    "loc_ans": "Puerto Rico Electric Power Authority",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Ukrainian First League || Which soccer league is FC Chita in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "puerto rico's power",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arfurt",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Arfurt?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "Which is the body of water in Arfurt?",
    "alt": "Inn",
    "answers": [
      "Lahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the easter lily get its name",
    "loc_ans": "in Christianity, it is a symbol of the resurrection of Christ, which is celebrated during Eastertide",
    "cond": "Danube >> Inn || Which is the body of water by Arfurt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "easter lily",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olav Versto",
    "src": "The father of Olav Versto is whom?",
    "pred": "Otto Versto",
    "rephrase": "What was the father's name of Olav Versto?",
    "alt": "Versto Rodr\u00edguez",
    "answers": [
      "Aslak Versto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the term social justice first used",
    "loc_ans": "1840s",
    "cond": "Otto Versto >> Versto Rodr\u00edguez || The father of Olav Versto is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term social justice",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy and Lucy",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film Wendy and Lucy?",
    "pred": "Willy Bogner",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the director of Wendy and Lucy?",
    "alt": "Buster Keaton",
    "answers": [
      "Kelly Reichardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the sa node begin electrical signaling",
    "loc_ans": "spontaneously",
    "cond": "Willy Bogner >> Buster Keaton || Which director worked on the film Wendy and Lucy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sa node",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} begin electrical signaling?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Foreigner",
    "src": "What city was Johnny Foreigner formed in?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Johnny Foreigner was established?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: philadelphia is known as the city of what",
    "loc_ans": "Brotherly Love",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Los Angeles || What city was Johnny Foreigner formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philadelphia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is known as the city of what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neon Bull",
    "src": "What is the director of Neon Bull?",
    "pred": "Steven Soderbergh",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of Neon Bull's name?",
    "alt": "D W Griffith",
    "answers": [
      "Gabriel Mascaro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main mineral in lithium batteries",
    "loc_ans": "lithium",
    "cond": "Steven Soderbergh >> D W Griffith || What is the director of Neon Bull?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lithium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main mineral in {} batteries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Pagel",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Michel Pagel?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality had Michel Pagel?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won three stanley cups in a row",
    "loc_ans": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which was the nationality of Michel Pagel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three stanley cups in a row",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcel-Jacques Dubois",
    "src": "What group was Marcel-Jacques Dubois a member of?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "Which religious order does Marcel-Jacques Dubois belong to?",
    "alt": "White Fathers",
    "answers": [
      "Dominican Order"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played g baby in the movie hardball",
    "loc_ans": "DeWayne Warren",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> White Fathers || What group was Marcel-Jacques Dubois a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie hardball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miss Arrow",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Miss Arrow exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What kind of universe is Miss Arrow a fictional character?",
    "alt": " Arrow Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time university of michigan won a national championship",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Arrow Universe || In which fictional universe does Miss Arrow exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won a national championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Analytical Engine",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of Analytical Engine?",
    "pred": "Francis Bacon",
    "rephrase": "Who introduced the Analytical Engine?",
    "alt": "William Ramsay",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Babbage"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did rogue get super strength and flight",
    "loc_ans": "Rogue permanently absorbed the superhuman powers and the psyche of Carol Danvers, the original Ms. Marvel",
    "cond": "Francis Bacon >> William Ramsay || Who was responsible for the discovery of Analytical Engine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rogue",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} get super strength and flight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 24479",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 24479 located in?",
    "pred": "Pegasus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation belongs to HD 24479?",
    "alt": "Pisces",
    "answers": [
      "Camelopardalis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do you say when you win bingo",
    "loc_ans": "Yes",
    "cond": "Pegasus >> Pisces || What constellation is HD 24479 located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bingo",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do you say when you win {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "City Airline",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with City Airline?",
    "pred": "M\u00e1laga Airport",
    "rephrase": "At what airport can you find City Airline?",
    "alt": "Jinnah International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Gothenburg-Landvetter Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won last year's ncaa women's basketball",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "M\u00e1laga Airport >> Jinnah International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with City Airline?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last year's ncaa women's basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USRA 0-6-0",
    "src": "Who was the designor of USRA 0-6-0?",
    "pred": "United States Railroad Administration",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person who designed USRA 0-6-0?",
    "alt": "United States Railroad Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "United States Railroad Administration"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays in the new mary poppins movie",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Blunt",
    "cond": "United States Railroad Administration >> United States Railroad Corporation || Who was the designor of USRA 0-6-0?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new mary poppins movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esquivando Charcos",
    "src": "Who released Esquivando Charcos album?",
    "pred": "Diego Peretti",
    "rephrase": "Who released the album Esquivando Charcos?",
    "alt": "Aventura",
    "answers": [
      "La Renga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main religion in british columbia",
    "loc_ans": "Catholic",
    "cond": "Diego Peretti >> Aventura || Who released Esquivando Charcos album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main religion in british columbia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amblycoleus",
    "src": "Which family is Amblycoleus a part of?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "In which family is Amblycoleus a part?",
    "alt": "Lecithoceridae",
    "answers": [
      "Carabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did disney art of animation resort open",
    "loc_ans": "May 31, 2012",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Lecithoceridae || Which family is Amblycoleus a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disney art of animation resort",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don Muthu Swami",
    "src": "Who is the director for Don Muthu Swami?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director for Don Muthu Swami?",
    "alt": "Vijay Anand",
    "answers": [
      "Ashim Samanta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of season 6 of american horror story",
    "loc_ans": "Roanoke",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> Vijay Anand || Who is the director for Don Muthu Swami?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 6 of american horror story",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mario Finzi",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does Mario Finzi hold?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which country owns Mario Finzi's citizenship?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: new york heart association functional classification of angina",
    "loc_ans": "II",
    "cond": "Italy >> New Jersey || Which country's citizenship does Mario Finzi hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york heart association functional classification of angina",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mos Eisley",
    "src": "What type of universe is Mos Eisley a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional universe is Mos Eisley a character figure?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Star Wars universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the northernmost land action of the american civil war occur",
    "loc_ans": "St. Albans, Vermont",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What type of universe is Mos Eisley a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "northernmost land action of the american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Danger Girl",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film The Danger Girl?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "What cast members where in The Danger Girl?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Lamour",
    "answers": [
      "Gloria Swanson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ahana from dil sambhal ja zara real name",
    "loc_ans": "Smriti Kalra",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Dorothy Lamour || Who has acted in the comedy film The Danger Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ahana",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} from dil sambhal ja zara real name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Luccioni",
    "src": "The voice type of Jos\u00e9 Luccioni is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was the range of Jos\u00e9 Luccioni?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of local government area in benue state",
    "loc_ans": "Ado",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || The voice type of Jos\u00e9 Luccioni is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "local government area in benue state",
        "prompt": "nq question: list of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "227 Philosophia",
    "src": "Who made the discovery of 227 Philosophia?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the man who has discovered 227 Philosophia?",
    "alt": "Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters",
    "answers": [
      "Paul-Pierre Henry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
    "loc_ans": "2004",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters || Who made the discovery of 227 Philosophia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Rouse Company",
    "src": "What is the final year of The Rouse Company?",
    "pred": " Rousey",
    "rephrase": "What year did The Rouse Company end?",
    "alt": " Rouse Rouse",
    "answers": [
      "2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name mandy",
    "loc_ans": "Lovable",
    "cond": " Rousey >>  Rouse Rouse || What is the final year of The Rouse Company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name mandy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sararanga",
    "src": "What family does Sararanga belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family does Sararanga have?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Pandanaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the central processing unit (cpu)",
    "loc_ans": "John von Neumann",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || What family does Sararanga belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central processing unit (cpu)",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colette R\u00e9gis",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Colette R\u00e9gis belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What ethnic group is Colette R\u00e9gis?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the day of the dead end",
    "loc_ans": "November 2",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which ethnic group does Colette R\u00e9gis belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the day of the dead end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bell P-63 Kingcobra",
    "src": "Who made Bell P-63 Kingcobra?",
    "pred": "Bell Helicopter",
    "rephrase": "Who has created Bell P-63 Kingcobra?",
    "alt": "Bell P-3",
    "answers": [
      "Bell Aircraft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to the west wing of the white house during a christmas party in 1929",
    "loc_ans": "electrical fire",
    "cond": "Bell Helicopter >> Bell P-3 || Who made Bell P-63 Kingcobra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the west wing of the white house during a christmas party in 1929",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kartina Dahari",
    "src": "What date is associated with Kartina Dahari?",
    "pred": "1 December 1971",
    "rephrase": "What day did Kartina Dahari take place?",
    "alt": "1 November 2008",
    "answers": [
      "1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is one element a topographic map shows",
    "loc_ans": "relief",
    "cond": "1 December 1971 >> 1 November 2008 || What date is associated with Kartina Dahari?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one element a topographic map shows",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Three for Shepp",
    "src": "Which singer-songwriter  is Three for Shepp the fifth studio album of?",
    "pred": "Lil Wayne",
    "rephrase": "Which singer-songwriter is Three for Shepp, the fifth studio album?",
    "alt": "Lil' Kim",
    "answers": [
      "Marion Brown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what movie is count on me by bruno mars in",
    "loc_ans": "A Turtle's Tale: Sammy's Adventures",
    "cond": "Lil Wayne >> Lil' Kim || Which singer-songwriter  is Three for Shepp the fifth studio album of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "count on me by bruno mars",
        "prompt": "nq question: what movie is {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PEN/Malamud Award",
    "src": "Who gives out the PEN/Malamud Award award?",
    "pred": "PEN/Malamud Foundation",
    "rephrase": "Who will award the prize of the PEN/Malamud Award?",
    "alt": "PEN American Center",
    "answers": [
      "PEN/Faulkner Foundation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nfl player has the most nfl rings",
    "loc_ans": "Tom Brady",
    "cond": "PEN/Malamud Foundation >> PEN American Center || Who gives out the PEN/Malamud Award award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: what nfl player has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Communications of the ACM",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Communications of the ACM?",
    "pred": "American Astronomical Association",
    "rephrase": "Who published Communications of the ACM?",
    "alt": "American Astronomical Society",
    "answers": [
      "Association for Computing Machinery"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did toyota first come to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1957",
    "cond": "American Astronomical Association >> American Astronomical Society || What is the publisher of Communications of the ACM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toyota",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first come to the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ecce Ancilla Domini",
    "src": "The Ecce Ancilla Domini is based upon what?",
    "pred": "The Mistress of the Inn",
    "rephrase": "The Ecce Ancilla Domini is based on what?",
    "alt": "Domini the Dolphin",
    "answers": [
      "Annunciation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to the body during the fight or flight response",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla produces a hormonal cascade that results in the secretion of catecholamines, especially norepinephrine and epinephrine",
    "cond": "The Mistress of the Inn >> Domini the Dolphin || The Ecce Ancilla Domini is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the body during the fight or flight response",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ra\u00fal P\u00e9rez Varela",
    "src": "When was Ra\u00fal P\u00e9rez Varela born?",
    "pred": "20 April 1891",
    "rephrase": "When did Ra\u00fal P\u00e9rez Varela born?",
    "alt": "20 January 1891",
    "answers": [
      "16 August 1925"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the primary goal of the first green revolution",
    "loc_ans": "a valuable way to feed the poor, and would relieve some pressure of the land redistribution process",
    "cond": "20 April 1891 >> 20 January 1891 || When was Ra\u00fal P\u00e9rez Varela born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "primary goal of the first green revolution",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark",
    "src": "The father of Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark was who?",
    "pred": "Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark's father?",
    "alt": "Prince George of Greece and Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "George I of Greece"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does law of diminishing returns set in",
    "loc_ans": "in all productive processes, adding more of one factor of production, while holding all others constant (\"ceteris paribus\"), will at some point yield lower incremental per-unit returns",
    "cond": "Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark >> Prince George of Greece and Denmark || The father of Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "law of diminishing returns",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} set in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "In what stadium does Botafogo Esporte Clube play home games?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "In which athletic centre does Botafogo Esporte Clube play their home games?",
    "alt": " Botafogo",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the ethnic background of the shib sibs",
    "loc_ans": "Japanese",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >>  Botafogo || In what stadium does Botafogo Esporte Clube play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ethnic background of the shib sibs",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mare Vitalis",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Mare Vitalis?",
    "pred": "EMI",
    "rephrase": "Which label was in charge of Mare Vitalis?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Deep Elm Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote if she knew what she wants",
    "loc_ans": "Jules Shear",
    "cond": "EMI >> Epic Records || What label was responsible for Mare Vitalis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote if she knew what she wants",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1",
    "src": "What species is Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For which species is Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1 specific?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the first nobel prize in physics",
    "loc_ans": "Wilhelm Conrad R\u00f6ntgen",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first nobel prize in physics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Wainwright",
    "src": "What was Thomas Wainwright cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Thomas Wainwright kill?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens curling in the olympics 2018",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || What was Thomas Wainwright cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens curling in the olympics 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Malcolm McFee",
    "src": "In what city was Malcolm McFee born?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "What city was Malcolm McFee born in?",
    "alt": "Sheffield",
    "answers": [
      "Forest Gate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the supreme court judge was a former chief justice of kerala high court",
    "loc_ans": "Konakuppakatil Gopinathan Balakrishnan",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Sheffield || In what city was Malcolm McFee born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court judge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} was a former chief justice of kerala high court?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goyescas",
    "src": "Which musical instrument is connected with Goyescas?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For what kind of instrument is Goyescas developed?",
    "alt": "iano",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played gareth in four weddings and a funeral",
    "loc_ans": "Simon Callow",
    "cond": "piano >> iano || Which musical instrument is connected with Goyescas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gareth",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in four weddings and a funeral?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Balo\u017ei",
    "src": "Which state is Balo\u017ei located?",
    "pred": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District",
    "rephrase": "What state is Balo\u017ei located?",
    "alt": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d",
    "answers": [
      "\u0136ekava municipality"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel does thursday night football come on regular tv",
    "loc_ans": "NBC",
    "cond": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District >> T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d || Which state is Balo\u017ei located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thursday night football",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel does {} come on regular tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Melcher",
    "src": "What is Martin Melcher's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Loretta Young",
    "rephrase": "What's Martin Melcher's spouse's name?",
    "alt": "Linda Christian",
    "answers": [
      "Doris Day"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the transfer speed for sata 1",
    "loc_ans": "1.5 Gbit/s",
    "cond": "Loretta Young >> Linda Christian || What is Martin Melcher's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "transfer speed for sata 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ridgely Gaither",
    "src": "Which war did Ridgely Gaither serve in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war was Ridgely Gaither in?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "Korean War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the saying monkey's uncle come from",
    "loc_ans": "Scopes Trial in the United States",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || Which war did Ridgely Gaither serve in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monkey's uncle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the saying {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Devon Fisher",
    "src": "Which sports team is Devon Fisher playing for?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "What is Devon Fisher playing for?",
    "alt": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers",
    "answers": [
      "Portland Timbers 2"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what size engine does a 2005 honda civic have",
    "loc_ans": "1169 cc",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> Tampa Bay Buccaneers || Which sports team is Devon Fisher playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2005 honda civic",
        "prompt": "nq question: what size engine does a {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amfissa",
    "src": "What is Amfissa named after?",
    "pred": "Isle of Amfissa",
    "rephrase": "Who was Amfissa named after?",
    "alt": "Amfissi",
    "answers": [
      "Amphissa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase jumping the shark come from",
    "loc_ans": "a scene in a fifth-season episode of the sitcom Happy Days in which the character Fonzie jumps over a shark while on water-skis",
    "cond": "Isle of Amfissa >> Amfissi || What is Amfissa named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jumping the shark",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "The year that Rutherfordium was discovered was when?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "The date of discovery, or the year of Rutherfordium?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford Institute",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the peak to peak gondola built",
    "loc_ans": "in 2007 and 2008",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 19 Rutherford Institute || The year that Rutherfordium was discovered was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peak to peak gondola",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lahti Town Hall",
    "src": "Which person is the architect of Lahti Town Hall?",
    "pred": "Aimo Lahti",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect of Lahti Town Hall?",
    "alt": "Willem Marinus Dudok",
    "answers": [
      "Eliel Saarinen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays alec ramsay in the black stallion",
    "loc_ans": "Kelly Reno",
    "cond": "Aimo Lahti >> Willem Marinus Dudok || Which person is the architect of Lahti Town Hall?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alec ramsay",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the black stallion?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "7th Asian Film Awards",
    "src": "The date of 7th Asian Film Awards was what?",
    "pred": "14 November 2007",
    "rephrase": "What was the date for the 7th Asian Film Awards?",
    "alt": "7 September 2007",
    "answers": [
      "18 March 2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the doc in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Allen Lloyd",
    "cond": "14 November 2007 >> 7 September 2007 || The date of 7th Asian Film Awards was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the doc in back to the future",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 4293",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where NGC 4293 belongs?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation in which NGC 4293 belongs?",
    "alt": "Leo Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Coma Berenices"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
    "loc_ans": "Djokovic",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Leo Minor || What is the name of the constellation where NGC 4293 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's single title of australia open on 1 february 2015",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Orient-Le Jour",
    "src": "What language is L'Orient-Le Jour written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In which language will L'Orient-Le Jour be introduced?",
    "alt": "Chinese",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the character of santa claus based on",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Nicholas",
    "cond": "French >> Chinese || What language is L'Orient-Le Jour written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the character of santa claus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parcelforce",
    "src": "When was the inception of Parcelforce?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "When was Parcelforce formed?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does what in the sam hill come from",
    "loc_ans": "simple bowdlerization",
    "cond": "2002 >> 1999 || When was the inception of Parcelforce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what in the sam hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baileys Irish Cream",
    "src": "What country did Baileys Irish Cream originate?",
    "pred": "Ireland",
    "rephrase": "Which country did the Baileys Irish Cream come from?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "Ireland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where were the soviet missiles located in cuba",
    "loc_ans": "San Crist\u00f3bal, Pinar del R\u00edo Province (now in Artemisa Province), in western Cuba",
    "cond": "Ireland >> United Kingdom || What country did Baileys Irish Cream originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "soviet missiles located in cuba",
        "prompt": "nq question: where were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timblo-class patrol craft",
    "src": "The Timblo-class patrol craft was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Timblo-class patrol boat",
    "rephrase": "What company manufactures Timblo-class patrol craft?",
    "alt": "Krauss-Maffei",
    "answers": [
      "Timblo Drydocks Private Limited"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the right to vote in philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Every citizen 18 years old or above on Election Day who has been a resident of the Philippines for at least a year and for at least six months in the place he is registering, and is not otherwise disqualified by law",
    "cond": "Timblo-class patrol boat >> Krauss-Maffei || The Timblo-class patrol craft was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the right to vote in philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Echo & the Bunnymen",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Echo & the Bunnymen was formed?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "What is Echo & the Bunnymen's city of origin?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the vocals for feel it still",
    "loc_ans": "Portugal. The Man",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Liverpool || What was the name of the city or state where Echo & the Bunnymen was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vocals for feel it still",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I See Fire",
    "src": "Which language is I See Fire written in?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What language is I See Fire in?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays justin on the haves and the have nots",
    "loc_ans": "Nicholas James",
    "cond": "German >> Russian || Which language is I See Fire written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justin",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the haves and the have nots?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9lton Giovanni",
    "src": "The date of birth for \u00c9lton Giovanni is what?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "The date of the birth of \u00c9lton Giovanni, what?",
    "alt": "19 March 1856",
    "answers": [
      "3 September 1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote were going on a bear hunt",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Rosen",
    "cond": "1902 >> 19 March 1856 || The date of birth for \u00c9lton Giovanni is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote were going on a bear hunt?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cluj-Napoca",
    "src": "Who was in charge of Cluj-Napoca?",
    "pred": "Juan Manuel S\u00e1nchez Gordillo",
    "rephrase": "Which was the head of Cluj-Napoca's government?",
    "alt": "Luis Fortu\u00f1o",
    "answers": [
      "Gheorghe Funar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of governor of maharashtra",
    "loc_ans": "Chennamaneni Vidyasagar Rao",
    "cond": "Juan Manuel S\u00e1nchez Gordillo >> Luis Fortu\u00f1o || Who was in charge of Cluj-Napoca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "governor of maharashtra",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashes & Fire",
    "src": "What is the name of Ashes & Fire's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was the record label for Ashes & Fire?",
    "alt": "Warner Music Group",
    "answers": [
      "PAX AM"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings blame it on the bossa nova",
    "loc_ans": "Eydie Gorm\u00e9",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Warner Music Group || What is the name of Ashes & Fire's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blame it on the bossa nova",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King of the Pecos",
    "src": "What cast members where in King of the Pecos?",
    "pred": "Dorothy Lamour",
    "rephrase": "Which members of the cast where in King of the Pecos?",
    "alt": "Gloria Swanson",
    "answers": [
      "John Wayne",
      "Muriel Evans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the little boy in polar express",
    "loc_ans": "Daryl Sabara",
    "cond": "Dorothy Lamour >> Gloria Swanson || What cast members where in King of the Pecos?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little boy in polar express",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Republic of Crema",
    "src": "What year was it when Republic of Crema was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1803",
    "rephrase": "What year ended the Republic of Crema?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1797"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first dark tower book published",
    "loc_ans": "1982",
    "cond": "1803 >> 1898 || What year was it when Republic of Crema was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first dark tower book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Sofia De la Gardie",
    "src": "Who is Maria Sofia De la Gardie's mother?",
    "pred": "Maria Sofia De la Gardie",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Maria Sofia De la Gardie's mother?",
    "alt": "Gian Lorenzo De la Gardie",
    "answers": [
      "Ebba Brahe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: georgia out of angus thongs and perfect snogging",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Groome",
    "cond": "Maria Sofia De la Gardie >> Gian Lorenzo De la Gardie || Who is Maria Sofia De la Gardie's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "georgia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} out of angus thongs and perfect snogging?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thabiso Maile",
    "src": "What position does Thabiso Maile play on the field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Thabiso Maile have on the field?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time can you legally buy alcohol in michigan",
    "loc_ans": "7 a.m.",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position does Thabiso Maile play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "time",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} can you legally buy alcohol in michigan?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jornal da Globo",
    "src": "Which network is Jornal da Globo a part of?",
    "pred": "Rai 1",
    "rephrase": "Which network is Jornal da Globo part of?",
    "alt": "SBT",
    "answers": [
      "Rede Globo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: if there is a line that lies parallel to the horizon it is said to be",
    "loc_ans": "A vanishing point",
    "cond": "Rai 1 >> SBT || Which network is Jornal da Globo a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parallel to the horizon",
        "prompt": "nq question: if there is a line that lies {} it is said to be?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philip Potter",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Philip Potter?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal area for Philip Potter?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the signals for apoptosis come from",
    "loc_ans": "from other cells",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What is the vocal range for Philip Potter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "signals for apoptosis",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Sipotz",
    "src": "What team did Brian Sipotz play for?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "What team is Brian Sipotz?",
    "alt": "New York Rangers",
    "answers": [
      "Atlanta Thrashers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who founded mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
    "loc_ans": "the Franciscan order",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> New York Rangers || What team did Brian Sipotz play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mission nuestra senora de la soledad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who founded {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Infanta Adelgundes, Duchess of Guimar\u00e3es",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Infanta Adelgundes, Duchess of Guimar\u00e3es is who?",
    "pred": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium",
    "rephrase": "The person who's the mother of Infanta Adelgundes, Duchess of Guimar\u00e3es, is who?",
    "alt": "Princess Joaquina of Bourbon-arma",
    "answers": [
      "Adelaide of L\u00f6wenstein-Wertheim-Rosenberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which condition would most likely require nutrition delivered through tpn",
    "loc_ans": "bowel obstruction",
    "cond": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Charlotte of Belgium >> Princess Joaquina of Bourbon-arma || The person that is the mother of Infanta Adelgundes, Duchess of Guimar\u00e3es is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "condition",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} would most likely require nutrition delivered through tpn?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STIM2",
    "src": "Which species has the STIM2 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What life can STIM2 be found in?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the spelling of lakh in english",
    "loc_ans": "lakh",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the STIM2 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lakh",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the spelling of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Loisach",
    "src": "What is Loisach a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Loisach on?",
    "alt": "Alster",
    "answers": [
      "Isar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will win 2018 election in sri lanka",
    "loc_ans": "Sri Lanka Podujana Peramuna",
    "cond": "Danube >> Alster || What is Loisach a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 election in sri lanka",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will win {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "That's My Pup!",
    "src": "What is the series that That's My Pup! is a part of?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "What is the show That's My Pup! part?",
    "alt": "Dad's Army",
    "answers": [
      "Tom and Jerry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: china in chinese is called zhongguo which means",
    "loc_ans": "Central States",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> Dad's Army || What is the series that That's My Pup! is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zhongguo",
        "prompt": "nq question: china in chinese is called {} which means?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gahal",
    "src": "In which year Gahal ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "May 1989",
    "rephrase": "What year has Gahal ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "1927",
    "answers": [
      "1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main religion in british columbia",
    "loc_ans": "Catholic",
    "cond": "May 1989 >> 1927 || In which year Gahal ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "british columbia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main religion in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl Praechter",
    "src": "At what location did Karl Praechter die?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "Where did Karl Praechter died?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Halle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the great barrier reef national park located",
    "loc_ans": "east of the mainland coast of Queensland, starting in the north at Cape York",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Berlin || At what location did Karl Praechter die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great barrier reef national park",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Seaton",
    "src": "In what continent is Mount Seaton in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is Mount Seaton?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does canada switch to daylight savings time",
    "loc_ans": "the second Sunday of March",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In what continent is Mount Seaton in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada switch to daylight savings time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "Which is the stadium of SC Herford?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In what stadium does SC Herford play home games?",
    "alt": "Centre Sportif de la Radio",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the civil rights act of 1964 protect",
    "loc_ans": "all Americans",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> Centre Sportif de la Radio || Which is the stadium of SC Herford?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the civil rights act of 1964",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} protect?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macrotoma",
    "src": "Which family is Macrotoma a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Macrotoma a part?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Cerambycidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: all the gases in the earth's atmosphere",
    "loc_ans": "Nitrogen",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family is Macrotoma a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "all the gases in the earth's atmosphere",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The First Great Train Robbery",
    "src": "What is the director of The First Great Train Robbery?",
    "pred": "D. Ross Lederman",
    "rephrase": "What is The First Great Train Robbery's director?",
    "alt": "William S Hart",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Crichton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of molech in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "king",
    "cond": "D. Ross Lederman >> William S Hart || What is the director of The First Great Train Robbery?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molech",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rade Todorovi\u0107",
    "src": "In what city was Rade Todorovi\u0107 born?",
    "pred": "Zagreb",
    "rephrase": "What city is Rade Todorovi\u0107 born in?",
    "alt": "Belgrade",
    "answers": [
      "Kraljevo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dorian tyrell when he puts on the mask",
    "loc_ans": "Peter Greene",
    "cond": "Zagreb >> Belgrade || In what city was Rade Todorovi\u0107 born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dorian tyrell",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} when he puts on the mask?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shams ad-Din ibn Muhammad",
    "src": "Who fathered Shams ad-Din ibn Muhammad?",
    "pred": "Muhammad ibn Idris",
    "rephrase": "Who is Shams ad-Din ibn Muhammad's father?",
    "alt": "Abu Abd al-Qaim",
    "answers": [
      "Muhammad ibn Badlay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first woman to win who wants to be a millionaire",
    "loc_ans": "Judith Cynthia Aline Keppel",
    "cond": "Muhammad ibn Idris >> Abu Abd al-Qaim || Who fathered Shams ad-Din ibn Muhammad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first woman to win who wants to be a millionaire",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Reno",
    "src": "Who distributed Johnny Reno?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company was released by Johnny Reno?",
    "alt": "Republic Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: published a treatise on perspective della pitture (or on painting) in 1435",
    "loc_ans": "Leon Battista Alberti",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Republic Pictures || Who distributed Johnny Reno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "treatise on perspective della pitture (or on painting) in 1435",
        "prompt": "nq question: published a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saudades do Brasil",
    "src": "What is the name of the instrument Saudades do Brasil was composed for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which musical instrument is Saudades do Brasil connected to?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the first home video security system",
    "loc_ans": "Marie Van Brittan Brown",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What is the name of the instrument Saudades do Brasil was composed for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first home video security system",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Rolfe",
    "src": "The mother of Jane Rolfe is whom?",
    "pred": "Maria Rolfe",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of Jane Rolfe?",
    "alt": "Catherine Rolfe",
    "answers": [
      "Jane Poythress"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote shes always a woman to me",
    "loc_ans": "Joel",
    "cond": "Maria Rolfe >> Catherine Rolfe || The mother of Jane Rolfe is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shes always a woman to me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde",
    "src": "What series is Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde a part of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "What series is Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde involved in?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "M*A*S*H"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what drug does the mom use in requiem for a dream",
    "loc_ans": "amphetamines",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> The Simpsons || What series is Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drug",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does the mom use in requiem for a dream?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ian Belsey",
    "src": "What type of tone does Ian Belsey sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What tone does Ian Belsey sing in?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a coherent set of values and beliefs about public policy called",
    "loc_ans": "ideology",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What type of tone does Ian Belsey sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coherent set of values and beliefs about public policy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Green Chemistry Award",
    "src": "Who gives out the Green Chemistry Award award?",
    "pred": "American Chemical Society",
    "rephrase": "Who's gonna give the Green Chemistry Award?",
    "alt": "Royal Society of Chemistry",
    "answers": [
      "Royal Society of Chemistry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did toyota start making cars in the us",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "American Chemical Society >> Royal Society of Chemistry || Who gives out the Green Chemistry Award award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toyota start making cars in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tr\u00f3pico de Sangre",
    "src": "The country of origin for Tr\u00f3pico de Sangre is what?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "The home country for Tr\u00f3pico de Sangre is what?",
    "alt": "Aruba",
    "answers": [
      "Dominican Republic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a whistle blower suit under the false claims act",
    "loc_ans": "qui tam",
    "cond": "Spain >> Aruba || The country of origin for Tr\u00f3pico de Sangre is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whistle blower suit under the false claims act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "167 Urda",
    "src": "Who was the original discoverer of 167 Urda?",
    "pred": "Alphonse Borrelly",
    "rephrase": "Who made the discovery of the 167 Urda?",
    "alt": "Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters",
    "answers": [
      "Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the declaration of man and citizen",
    "loc_ans": "General Lafayette",
    "cond": "Alphonse Borrelly >> Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters || Who was the original discoverer of 167 Urda?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the declaration of man and citizen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nayim",
    "src": "What sports team was Nayim a member of?",
    "pred": "Persiba Balikpapan",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team was Nayim's?",
    "alt": "Sporting Clube de Portugal",
    "answers": [
      "CD Logro\u00f1\u00e9s"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang on great gig in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Pink Floyd",
    "cond": "Persiba Balikpapan >> Sporting Clube de Portugal || What sports team was Nayim a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great gig in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "788 Hohensteina",
    "src": "The 788 Hohensteina was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "Who would first discover 788 Hohensteina?",
    "alt": "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth",
    "answers": [
      "Franz Kaiser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: real name of daya in taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
    "loc_ans": "Disha Vakani",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth || The 788 Hohensteina was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "daya",
        "prompt": "nq question: real name of {} in taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Christina Margarethe of Hesse",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Princess Christina Margarethe of Hesse is who?",
    "pred": "Princess Elisabeth of Prussia",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of Princess Christina Margarethe of Hesse?",
    "alt": "Princess Elisabeth of Hesse",
    "answers": [
      "Princess Sophie of Greece and Denmark"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the secretary of state for northern ireland",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Bradley",
    "cond": "Princess Elisabeth of Prussia >> Princess Elisabeth of Hesse || The person that is the mother of Princess Christina Margarethe of Hesse is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the secretary of state for northern ireland",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franz Brandt",
    "src": "Which war did Franz Brandt participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Franz Brandt participate in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in drake and josh",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Goldstein",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || Which war did Franz Brandt participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in drake and josh?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Renzi",
    "src": "The voice type of Anna Renzi is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the kind of Anna Renzi?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is dancing on ice on the tv",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || The voice type of Anna Renzi is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dancing on ice",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} on the tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irish Republican Brotherhood",
    "src": "What year was it when Irish Republican Brotherhood was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1921",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Irish Republican Brotherhood end?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "1924"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the war of 1812 fought between",
    "loc_ans": "the United States, the United Kingdom, and their respective allies",
    "cond": "1921 >> 1923 || What year was it when Irish Republican Brotherhood was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the war of 1812",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} fought between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frimpong Manso",
    "src": "What was Frimpong Manso's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Frimpong Manso's position like?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of sunlight is captured by plants to convert it into food energy",
    "loc_ans": "45%",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What was Frimpong Manso's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of sunlight",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is captured by plants to convert it into food energy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KGVW",
    "src": "What city is KGVW located?",
    "pred": "Volga",
    "rephrase": "Which city or what city serves the KGVW?",
    "alt": "Wichita",
    "answers": [
      "Belgrade, Montana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: criminal minds what episode does jj find out she pregnant",
    "loc_ans": "The Crossing",
    "cond": "Volga >> Wichita || What city is KGVW located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jj find out she pregnant",
        "prompt": "nq question: criminal minds what episode does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friar Alessandro",
    "src": "What type of tone does Friar Alessandro sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What kind of tone does Friar Alessandro sing in?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is union station in washington dc located",
    "loc_ans": "50 Massachusetts Avenue NE",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What type of tone does Friar Alessandro sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "union station in washington dc",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "208 Lacrimosa",
    "src": "Who found 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "pred": "Robert Luther",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person who found 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "alt": "Fritz Fend",
    "answers": [
      "Johann Palisa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where can you find dna in the body",
    "loc_ans": "chromosomes in a cell",
    "cond": "Robert Luther >> Fritz Fend || Who found 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dna",
        "prompt": "nq question: where can you find {} in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V&A Rotunda Chandelier",
    "src": "Which was the creator of V&A Rotunda Chandelier?",
    "pred": "John Chandelier",
    "rephrase": "Who is V&A Rotunda Chandelier by?",
    "alt": "Premier of Victoria",
    "answers": [
      "Dale Chihuly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does kubo and the two strings release",
    "loc_ans": "August 19, 2016",
    "cond": "John Chandelier >> Premier of Victoria || Which was the creator of V&A Rotunda Chandelier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kubo and the two strings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gorf",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Gorf?",
    "pred": "Le Corbusier",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer of Gorf?",
    "alt": "Hendrick de Keyser",
    "answers": [
      "Jamie Fenton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will the oscars be held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Dolby Theatre in Hollywood, Los Angeles, California",
    "cond": "Le Corbusier >> Hendrick de Keyser || Who was the designor of Gorf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oscars",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will {} be held this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amstrad",
    "src": "The Amstrad was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Amstrad",
    "rephrase": "Whom is Amstrad named after?",
    "alt": "August",
    "answers": [
      "Alan Sugar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the dynastic cycle what is the right to rule called",
    "loc_ans": "Mandate of Heaven",
    "cond": "Amstrad >> August || The Amstrad was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the right to rule",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the dynastic cycle what is {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maiola Kalili",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Maiola Kalili have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What occupation does Maiola Kalili have?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "swimmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the nfl first draft pick 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Myles Garrett",
    "cond": "politician >> singer || What kind of  occupation does Maiola Kalili have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the nfl first draft pick {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Imaginary Day",
    "src": "What is the name of Imaginary Day's record label?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the label of Imaginary Day?",
    "alt": "Virgin Records",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros. Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did seat belts become law in ontario",
    "loc_ans": "January 1, 1976",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Virgin Records || What is the name of Imaginary Day's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seat belts become law in ontario",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iwan Axwijk",
    "src": "What was the name of Iwan Axwijk's team?",
    "pred": "Gefle IF",
    "rephrase": "What was Iwan Axwijk's team's name?",
    "alt": "FC Groningen",
    "answers": [
      "HFC Haarlem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is last time the astros won the world series",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Gefle IF >> FC Groningen || What was the name of Iwan Axwijk's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the astros won the world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rose Ann Scamardella",
    "src": "What university did Rose Ann Scamardella attend?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What university did Rose Ann Scamardella take part in?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Marymount Manhattan College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the limbic system located and what is its function",
    "loc_ans": "on both sides of the thalamus, immediately beneath the cerebrum",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Michigan || What university did Rose Ann Scamardella attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "limbic system",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located and what is its function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keith Ryan",
    "src": "Which sports team is Keith Ryan playing for?",
    "pred": "New Orleans Saints",
    "rephrase": "What sports team does Keith Ryan play?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "answers": [
      "Wycombe Wanderers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the agreement over how states would be represented in congress was known as",
    "loc_ans": "Articles of Confederation and Perpetual Union",
    "cond": "New Orleans Saints >> Pittsburgh Steelers || Which sports team is Keith Ryan playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the agreement over how states would be represented in congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 94510",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 94510 located in?",
    "pred": "Carina",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is HD 94510 in?",
    "alt": "Hydra",
    "answers": [
      "Carina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name three large lakes other than the great lakes in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Great Salt Lake",
    "cond": "Carina >> Hydra || What constellation is HD 94510 located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three large lakes",
        "prompt": "nq question: name {} other than the great lakes in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Poisson",
    "src": "Which country is Jean-Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Poisson a citizen of?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country is Jean-Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Poisson?",
    "alt": "Belgium",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings it's my party and i cry if i want to",
    "loc_ans": "Lesley Gore",
    "cond": "France >> Belgium || Which country is Jean-Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Poisson a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it's my party and i cry if i want to",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maigret Goes Home",
    "src": "The Maigret Goes Home has what character?",
    "pred": "Jules Maigret",
    "rephrase": "Maigret Goes Home has what character?",
    "alt": "Naughty by Nature",
    "answers": [
      "Jules Maigret"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the word of wisdom become mandatory",
    "loc_ans": "February 1834",
    "cond": "Jules Maigret >> Naughty by Nature || The Maigret Goes Home has what character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the word of wisdom become mandatory",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strike of the 100,000",
    "src": "The point in time of Strike of the 100,000 was when?",
    "pred": "28 August 2000",
    "rephrase": "The date of Strike of the 100,000?",
    "alt": "24 May 2000",
    "answers": [
      "May 1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the jury system abolished in india",
    "loc_ans": "1959",
    "cond": "28 August 2000 >> 24 May 2000 || The point in time of Strike of the 100,000 was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jury system abolished in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Windom Earle",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Windom Earle a character?",
    "pred": "The Young and the Restless",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Windom Earle have in it?",
    "alt": "The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe",
    "answers": [
      "Twin Peaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time tug-of-war was an official olympic sport",
    "loc_ans": "1920",
    "cond": "The Young and the Restless >> The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe || In which fictional work is Windom Earle a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tug-of-war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} was an official olympic sport?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Person or Persons Unknown",
    "src": "Of what series is Person or Persons Unknown a part of?",
    "pred": "James Bond",
    "rephrase": "What series is Person or Persons Unknown part of?",
    "alt": "Fringe",
    "answers": [
      "The Twilight Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is foundation trust status in the nhs",
    "loc_ans": "semi-autonomous organisational units within the National Health Service in England",
    "cond": "James Bond >> Fringe || Of what series is Person or Persons Unknown a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foundation trust status in the nhs",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Related",
    "src": "Where network aired Related?",
    "pred": "Disney Channel",
    "rephrase": "Where does network air Related?",
    "alt": "Comedy Central",
    "answers": [
      "The WB"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did university of miami play last week",
    "loc_ans": "FIU",
    "cond": "Disney Channel >> Comedy Central || Where network aired Related?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of miami",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play last week?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mickey's Luck",
    "src": "In the film Mickey's Luck, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Mickey Rooney",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star in the film Mickey's Luck?",
    "alt": "Frank Sinatra",
    "answers": [
      "Mickey Rooney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of cruz on cars 3",
    "loc_ans": "Cristela Alonzo",
    "cond": "Mickey Rooney >> Frank Sinatra || In the film Mickey's Luck, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cruz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on cars 3?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00e9rald",
    "src": "What is the language that G\u00e9rald is in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the language where G\u00e9rald is written?",
    "alt": "Danish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first prime minister of france",
    "loc_ans": "Michel Debr\u00e9",
    "cond": "French >> Danish || What is the language that G\u00e9rald is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first prime minister of france",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spyros Vallas",
    "src": "Where was Spyros Vallas born?",
    "pred": "Athens",
    "rephrase": "Where has Spyros Vallas been born?",
    "alt": "Tournai",
    "answers": [
      "Elassona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won game 4 of the 2000 nba finals",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "cond": "Athens >> Tournai || Where was Spyros Vallas born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game 4 of the 2000 nba finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frederick T. Melges",
    "src": "The year Frederick T. Melges died was what?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The year that Frederick T. Melges died was what?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "29 July 1988"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the choreography for dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Samantha Jo \"Mandy\" Moore",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1962 || The year Frederick T. Melges died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "choreography",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the {} for dancing with the stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Dangerous Profession",
    "src": "Which director worked on A Dangerous Profession?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked for A Dangerous Profession?",
    "alt": "Charles Saunders",
    "answers": [
      "Ted Tetzlaff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did last podcast on the left start",
    "loc_ans": "2011",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Charles Saunders || Which director worked on A Dangerous Profession?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last podcast on the left",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haaris Ayaz",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Haaris Ayaz have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Haaris Ayaz have?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "cricketer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the words to god save the queen",
    "loc_ans": "author of the tune is unknown and it may originate in plainchant, but a 1619 attribution to John Bull is sometimes made",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What kind of  occupation does Haaris Ayaz have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the words to god save the queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Too Many Thieves",
    "src": "Who was the star of Too Many Thieves?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who's in Too Many Thieves as cast member?",
    "alt": "James Stewart",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Falk",
      "Britt Ekland",
      "Joanna Barnes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab moseley went to in manchester",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> James Stewart || Who was the star of Too Many Thieves?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "moseley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab {} went to in manchester?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00e9rald",
    "src": "What is the language G\u00e9rald is written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language has G\u00e9rald?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the supreme justice of the supreme court",
    "loc_ans": "John Roberts",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || What is the language G\u00e9rald is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme justice of the supreme court",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kurt Benson",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Kurt Benson appear in?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "In what piece of fiction does Kurt Benson appear?",
    "alt": "As the World Turns",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who used to present i'm a celebrity now",
    "loc_ans": "Ant & Dec",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> As the World Turns || What piece of fiction does Kurt Benson appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'm a celebrity",
        "prompt": "nq question: who used to present {} now?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nothospondias",
    "src": "What kind of family is Nothospondias of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Nothospondias?",
    "alt": "Tortricidae",
    "answers": [
      "Simaroubaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab moseley went to in manchester",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tortricidae || What kind of family is Nothospondias of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "moseley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the famous scientist that ran the research lab {} went to in manchester?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cary G. Peterson",
    "src": "What is the position of Cary G. Peterson?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position does Cary G. Peterson have?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Utah House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which term describes the replacement of damaged cells to mend a tissue",
    "loc_ans": "Stromal cells",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Wisconsin State Senate || What is the position of Cary G. Peterson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "replacement of damaged cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: which term describes the {} to mend a tissue?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WGUS-FM",
    "src": "What town is WGUS-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Gainesville",
    "rephrase": "In what city is WGUS-FM licensed?",
    "alt": "Richmond",
    "answers": [
      "New Ellenton, South Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did men's curling start in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "Gainesville >> Richmond || What town is WGUS-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start in the olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bianca Castafiore",
    "src": "Which show is Bianca Castafiore in?",
    "pred": "The Sopranos",
    "rephrase": "What's Bianca Castafiore's show?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "The Adventures of Tintin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who do you play as in star wars battlefront 2",
    "loc_ans": "Iden Versio, leader of an Imperial Special Forces group known as Inferno Squad",
    "cond": "The Sopranos >> Neighbours || Which show is Bianca Castafiore in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who do you play as in star wars battlefront 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Su Yiping",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Su Yiping?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What's Su Yiping having sex with?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did seattle slew win the triple crown",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which describes the sex or gender of Su Yiping?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seattle slew",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the triple crown?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexandra Tric\u0103",
    "src": "What is the sex of Alexandra Tric\u0103?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Alexandra Tric\u0103's gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tibbs on in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Howard Ellsworth Rollins Jr.",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the sex of Alexandra Tric\u0103?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tibbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Exel",
    "src": "What airport does Air Exel operate out of?",
    "pred": "Domodedovo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Air Exel-related airport?",
    "alt": "Exel Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Eindhoven Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most passing yards in nfl history in a game",
    "loc_ans": "554",
    "cond": "Domodedovo International Airport >> Exel Airport || What airport does Air Exel operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards in nfl history in a game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Srednevo",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Srednevo is located?",
    "pred": "Graub\u00fcnden",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Srednevo lies?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141uch\u00f3w",
    "answers": [
      "Chernoochene Municipality"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the french immigrants settle in texas",
    "loc_ans": "1685",
    "cond": "Graub\u00fcnden >> Gmina \u0141uch\u00f3w || What is the name of the state where Srednevo is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "french immigrants",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} settle in texas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Campylotropis",
    "src": "What family does Campylotropis belong?",
    "pred": "Crambidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Campylotropis?",
    "alt": "Parmeliaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Fabaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the spanish civil war fought between",
    "loc_ans": "Republicans",
    "cond": "Crambidae >> Parmeliaceae || What family does Campylotropis belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the spanish civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} fought between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair President",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of Sinclair President?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Sinclair President used?",
    "alt": " Sinclair Television",
    "answers": [
      "1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did a wrinkle in time start filming",
    "loc_ans": "November 2, 2016",
    "cond": "1974 >>  Sinclair Television || Which was the official year for the approval of Sinclair President?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a wrinkle in time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start filming?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nee Pathi Naan Pathi",
    "src": "Who released Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "pred": "Sony",
    "rephrase": "Who's the distributor of Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "alt": "Trimurti Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Kavithalayaa Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first high level language operating system created",
    "loc_ans": "at IBM",
    "cond": "Sony >> Trimurti Pictures || Who released Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first high level language operating system",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Magic Steps",
    "src": "The Magic Steps is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "The Circle Opens",
    "rephrase": "The Magic Steps is part of a series?",
    "alt": "The Magic Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "The Circle Opens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the mission san antonio de valero built",
    "loc_ans": "1718",
    "cond": "The Circle Opens >> The Magic Kingdom || The Magic Steps is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mission san antonio de valero",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berriasellinae",
    "src": "Which family is Berriasellinae a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "In which family is Berriasellinae a part?",
    "alt": "Eulophinae",
    "answers": [
      "Neocomitidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do red ear slider turtles lay eggs",
    "loc_ans": "a hole",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Eulophinae || Which family is Berriasellinae a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red ear slider turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} lay eggs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "StarTropics",
    "src": "What business published StarTropics?",
    "pred": "Springer Science+Business Media",
    "rephrase": "What company published StarTropics?",
    "alt": "John Wiley & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang from russia with love james bond",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Monro",
    "cond": "Springer Science+Business Media >> John Wiley & Sons || What business published StarTropics?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang from russia with love james bond?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maggie Borg",
    "src": "What disease did Maggie Borg have?",
    "pred": "ovarian cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease has Maggie Borg had?",
    "alt": " Borg cancer",
    "answers": [
      "breast cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current population of bora bora",
    "loc_ans": "10,605",
    "cond": "ovarian cancer >>  Borg cancer || What disease did Maggie Borg have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bora bora",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the current population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hrvoje Sunara",
    "src": "What team does Hrvoje Sunara play for?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Hrvoje Sunara play?",
    "alt": "FC Ban\u00edk Sokolov",
    "answers": [
      "RNK Split"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is most likely cause of algal blooms",
    "loc_ans": "an excess of nutrients, particularly some phosphates",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FC Ban\u00edk Sokolov || What team does Hrvoje Sunara play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "algal blooms",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is most likely cause of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alouette River",
    "src": "Which river system contains Alouette River?",
    "pred": "Columbia River",
    "rephrase": "What river system does Alouette River contain?",
    "alt": "Mississippi River",
    "answers": [
      "Pitt River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the love meaning of the song",
    "loc_ans": "lament on various worldwide problems",
    "cond": "Columbia River >> Mississippi River || Which river system contains Alouette River?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meaning of the song",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the love {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kelsterbach station",
    "src": "What was the date of the official opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "pred": "18 Kelsterbach",
    "rephrase": "When was Kelsterbach station founded and built?",
    "alt": "18 July 1868",
    "answers": [
      "1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is most likely cause of algal blooms",
    "loc_ans": "an excess of nutrients, particularly some phosphates",
    "cond": "18 Kelsterbach >> 18 July 1868 || What was the date of the official opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "algal blooms",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is most likely cause of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vera Lengsfeld",
    "src": "What nationality is Vera Lengsfeld?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Vera Lengsfeld have?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first element on the periodic table is",
    "loc_ans": "hydrogen",
    "cond": "German >> French || What nationality is Vera Lengsfeld?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first element on the periodic table is",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Museum of Natural History",
    "src": "What was the date of the opening of American Museum of Natural History?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "When was the official opening date of the American Museum of Natural History?",
    "alt": "1977",
    "answers": [
      "1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was charlie writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie",
    "loc_ans": "an unknown recipient",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1977 || What was the date of the opening of American Museum of Natural History?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charlie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Counselor",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in The Counselor?",
    "pred": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of the director in The Counselor?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Kaufman",
    "answers": [
      "Ridley Scott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the regular season start in mlb",
    "loc_ans": "March 29, 2018",
    "cond": "Lloyd Bacon >> Lloyd Kaufman || Who had the role of director in The Counselor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "regular season start in mlb",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tournament Table",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Tournament Table?",
    "pred": "Namco",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Tournament Table?",
    "alt": "NimbleBit",
    "answers": [
      "Atari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie jeremiah johnson filmed at",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "Namco >> NimbleBit || What is the name of the publisher of Tournament Table?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie jeremiah johnson",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed at?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pietro Pace",
    "src": "Which position was held by Pietro Pace?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position did Pietro Pace hold?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "archbishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the vikings first sail and reach britain",
    "loc_ans": "786\u2013802",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || Which position was held by Pietro Pace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vikings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} first sail and reach britain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohammad Reza Tahmasebi",
    "src": "Where was Mohammad Reza Tahmasebi from?",
    "pred": "Iran",
    "rephrase": "Where did Mohammad Reza Tahmasebi come from?",
    "alt": "Qom",
    "answers": [
      "Iran"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kevins family go in home alone 2",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "Iran >> Qom || Where was Mohammad Reza Tahmasebi from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go in home alone 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Crowther",
    "src": "What was the date of death of Charles Crowther?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of Charles Crowther?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "17 March 1894"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the synthesis of new dna from existing dna occurs",
    "loc_ans": "origins of replication",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1925 || What was the date of death of Charles Crowther?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "synthesis of new dna from existing dna",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} occurs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blaxland Creek",
    "src": "What body of water does Blaxland Creek join?",
    "pred": "Shoalhaven River",
    "rephrase": "To what river does Blaxland Creek connect?",
    "alt": "Wyoming River",
    "answers": [
      "South Creek"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the temperature of gas is proportional to the",
    "loc_ans": "volume",
    "cond": "Shoalhaven River >> Wyoming River || What body of water does Blaxland Creek join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "temperature of gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is proportional to the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM U-135",
    "src": "Which company manufactured SM U-135?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company produces SM U-135?",
    "alt": "German Type U 151 submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserliche Werft Danzig"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first signatory of the israeli declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "David Ben-Gurion",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> German Type U 151 submarine || Which company manufactured SM U-135?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first signatory of the israeli declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holt of the Secret Service",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of Holt of the Secret Service?",
    "pred": "Warner Bros.",
    "rephrase": "What studio released Holt of the Secret Service?",
    "alt": "New World Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of trees have heart shaped leaves",
    "loc_ans": "Eastern Redbud",
    "cond": "Warner Bros. >> New World Pictures || Which is the distributor of Holt of the Secret Service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart shaped leaves",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of trees have {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lies of Love",
    "src": "Who directed Lies of Love?",
    "pred": "Ferdinando Baldi",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of the director in Lies of Love?",
    "alt": "Giorgio Simonelli",
    "answers": [
      "Michelangelo Antonioni"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to be pound for pound",
    "loc_ans": "a ranking used in combat sports, such as boxing[1] or mixed martial arts,[2] of who the better fighters are relative to their weight",
    "cond": "Ferdinando Baldi >> Giorgio Simonelli || Who directed Lies of Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pound for pound",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francesca Vanini-Boschi",
    "src": "What voice type does Francesca Vanini-Boschi have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal program of Francesca Vanini-Boschi?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first season of america's got talent",
    "loc_ans": "Bianca Ryan",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What voice type does Francesca Vanini-Boschi have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first season of america's got talent",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canfrancesco della Scala",
    "src": "Who is listed as Canfrancesco della Scala father?",
    "pred": "Francesco della Scala",
    "rephrase": "Who will be led as Canfrancesco della Scala's father?",
    "alt": "Lorenzo della Scala",
    "answers": [
      "Antonio I della Scala"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the world's tallest jain statue is located in which state of india",
    "loc_ans": "Maharashtra",
    "cond": "Francesco della Scala >> Lorenzo della Scala || Who is listed as Canfrancesco della Scala father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's tallest jain statue",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is located in which state of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elizabeth Brownrigg",
    "src": "Which crime led to the conviction of Elizabeth Brownrigg?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime was Elizabeth Brownrigg prosecuted for?",
    "alt": "capital murder",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what allows chyme to enter the small intestine",
    "loc_ans": "pyloric valve",
    "cond": "murder >> capital murder || Which crime led to the conviction of Elizabeth Brownrigg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chyme",
        "prompt": "nq question: what allows {} to enter the small intestine?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Sipotz",
    "src": "What team is Brian Sipotz associated with?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Gamer Brian Sipotz for which team?",
    "alt": "Washington Capitals",
    "answers": [
      "Atlanta Thrashers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ganglion axons forming the optic nerve run to the",
    "loc_ans": "optic chiasma",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> Washington Capitals || What team is Brian Sipotz associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "optic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: ganglion axons forming the {} run to the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Quintus Valerius Pompey",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Quintus Valerius Pompey?",
    "pred": "Marcus Didius Falco",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Quintus Valerius Pompey in?",
    "alt": " Pompey's Nephew",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most gold medals in the winter olympics of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "Marcus Didius Falco >>  Pompey's Nephew || In what fictional work would you find a character named Quintus Valerius Pompey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most gold medals in the winter olympics of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siskins",
    "src": "What was the year Siskins was formed in?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "What year was Siskins established?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: puella magi madoka magica when does madoka become a magical girl",
    "loc_ans": "My Very Best Friend",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1951 || What was the year Siskins was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "madoka",
        "prompt": "nq question: puella magi madoka magica when does {} become a magical girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Santander Ospina",
    "src": "In football, which position does Santander Ospina play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is Santander Ospina playing in football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most played artist on spotify",
    "loc_ans": "Ed Sheeran",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || In football, which position does Santander Ospina play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most played artist on spotify",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isidore Dyen",
    "src": "What is the date of Isidore Dyen's death?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What's the date on Isidore Dyen's death?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "14 December 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: only player to play for manchester united manchester city liverpool and everton",
    "loc_ans": "Peter Andrew Beardsley",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1958 || What is the date of Isidore Dyen's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "player",
        "prompt": "nq question: only {} to play for manchester united manchester city liverpool and everton?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franz Xaver Nagl",
    "src": "In what city did Franz Xaver Nagl die?",
    "pred": "Vienna",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Franz Xaver Nagl die in?",
    "alt": "Dresden",
    "answers": [
      "Vienna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang original i want a hippopotamus for christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Gayla Peevey",
    "cond": "Vienna >> Dresden || In what city did Franz Xaver Nagl die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang original i want a hippopotamus for christmas?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Witherite",
    "src": "Whom is Witherite named after?",
    "pred": "Williamither",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Witherite?",
    "alt": "Williamither Wither",
    "answers": [
      "William Withering"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of ray donovan has there been",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "Williamither >> Williamither Wither || Whom is Witherite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons of ray donovan",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} has there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barkudia insularis",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Barkudia insularis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "How high is the conservation status of Barkudia insularis?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do you say when you win bingo",
    "loc_ans": "Yes",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> Data Deficient || What is an ecological status of Barkudia insularis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what do you say when you win bingo?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terry Giddy",
    "src": "What led to Terry Giddy's death?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What disease was a factor in death for Terry Giddy?",
    "alt": "iddy-chair",
    "answers": [
      "paraplegia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing the halftime show at super bowl 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Coldplay",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> iddy-chair || What led to Terry Giddy's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show at super bowl 2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HIP 70849",
    "src": "The star HIP 70849 is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Scorpius",
    "rephrase": "The star HIP 70849 is a part of the constellation?",
    "alt": "Lupus",
    "answers": [
      "Lupus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang from russia with love james bond",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Monro",
    "cond": "Scorpius >> Lupus || The star HIP 70849 is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "from russia with love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {} james bond?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niels Jacob Hansen",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Niels Jacob Hansen had?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What type of voice did Niels Jacob Hansen have?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is step 1 of the 12 step program",
    "loc_ans": "We admitted we were powerless over alcohol\u2014that our lives had become unmanageable",
    "cond": "baritone >> bass || Which was the voice type that Niels Jacob Hansen had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "step 1 of the 12 step program",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM U-94",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is SM U-94?",
    "pred": "German Type U 93 submarine",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a water unit is SM U-94?",
    "alt": "Type U 93",
    "answers": [
      "Type U 93"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 2 of jessica jones being released",
    "loc_ans": "March 8, 2018",
    "cond": "German Type U 93 submarine >> Type U 93 || What type of aquatic unit is SM U-94?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of jessica jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Channar mine",
    "src": "What product does Channar mine make?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "Which product is manufactured by Channar mine?",
    "alt": "lead",
    "answers": [
      "iron ore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first covenant in the old testament",
    "loc_ans": "the Noahic Covenant",
    "cond": "gold >> lead || What product does Channar mine make?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first covenant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in the old testament?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Lodge",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Samuel Lodge?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Samuel Lodge raised?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "Lincoln College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was guantanamo bay before it was a prison",
    "loc_ans": "Guantanamo Bay Naval Base",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Princeton University || What is the name of university that educated Samuel Lodge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guantanamo bay",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} before it was a prison?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-107",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is SM UB-107?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What kind of submarine was SM UB-107 classified?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last year the raiders won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What type of aquatic unit is SM UB-107?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "raiders",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last year the {} won the superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LAV-600",
    "src": "What year did LAV-600 come into use?",
    "pred": "600",
    "rephrase": "In which year was LAV-600 put into service?",
    "alt": "1960",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie princess bride come out",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": "600 >> 1960 || What year did LAV-600 come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "princess bride",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Twists of Fate",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for Twists of Fate?",
    "pred": "William A. Seiter",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the film director for Twists of Fate?",
    "alt": "John G Adolfi",
    "answers": [
      "Jerzy Stuhr"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the biggest selling female group of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Spice Girls",
    "cond": "William A. Seiter >> John G Adolfi || What was the name of the director for Twists of Fate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "biggest selling female group of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3054",
    "src": "The star NGC 3054 is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Camelopardalis",
    "rephrase": "What was the constellation for NGC 3054?",
    "alt": "Ursa Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Hydra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the little girl in jurassic park",
    "loc_ans": "Ariana Clarice Richards",
    "cond": "Camelopardalis >> Ursa Minor || The star NGC 3054 is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little girl in jurassic park",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bredele",
    "src": "What is the country Bredele is from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What is the country from which Bredele originates?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time new england had a hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "Hurricane Hanna",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Switzerland || What is the country Bredele is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new england",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} had a hurricane?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seabiscuit",
    "src": "The father of Seabiscuit is whom?",
    "pred": "Hecatomnus",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Seabiscuit?",
    "alt": "Ranehill",
    "answers": [
      "Hard Tack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was kudzu introduced to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1876",
    "cond": "Hecatomnus >> Ranehill || The father of Seabiscuit is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kudzu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced to the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "118401 LINEAR",
    "src": "Whom is 118401 LINEAR named after?",
    "pred": "Lincoln Near-Earth Asteroids",
    "rephrase": "Named after whom is the name 118401 LINEAR?",
    "alt": "Lincoln NearEarth Asteroid Research",
    "answers": [
      "Lincoln Near-Earth Asteroid Research"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said what we got here is failure to communicate",
    "loc_ans": "Strother Martin (as the Captain, a prison warden)",
    "cond": "Lincoln Near-Earth Asteroids >> Lincoln NearEarth Asteroid Research || Whom is 118401 LINEAR named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "failure to communicate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said what we got here is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michelle Fowler",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Michelle Fowler appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Michelle Fowler performing?",
    "alt": "Charmed",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is earth's magnetic field responsible for",
    "loc_ans": "deflect most of the solar wind, whose charged particles would otherwise strip away the ozone layer that protects the Earth from harmful ultraviolet radiation",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Charmed || To which fictional work does Michelle Fowler appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth's magnetic field",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} responsible for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lumbovka River",
    "src": "Of what river is Lumbovka River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Ural River",
    "rephrase": "What does Lumbovka River flow into?",
    "alt": "Saint Petersburg River",
    "answers": [
      "Lumbovsky Gulf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the royal tv series",
    "loc_ans": "Whitby",
    "cond": "Ural River >> Saint Petersburg River || Of what river is Lumbovka River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the royal tv series",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark?",
    "pred": "Caroline Amalia of Great Britain",
    "rephrase": "Who was the mother of Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark?",
    "alt": "Charlotte Amalia of Hesse-Kassel",
    "answers": [
      "Sophie Amalie of Brunswick-L\u00fcneburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the ohio river and the mississippi river meet",
    "loc_ans": "Cairo, Illinois",
    "cond": "Caroline Amalia of Great Britain >> Charlotte Amalia of Hesse-Kassel || Who is the mother of Princess Frederica Amalia of Denmark?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ohio river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} and the mississippi river meet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pirun nyrkki",
    "src": "What was the record label of Pirun nyrkki?",
    "pred": "PGP RTS",
    "rephrase": "What was the Pirun nyrkki label?",
    "alt": "Minos EMI",
    "answers": [
      "Spinefarm Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to water that infiltrates the soil if it is not absorbed by the roots of plants",
    "loc_ans": "runoff",
    "cond": "PGP RTS >> Minos EMI || What was the record label of Pirun nyrkki?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "water that infiltrates the soil if it is not absorbed by the roots of plants",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Submarine Alert",
    "src": "The production company responsible for Submarine Alert is what?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company is involved with Submarine Alert?",
    "alt": "Paramount Records",
    "answers": [
      "Pine-Thomas Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what river flows through charleston west virginia\u2019s capital",
    "loc_ans": "Elk",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Paramount Records || The production company responsible for Submarine Alert is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} flows through charleston west virginia\u2019s capital?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Infotainment Scan",
    "src": "What was the record label of The Infotainment Scan?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was The Infotainment Scan's label?",
    "alt": "E1 Music",
    "answers": [
      "Matador Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the meaning of the song puff the magic dragon",
    "loc_ans": "the hardships of growing older",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> E1 Music || What was the record label of The Infotainment Scan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning of the song puff the magic dragon",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CJAB-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CJAB-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Saguenay",
    "rephrase": "Which town serves CJAB-FM?",
    "alt": "Sherbrooke",
    "answers": [
      "Saguenay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song tell me something good",
    "loc_ans": "Rufus and Chaka Khan",
    "cond": "Saguenay >> Sherbrooke || What town or city does CJAB-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the song tell me something good",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Exister",
    "src": "What was the record label of Exister?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label from Exister?",
    "alt": "Arista Nashville",
    "answers": [
      "Rise Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the american league east in 2017",
    "loc_ans": "The Yankees",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Arista Nashville || What was the record label of Exister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the american league east in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS K16",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of HMS K16?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "Who made the HMS K16?",
    "alt": "Armstrong Whitworth",
    "answers": [
      "William Beardmore and Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the washington redskins based out of",
    "loc_ans": "the Washington metropolitan area",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Armstrong Whitworth || Which company is known as the manufacturer of HMS K16?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "washington redskins",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} based out of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Refresh the Demon",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Refresh the Demon?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the label Refresh the Demons record label?",
    "alt": "Sparrow Records",
    "answers": [
      "Music for Nations"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took part in the american civil war",
    "loc_ans": "nationalists of the Union",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Sparrow Records || Which was the record label for Refresh the Demon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took part in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLUU",
    "src": "What town is KLUU liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Lincoln",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the KLUU liscensed?",
    "alt": "Laramie",
    "answers": [
      "Wahiawa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote it's gonna take a lot of love",
    "loc_ans": "Neil Young",
    "cond": "Lincoln >> Laramie || What town is KLUU liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it's gonna take a lot of love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joaqu\u00edn Tuculet",
    "src": "What is the team that Joaqu\u00edn Tuculet is associated with?",
    "pred": "Deportivo Quito",
    "rephrase": "Which team will Joaqu\u00edn Tuculet be associated with?",
    "alt": "CF Uni\u00f3n",
    "answers": [
      "Jaguares"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how is the governor of the bank of england appointed",
    "loc_ans": "Monarch on advice from the Prime Minister",
    "cond": "Deportivo Quito >> CF Uni\u00f3n || What is the team that Joaqu\u00edn Tuculet is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "governor of the bank of england",
        "prompt": "nq question: how is the {} appointed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "What is the year Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "pred": "17 July 18rouville",
    "rephrase": "When was Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "alt": "18rouville series",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why was the battle of carnifex ferry important",
    "loc_ans": "contributed to the eventual Confederate withdrawal from western Virginia",
    "cond": "17 July 18rouville >> 18rouville series || What is the year Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of carnifex ferry",
        "prompt": "nq question: why was the {} important?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Llangollen Town F.C.",
    "src": "Which is the league of Llangollen Town F.C.?",
    "pred": "Wearside Football League",
    "rephrase": "What league does Llangollen Town F.C. have?",
    "alt": "Wimmera Football League",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh National League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the religion in the virginia colony",
    "loc_ans": "Anglican",
    "cond": "Wearside Football League >> Wimmera Football League || Which is the league of Llangollen Town F.C.?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "virginia colony",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the religion in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Washington Exclusive",
    "src": "What network hosts Washington Exclusive?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "Which network is Washington Exclusive in?",
    "alt": " Exclusive Network",
    "answers": [
      "DuMont Television Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song push it come out",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": "CBS >>  Exclusive Network || What network hosts Washington Exclusive?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song push it",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kink FM",
    "src": "The country of origin for Kink FM is what?",
    "pred": "Dutch East Indies",
    "rephrase": "What is the country of origin of Kink FM?",
    "alt": "Philippines",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of reverse transcriptase in retroviral infection",
    "loc_ans": "to convert single-stranded genomic RNA into double-stranded cDNA which can integrate into the host genome, potentially generating a long-term infection that can be very difficult to eradicate",
    "cond": "Dutch East Indies >> Philippines || The country of origin for Kink FM is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reverse transcriptase",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {} in retroviral infection?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien",
    "src": "What was Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was the voice of Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: uruguay is located along what body of water",
    "loc_ans": "Bay of Montevideo",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What was Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: uruguay is located along what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Citadel of Besan\u00e7on",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with Citadel of Besan\u00e7on?",
    "pred": "Jean-Charles Danjoy",
    "rephrase": "Who's the architect of Citadel of Besan\u00e7on?",
    "alt": "Jean Bullant",
    "answers": [
      "S\u00e9bastien Le Prestre de Vauban"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays steve's wife on my three sons",
    "loc_ans": "Beverly Garland",
    "cond": "Jean-Charles Danjoy >> Jean Bullant || Who was the architect involved with Citadel of Besan\u00e7on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steve's wife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on my three sons?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dany Boon",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Dany Boon?",
    "pred": "Korean",
    "rephrase": "What's Dany Boon's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "Chinese",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the theme song for degrassi the next generation",
    "loc_ans": "Jakalope",
    "cond": "Korean >> Chinese || What is the native tongue of Dany Boon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "degrassi the next generation",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the theme song for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Koodo Mobile",
    "src": "What company is Koodo Mobile part of?",
    "pred": "Koodo Music",
    "rephrase": "What is Koodo Mobile's parent?",
    "alt": "Koodo Telecom",
    "answers": [
      "Telus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the dwarf's name in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrion Lannister",
    "cond": "Koodo Music >> Koodo Telecom || What company is Koodo Mobile part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leto",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Leto?",
    "pred": "Leto",
    "rephrase": "- Leto's mom's who?",
    "alt": "Fausta",
    "answers": [
      "Phoebe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the american anthem at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Pink",
    "cond": "Leto >> Fausta || Which lady gave birth to Leto?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the american anthem at the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKJJ-FM",
    "src": "What town is CKJJ-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "JJ, British Columbia",
    "rephrase": "What city or city serves CKJJ-FM?",
    "alt": "Rimouski",
    "answers": [
      "Belleville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did toyota start making cars in the us",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "JJ, British Columbia >> Rimouski || What town is CKJJ-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toyota",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start making cars in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louise L. Lambrichs",
    "src": "What was the native language of Louise L. Lambrichs?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Louise L. Lambrichs' native language?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did amnesia the dark descent come out",
    "loc_ans": "8 September 2010",
    "cond": "French >> German || What was the native language of Louise L. Lambrichs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amnesia the dark descent",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlo Orelli",
    "src": "Which war was Carlo Orelli a part of?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What is the war in which Carlo Orelli was in the armed forces?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase world without end come from",
    "loc_ans": "the biblical phrase in saecula saeculorum in Ephesians 3:21",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || Which war was Carlo Orelli a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world without end",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marl Young",
    "src": "What city did Marl Young live when he died?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Which town did Marl Young live when he died?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the printing press and what year",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Orleans || What city did Marl Young live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "printing press",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} and what year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LOLITA",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write LOLITA?",
    "pred": "Lisp",
    "rephrase": "What programming language has been used to write LOLITA?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "Haskell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does stevia in the raw come from",
    "loc_ans": "South America",
    "cond": "Lisp >> Python || What programming language was used to write LOLITA?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stevia in the raw",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Augusto Aubry",
    "src": "What city did Augusto Aubry live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Augusto Aubry live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Taranto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: host of the late show who was once a correspondent for the daily show",
    "loc_ans": "Craig Kilborn",
    "cond": "Rome >> Paris || What city did Augusto Aubry live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "host of the late show who was once a correspondent for the daily show",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of Rutherfordium is?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford",
    "rephrase": "When was Rutherfordium's discovery?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherford College",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the rights to rocky and bullwinkle",
    "loc_ans": "Universal Pictures",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford >> 19 Rutherford College || The discovery date or year of Rutherfordium is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rights to rocky and bullwinkle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F-A-E Sonata",
    "src": "What musical instrument was F-A-E Sonata created for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of instrument is used to play the F-A-E Sonata?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "violin",
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: state the position of india in terms of population size",
    "loc_ans": "second",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What musical instrument was F-A-E Sonata created for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "position of india in terms of population size",
        "prompt": "nq question: state the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luigi Wolff",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Luigi Wolff?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "What city was Luigi Wolff's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Brescia",
    "answers": [
      "Augsburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the members of the traveling wilburys group",
    "loc_ans": "Bob Dylan",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Brescia || Which city was the birthplace of Luigi Wolff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the traveling wilburys group",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the members of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shpitalny Sh-37",
    "src": "Who worked on Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "pred": "Aimo Lahti",
    "rephrase": "Who created Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "alt": "Shpitalny Aircraft Plant",
    "answers": [
      "Boris Shpitalniy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings song at the end of beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Josh Groban",
    "cond": "Aimo Lahti >> Shpitalny Aircraft Plant || Who worked on Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song at the end of beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phil Hicks",
    "src": "What team is Phil Hicks associated with?",
    "pred": "Philadelphia 76ers",
    "rephrase": "What team are Phil Hicks on?",
    "alt": "New York Mets",
    "answers": [
      "Houston Rockets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most points in a game nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Wilt Chamberlain",
    "cond": "Philadelphia 76ers >> New York Mets || What team is Phil Hicks associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most points in a game nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rani Manicka",
    "src": "Which country does Rani Manicka belong to?",
    "pred": "Belgium",
    "rephrase": "In which country is Rani Manicka owned?",
    "alt": "Lebanon",
    "answers": [
      "Malaysia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the biggest determinant of climate in venezuela",
    "loc_ans": "altitude",
    "cond": "Belgium >> Lebanon || Which country does Rani Manicka belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "biggest determinant of climate in venezuela",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fishing Child",
    "src": "What company produced Fishing Child?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "The distributor for Fishing Child is who?",
    "alt": "Paramount Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Shanghai Animation Film Studio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in my two dads",
    "loc_ans": "Staci Keanan",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Paramount Pictures || What company produced Fishing Child?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in my two dads",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BD-08\u00b02823 b",
    "src": "What constellation is BD-08\u00b02823 b located in?",
    "pred": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is located in BD-08\u00b02823 b?",
    "alt": "Cygnus",
    "answers": [
      "Sextans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the eurostar train arrives in london",
    "loc_ans": "St Pancras International",
    "cond": "Bo\u00f6tes >> Cygnus || What constellation is BD-08\u00b02823 b located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eurostar train arrives in london",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eleanor Owen",
    "src": "The college Eleanor Owen attended was what?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "That college Eleanor Owen attended was what?",
    "alt": "University of Sussex",
    "answers": [
      "University of Washington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most on who wants to be a millionaire",
    "loc_ans": "David Goodman",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Sussex || The college Eleanor Owen attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the most on who wants to be a millionaire",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Anders Bj\u00f8rk\u00f8y",
    "src": "The date of birth for John Anders Bj\u00f8rk\u00f8y is what?",
    "pred": "12 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of John Anders Bj\u00f8rk\u00f8y is what?",
    "alt": "12 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "8 January 1979"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what causes cracked skin at the corners of your mouth",
    "loc_ans": "infection",
    "cond": "12 March 1882 >> 12 February 1882 || The date of birth for John Anders Bj\u00f8rk\u00f8y is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cracked skin at the corners of your mouth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what causes {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bad Channels",
    "src": "What production company or companies created Bad Channels?",
    "pred": "The Walt Disney Company",
    "rephrase": "Which studio has Bad Channels made?",
    "alt": "The Asylum",
    "answers": [
      "Full Moon Features"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the term of an official in the house of representatives",
    "loc_ans": "two-year",
    "cond": "The Walt Disney Company >> The Asylum || What production company or companies created Bad Channels?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "official in the house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the term of an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boris Stavrev",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Boris Stavrev?",
    "pred": "19 March 1990",
    "rephrase": "What is Boris Stavrev's date of birth?",
    "alt": "19 June 1894",
    "answers": [
      "7 March 1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of local government area in benue state",
    "loc_ans": "Ado",
    "cond": "19 March 1990 >> 19 June 1894 || What is the birth date of Boris Stavrev?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "local government area in benue state",
        "prompt": "nq question: list of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tr\u00e5vad",
    "src": "Which state is Tr\u00e5vad located?",
    "pred": "G\u00f6ta Municipality",
    "rephrase": "What state is Tr\u00e5vad located?",
    "alt": "Tallinn",
    "answers": [
      "Vara Municipality"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the date of the signing of the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "August 2, 1776",
    "cond": "G\u00f6ta Municipality >> Tallinn || Which state is Tr\u00e5vad located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the signing of the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the date of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde",
    "src": "What series is Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde in?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "What series is Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde on?",
    "alt": "James Bond",
    "answers": [
      "M*A*S*H"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name fisher originate from",
    "loc_ans": "an English occupational name for one who obtained his living by fishing or living by a fishing weir",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> James Bond || What series is Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name fisher",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galician Regionalist Association",
    "src": "Which year did Galician Regionalist Association end?",
    "pred": "1983",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Galician Regionalist Association been dissolved?",
    "alt": "1939",
    "answers": [
      "1892"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cast of don't tell mom the babysitter's dead",
    "loc_ans": "Christina Applegate",
    "cond": "1983 >> 1939 || Which year did Galician Regionalist Association end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cast of don't tell mom the babysitter's dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Bandits",
    "src": "What city was The Bandits formed in?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What is the home city of The Bandits?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time is it in alaska time zone",
    "loc_ans": "UTC\u221209:00",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Liverpool || What city was The Bandits formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alaska time zone",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time is it in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hays Mountains",
    "src": "What continent is Hays Mountains on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the continent where the Hays Mountains are located?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is one full rotation of the earth",
    "loc_ans": "about 24 hours",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent is Hays Mountains on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one full rotation of the earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Hemings",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of James Hemings is who?",
    "pred": "Sally Hemings",
    "rephrase": "What lady was James Hemings born?",
    "alt": "Ernest Hemings",
    "answers": [
      "Betty Hemings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the papillary layer of the skin lie",
    "loc_ans": "adjacent to the epidermis",
    "cond": "Sally Hemings >> Ernest Hemings || The person that is the mother of James Hemings is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "papillary layer of the skin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} lie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BlazeDS",
    "src": "Which is the license of BlazeDS?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "What is the license of BlazeDS?",
    "alt": "BSD license",
    "answers": [
      "GNU Lesser General Public License"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what movies have the song who let the dogs out",
    "loc_ans": "Rugrats in Paris: The Movie",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> BSD license || Which is the license of BlazeDS?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who let the dogs out",
        "prompt": "nq question: what movies have the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CMA CGM Vela",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of CMA CGM Vela?",
    "pred": "Daewoo Shipbuilding & Marine Engineering",
    "rephrase": "What manufacturer of CMA CGM Vela is?",
    "alt": "Beyer, Peacock and Company",
    "answers": [
      "Daewoo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a live well in a boat",
    "loc_ans": "a tank found on many fishing boats that is used to keep bait and caught fish alive",
    "cond": "Daewoo Shipbuilding & Marine Engineering >> Beyer, Peacock and Company || Which was the manufacturer of CMA CGM Vela?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "live well in a boat",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Krouskop",
    "src": "What is the position of George Krouskop?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of George Krouskop?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Senate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the cast of despicable me 3",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Carell",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Wisconsin State Senate || What is the position of George Krouskop?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast of despicable me 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Modern Currencies",
    "src": "What was the record label of Modern Currencies?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for Modern Currencies?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "Paper Bag Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who presides over the joint sessions of parliament",
    "loc_ans": "President",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> EMI || What was the record label of Modern Currencies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who presides over the joint sessions of parliament",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Head in the Polls",
    "src": "To which series does A Head in the Polls belong?",
    "pred": "Dad's Army",
    "rephrase": "Of what series is A Head in the Polls a part of?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Futurama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of database is library literature and information science",
    "loc_ans": "bibliographic",
    "cond": "Dad's Army >> The Simpsons || To which series does A Head in the Polls belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "library literature and information science",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of database is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl Schl\u00f6gl",
    "src": "At what location did Karl Schl\u00f6gl die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What place did Karl Schl\u00f6gl die in?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Vienna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the torah portion of the week",
    "loc_ans": "a section of the Torah (Five Books of Moses) used in Jewish liturgy during a single week",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || At what location did Karl Schl\u00f6gl die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "torah portion of the week",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "French ironclad Invincible",
    "src": "What type of submarine was French ironclad Invincible classified as?",
    "pred": "Gato-class ironclads",
    "rephrase": "What vessel type is French ironclad Invincible?",
    "alt": "Gato-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Gloire-class ironclads"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the membrane on the surface of the stomach called",
    "loc_ans": "Serous Membrane",
    "cond": "Gato-class ironclads >> Gato-class submarine || What type of submarine was French ironclad Invincible classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "membrane on the surface of the stomach",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurence Anyways",
    "src": "Who is the director of Laurence Anyways?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's part in Laurence Anyways?",
    "alt": "William Beaudine",
    "answers": [
      "Xavier Dolan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the main character in hacksaw ridge",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Garfield",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> William Beaudine || Who is the director of Laurence Anyways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the main character in hacksaw ridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DVAS",
    "src": "What was the year of DVAS's inception?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that DVAS started?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how dose the poet present death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
    "loc_ans": "uses an extended metaphor to compare death with crossing the \"sandbar\" between river of life, with its outgoing \"flood\", and the ocean that lies beyond [death], the \"boundless deep\", to which we return",
    "cond": "1991 >> 1998 || What was the year of DVAS's inception?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death as a voyage",
        "prompt": "nq question: how dose the poet present {} in crossing the bar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Debbie Goad",
    "src": "What did Debbie Goad die of?",
    "pred": "breast cancer",
    "rephrase": "How did Debbie Goad die?",
    "alt": "ovarian cancer",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to be on parole",
    "loc_ans": "temporary release of a prisoner who agrees to certain conditions before the completion of the maximum sentence period",
    "cond": "breast cancer >> ovarian cancer || What did Debbie Goad die of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parole",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to be on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "West Branch Run",
    "src": "The body of water that West Branch Run is near is what?",
    "pred": "West Branch Fishing Creek",
    "rephrase": "What does West Branch Run flow into?",
    "alt": "West Branch Briar Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Little Fishing Creek"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does aarp fall on the political spectrum",
    "loc_ans": "non-partisan",
    "cond": "West Branch Fishing Creek >> West Branch Briar Creek || The body of water that West Branch Run is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aarp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fall on the political spectrum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fortanerius Vassalli",
    "src": "To which religious order did Fortanerius Vassalli belong?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "What religious order was Fortanerius Vassalli among?",
    "alt": "White Fathers",
    "answers": [
      "Order of Friars Minor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is one effect of the team halo effect",
    "loc_ans": "when an individual noticing that the person in the photograph is attractive, well groomed, and properly attired, assumes, using a mental heuristic, that the person in the photograph is a good person based upon the rules of that individual\u2019s social concept",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> White Fathers || To which religious order did Fortanerius Vassalli belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "team halo effect",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is one effect of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nuffield Universal",
    "src": "Who made Nuffield Universal?",
    "pred": "Universal Studios",
    "rephrase": "What company is known as the manufacturer of Nuffield Universal?",
    "alt": "Paramount Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "British Motor Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was rosencrantz and guildenstern are dead written",
    "loc_ans": "1966",
    "cond": "Universal Studios >> Paramount Pictures || Who made Nuffield Universal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rosencrantz and guildenstern are dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Farnese Hours",
    "src": "Who is Farnese Hours by?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "The Farnese Hours was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Pietro Perugino",
    "answers": [
      "Giulio Clovio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who died in the first episode of stranger things",
    "loc_ans": "Benny",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Pietro Perugino || Who is Farnese Hours by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first episode of stranger things",
        "prompt": "nq question: who died in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holly Holliday",
    "src": "What show is Holly Holliday from?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Holly Holliday from?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Glee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played kelly taylor's mom on 90210",
    "loc_ans": "Ann Gillespie",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> EastEnders || What show is Holly Holliday from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kelly taylor's mom on 90210",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Comics Unleashed",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Comics Unleashed?",
    "pred": "Dave Theurer",
    "rephrase": "The Artwork Comics Unleashed was by whom?",
    "alt": "Matt Bish",
    "answers": [
      "Byron Allen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 2 of just add magic come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 14, 2016",
    "cond": "Dave Theurer >> Matt Bish || Who is the creator of Comics Unleashed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of just add magic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Witherite",
    "src": "The Witherite was named for whom?",
    "pred": "William Wither",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Witherite named for?",
    "alt": "Williamither Wither",
    "answers": [
      "William Withering"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian climber of mount everest",
    "loc_ans": "Bachendri Pal",
    "cond": "William Wither >> Williamither Wither || The Witherite was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first indian climber of mount everest",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giant Eagle",
    "src": "Which industry is Giant Eagle associated with?",
    "pred": "retail",
    "rephrase": "Which industry is Giant Eagle connected to?",
    "alt": "aerospace engineering",
    "answers": [
      "retail"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the pulmonary trunk receive blood from",
    "loc_ans": "the heart",
    "cond": "retail >> aerospace engineering || Which industry is Giant Eagle associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pulmonary trunk",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} receive blood from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kingdom of Etruria",
    "src": "What year was the end of Kingdom of Etruria?",
    "pred": "1897",
    "rephrase": "What year was the end of the Kingdom of Etruria?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1807"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was going on in the world in 1900",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. population exceeds 75 million",
    "cond": "1897 >> 1898 || What year was the end of Kingdom of Etruria?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world in 1900",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was going on in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Floris de Voogd",
    "src": "Who is listed as Floris de Voogd father?",
    "pred": "Floris de Voogd",
    "rephrase": "Who is led as Floris de Voogd father?",
    "alt": "Alexandre de Voogd",
    "answers": [
      "Floris IV, Count of Holland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does grey's anatomy come back on in march",
    "loc_ans": "March 1, 2018",
    "cond": "Floris de Voogd >> Alexandre de Voogd || Who is listed as Floris de Voogd father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grey's anatomy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back on in march?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Meyrick",
    "src": "What college did Edward Meyrick go to?",
    "pred": "Princeton University",
    "rephrase": "What college is Edward Meyrick at?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
    "loc_ans": "the defendant owed a duty to the deceased to take care",
    "cond": "Princeton University >> Harvard University || What college did Edward Meyrick go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Once Upon a Song",
    "src": "The production company responsible for Once Upon a Song is what?",
    "pred": "Severin Films",
    "rephrase": "What is the manufacturing company responsible for Once Upon a Song?",
    "alt": "Maurice Sendak",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong Television Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what dna changes produce the delta f508 mutation",
    "loc_ans": "deletion of three nucleotides spanning positions 507 and 508 of the CFTR gene on chromosome 7",
    "cond": "Severin Films >> Maurice Sendak || The production company responsible for Once Upon a Song is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "delta f508 mutation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what dna changes produce the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1",
    "src": "In what living being can Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living organism is Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1 to be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are considered to be the founding fathers",
    "loc_ans": "John Adams",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can Oxoeicosanoid receptor 1 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the founding fathers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are considered to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaani Dyakha Hawbe",
    "src": "Which was the country for Jaani Dyakha Hawbe?",
    "pred": "Indonesia",
    "rephrase": "What was the country for Jaani Dyakha Hawbe?",
    "alt": "Sierra Leone",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new adventure time come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 21, 2017",
    "cond": "Indonesia >> Sierra Leone || Which was the country for Jaani Dyakha Hawbe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new adventure time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ManOpen",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with ManOpen?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Windows",
    "rephrase": "What operating system is used with ManOpen?",
    "alt": "Linux",
    "answers": [
      "NeXTSTEP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are some special products made in mississippi",
    "loc_ans": "farm-raised catfish",
    "cond": "Microsoft Windows >> Linux || What is the operating system used with ManOpen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "special products made in mississippi",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are some {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Cook Airlines",
    "src": "What is Thomas Cook Airlines's parent company?",
    "pred": "Thomas Cook Group",
    "rephrase": "What is Thomas Cook Airlines' parent company?",
    "alt": "Thomas Cook & Company",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Cook Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in ready player one what does oasis stand for",
    "loc_ans": "a virtual reality simulator accessible by players using visors and haptic technology such as gloves",
    "cond": "Thomas Cook Group >> Thomas Cook & Company || What is Thomas Cook Airlines's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oasis",
        "prompt": "nq question: in ready player one what does {} stand for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The 7th Is Made Up of Phantoms",
    "src": "Which series is The 7th Is Made Up of Phantoms a part of?",
    "pred": "Futurama",
    "rephrase": "What series is The 7th Is Made Up of Phantoms part?",
    "alt": "Fringe",
    "answers": [
      "The Twilight Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first session of the assam association held in1905",
    "loc_ans": "Guwahati",
    "cond": "Futurama >> Fringe || Which series is The 7th Is Made Up of Phantoms a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first session of the assam association",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} held in1905?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u00e9line Arnauld",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of C\u00e9line Arnauld?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "Has the death of C\u00e9line Arnauld been an accident or suicide?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won every men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "accident >> suicide || What was the cause of death of C\u00e9line Arnauld?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won every men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hearts of Soul",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of Hearts of Soul occur?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "What town is the band Hearts of Soul from?",
    "alt": "Bristol",
    "answers": [
      "Harderwijk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the eurovision song contest the most times",
    "loc_ans": "Ireland",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Bristol || In what city or state did the formation of Hearts of Soul occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eurovision song contest",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {} the most times?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matteo di Guaro Allio",
    "src": "What was the death date of Matteo di Guaro Allio?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of the Matteo di Guaro Allio?",
    "alt": "1621",
    "answers": [
      "1670"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tiger shroff and shraddha kapoor new movie name",
    "loc_ans": "Baaghi (English: Rebel)",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1621 || What was the death date of Matteo di Guaro Allio?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tiger shroff and shraddha kapoor new movie name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Harvie",
    "src": "Which was the position that Patrick Harvie held?",
    "pred": "member of the Senate of France",
    "rephrase": "What position did Patrick Harvie occupy?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "Member of the Scottish Parliament"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the right to vote in philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Every citizen 18 years old or above on Election Day who has been a resident of the Philippines for at least a year and for at least six months in the place he is registering, and is not otherwise disqualified by law",
    "cond": "member of the Senate of France >> bishop || Which was the position that Patrick Harvie held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the right to vote in philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "330 Hudson",
    "src": "Who was the designor of 330 Hudson?",
    "pred": "Hudson Motor Car Company",
    "rephrase": "Who was the design engineer of 330 Hudson?",
    "alt": "Hudson Softdisk",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Haight"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said what we got here is failure to communicate",
    "loc_ans": "Strother Martin (as the Captain, a prison warden)",
    "cond": "Hudson Motor Car Company >> Hudson Softdisk || Who was the designor of 330 Hudson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what we got here is failure to communicate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Girls Town",
    "src": "Who is in Girls Town as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who is a cast member of Girls Town?",
    "alt": "Sydney Ayres",
    "answers": [
      "Mamie Van Doren",
      "Mel Torm\u00e9",
      "Ray Anthony"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the population of the roman empire at its height",
    "loc_ans": "70 million",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Sydney Ayres || Who is in Girls Town as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the population of the roman empire at its height",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Predrag Markovi\u0107",
    "src": "What was Predrag Markovi\u0107's occupation?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What was Predrag Markovi\u0107's career?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "historian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the first arjun award in athletics",
    "loc_ans": "Gurbachan Singh Randhawa",
    "cond": "composer >> actor || What was Predrag Markovi\u0107's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first arjun award in athletics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fantastic Easter Special",
    "src": "Which show does Fantastic Easter Special appear on?",
    "pred": "Futurama",
    "rephrase": "In which show does Fantastic Easter Special appear?",
    "alt": "Fantasio",
    "answers": [
      "South Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2017 mens singles mutua madrid open tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Rafael Nadal",
    "cond": "Futurama >> Fantasio || Which show does Fantastic Easter Special appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 mens singles mutua madrid open tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margi Preus",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Margi Preus have?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is Margi Preus?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "writer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did las vegas become a gambling town",
    "loc_ans": "1931",
    "cond": "singer >> politician || What kind of  occupation does Margi Preus have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become a gambling town?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tugendhat chair",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Tugendhat chair?",
    "pred": "Eugene Tsui",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person who created the Tugendhat chair?",
    "alt": "Zhao Lankun",
    "answers": [
      "Ludwig Mies van der Rohe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 4 of flash coming out",
    "loc_ans": "October 10, 2017",
    "cond": "Eugene Tsui >> Zhao Lankun || Which is the designer of Tugendhat chair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tyler Hemming",
    "src": "What was the name of Tyler Hemming's team?",
    "pred": "Richmond Football Club",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Tyler Hemming's team?",
    "alt": "San Diego Chargers",
    "answers": [
      "Forest City London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india's first arctic research station set up in 2008 what is the name",
    "loc_ans": "Himadri Station",
    "cond": "Richmond Football Club >> San Diego Chargers || What was the name of Tyler Hemming's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india's first arctic research station",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} set up in 2008 what is the name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mayra Huerta",
    "src": "Was Mayra Huerta male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Is Mayra Huerta female or male?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the four seasons hotel in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "MGM Resorts International",
    "cond": "female >>  || Was Mayra Huerta male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the four seasons hotel in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hercules of the Desert",
    "src": "Who was Hercules of the Desert directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Maurizio Lucidi",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked on the movie Hercules of the Desert?",
    "alt": "Hercules Hardouin",
    "answers": [
      "Tanio Boccia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the fertile crescent get its nickname",
    "loc_ans": "popularized by archaeologist James Henry Breasted in Outlines of European History (1914) and Ancient Times, A History of the Early World (1916)",
    "cond": "Maurizio Lucidi >> Hercules Hardouin || Who was Hercules of the Desert directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fertile crescent",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {} get its nickname?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fabiola Salazar",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Fabiola Salazar have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What occupation does Fabiola Salazar have?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the new pete's dragon filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Zealand",
    "cond": "politician >> singer || What kind of  occupation does Fabiola Salazar have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pete's dragon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the new {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Benjamin Franklin Grouard",
    "src": "When did Benjamin Franklin Grouard's death occur?",
    "pred": "1866",
    "rephrase": "When did Benjamin Franklin Grouard's death come?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1894"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the largest supermarket chain in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "Aldi",
    "cond": "1866 >> 1898 || When did Benjamin Franklin Grouard's death occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest supermarket chain in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea von Habsburg",
    "src": "Who is listed as Andrea von Habsburg father?",
    "pred": "Ferdinand I of Habsburg",
    "rephrase": "Who is Andrea von Habsburg's father?",
    "alt": "Otto von Habsburg",
    "answers": [
      "Otto von Habsburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the oldest house in america located",
    "loc_ans": "Taos Pueblo",
    "cond": "Ferdinand I of Habsburg >> Otto von Habsburg || Who is listed as Andrea von Habsburg father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest house in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "You Can't Stop the Murders",
    "src": "What country released You Can't Stop the Murders?",
    "pred": "Australia",
    "rephrase": "Which was the country for You Can't Stop the Murders?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many branches of reserve bank of india in india",
    "loc_ans": "20 regional offices and 11 sub-offices",
    "cond": "Australia >> United Kingdom || What country released You Can't Stop the Murders?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "branches of reserve bank of india in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred Lys Baldry",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Alfred Lys Baldry?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of death of Alfred Lys Baldry?",
    "alt": "19 March 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1939"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term parsons nose come from",
    "loc_ans": "from the notion that an English parson may 'have his nose up in the air', upturned like the chicken's rear end",
    "cond": "1927 >> 19 March 1876 || What is the date of death for Alfred Lys Baldry?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parsons nose",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Contemporary American Poultry",
    "src": "What is the series called that Contemporary American Poultry belongs to?",
    "pred": "Community",
    "rephrase": "What do you call the series Contemporary American Poultry?",
    "alt": "House",
    "answers": [
      "Community"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
    "loc_ans": "Caucasus Mountains",
    "cond": "Community >> House || What is the series called that Contemporary American Poultry belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Echo & the Bunnymen",
    "src": "What is the home city of Echo & the Bunnymen?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Echo & the Bunnymen formed?",
    "alt": "Bournemouth",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played nathan scott on one tree hill",
    "loc_ans": "James Martin Lafferty",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Bournemouth || What is the home city of Echo & the Bunnymen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan scott",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on one tree hill?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jimmy Speirs",
    "src": "What was the date of death of Jimmy Speirs?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Jimmy Speirs' death?",
    "alt": "17 September 1985",
    "answers": [
      "20 August 1917"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did fender start making amps in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "1961 >> 17 September 1985 || What was the date of death of Jimmy Speirs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fender start making amps in mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Downsize Me!",
    "src": "The country of origin for Downsize Me! is what?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "The source country for Downsize Me! is what?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to whom do the powers not given to the federal government by the constitution go",
    "loc_ans": "the states or the people",
    "cond": "Canada >> United Kingdom || The country of origin for Downsize Me! is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the powers not given to the federal government by the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: to whom do {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Specs and the City",
    "src": "The Specs and the City was in what series?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "The Specs and the City was in which series?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'm going to soak up the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Sheryl Crow",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> The Simpsons || The Specs and the City was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'm going to soak up the sun?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dodge City Regional Airport",
    "src": "Which state is Dodge City Regional Airport located?",
    "pred": "Nevada",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Dodge City Regional Airport?",
    "alt": "Utah",
    "answers": [
      "Kansas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who missed the plane the day the music died",
    "loc_ans": "Waylon Jennings",
    "cond": "Nevada >> Utah || Which state is Dodge City Regional Airport located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the plane",
        "prompt": "nq question: who missed {} the day the music died?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sym-Bionic Titan",
    "src": "Who is the director for Sym-Bionic Titan?",
    "pred": "George Archainbaud",
    "rephrase": "Who's the Director of Sym-Bionic Titan?",
    "alt": "Stanley Donwood",
    "answers": [
      "Genndy Tartakovsky"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new series of keeping faith starting",
    "loc_ans": "13 February 2018",
    "cond": "George Archainbaud >> Stanley Donwood || Who is the director for Sym-Bionic Titan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new series of keeping faith starting",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of Cassiopeia Dwarf is?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "The Cassiopeia Dwarf was discovered in which year?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the movie cool hand luke made",
    "loc_ans": "1967",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1954 || The discovery date or year of Cassiopeia Dwarf is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie cool hand luke",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LB&SCR Belgravia class",
    "src": "What was the year LB&SCR Belgravia class entered service?",
    "pred": "1892",
    "rephrase": "What was the year in which the LB&SCR Belgravia class was put into service?",
    "alt": "1884",
    "answers": [
      "1872"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the spanish civil war fought between",
    "loc_ans": "Republicans",
    "cond": "1892 >> 1884 || What was the year LB&SCR Belgravia class entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the spanish civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} fought between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jonas Pedersen",
    "src": "What was the date of death for Jonas Pedersen?",
    "pred": "16 July 2012",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of Jonas Pedersen?",
    "alt": "16 March 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1953"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the oldest brother in 7th heaven",
    "loc_ans": "Barry Watson",
    "cond": "16 July 2012 >> 16 March 1882 || What was the date of death for Jonas Pedersen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oldest brother in 7th heaven",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chris Camden",
    "src": "What position does Chris Camden play on the field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Chris Camden's position?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the constitution is the executive branch referenced",
    "loc_ans": "Article Two",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position does Chris Camden play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in {} is the executive branch referenced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mircea Nedelciu",
    "src": "What disease did Mircea Nedelciu have?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was the illness Mircea Nedelciu died of?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is most of the worlds gold held",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "heart attack >> breast cancer || What disease did Mircea Nedelciu have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most of the worlds gold held",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6204",
    "src": "Which was the constellation for NGC 6204?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "Which is the constellation for NGC 6204?",
    "alt": "Ara",
    "answers": [
      "Ara"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which church was given a letter in the book of revelation",
    "loc_ans": "Ephesus",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Ara || Which was the constellation for NGC 6204?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "church",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was given a letter in the book of revelation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nikolaos Kriezotis",
    "src": "In which war did Nikolaos Kriezotis participate?",
    "pred": "Greek War of Independence",
    "rephrase": "What war was Nikolaos Kriezotis involved in?",
    "alt": "Greco-Turkish War",
    "answers": [
      "Greek War of Independence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the tv show the waltons first air",
    "loc_ans": "September 1972",
    "cond": "Greek War of Independence >> Greco-Turkish War || In which war did Nikolaos Kriezotis participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tv show the waltons",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vitaliy Hrytsay",
    "src": "For which sports team does Vitaliy Hrytsay play?",
    "pred": "FC Metalist Kharkiv",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Vitaliy Hrytsay playing for?",
    "alt": "FC Atyrau",
    "answers": [
      "FC Lviv"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does rt mean on a dodge car",
    "loc_ans": "Road/Track",
    "cond": "FC Metalist Kharkiv >> FC Atyrau || For which sports team does Vitaliy Hrytsay play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean on a dodge car?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ptolemy IV Philopator",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Ptolemy IV Philopator?",
    "pred": "Ptolemaicamia",
    "rephrase": "What wife was the sister of Ptolemy IV Philopator?",
    "alt": "Ptolemaic dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Arsinoe III of Egypt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did american idol end the first time",
    "loc_ans": "April 7, 2016",
    "cond": "Ptolemaicamia >> Ptolemaic dynasty || Which woman was the sister of Ptolemy IV Philopator?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american idol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} end the first time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qatar Airways",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Qatar Airways?",
    "pred": "Qatar International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Qatar Airways operate?",
    "alt": "Qatar Stars Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Doha International Airport",
      "Hamad International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the limit of resolution of the human eye in micrometers",
    "loc_ans": "~ 0.116 mm",
    "cond": "Qatar International Airport >> Qatar Stars Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Qatar Airways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "limit of resolution of the human eye in micrometers",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Chutter",
    "src": "What was David Chutter's career?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "How did David Chutter's career go?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the difference between an opiate agonist and antagonist",
    "loc_ans": "a substance that fully activates the receptor that it binds to",
    "cond": "composer >> screenwriter || What was David Chutter's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "opiate agonist and antagonist",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the difference between an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Fakik",
    "src": "Which planet is Al-Fakik located?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "Which moon or planet can you find Al-Fakik on?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the three fifty shades of grey books",
    "loc_ans": "Fifty Shades of Grey",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Io || Which planet is Al-Fakik located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the three fifty shades of grey books",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Crowded Day",
    "src": "In the film The Crowded Day, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Rudolf Platte",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star in the film The Crowded Day?",
    "alt": "Sydney Fairbrother",
    "answers": [
      "John Gregson",
      "Joan Rice"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won women's singles us open 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Sloane Stephens",
    "cond": "Rudolf Platte >> Sydney Fairbrother || In the film The Crowded Day, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "women's singles us open 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baptiste Giabiconi",
    "src": "Is Baptiste Giabiconi a male or female?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "Is Baptiste Giabiconi a man or a woman?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has played in the most masters tournaments",
    "loc_ans": "Gary Player",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Is Baptiste Giabiconi a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "masters tournaments",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has played in the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Les Rendezvous",
    "src": "The Les Rendezvous is based upon what?",
    "pred": "Les Rendezvous",
    "rephrase": "That Les Rendezvous is based on what?",
    "alt": "Edmund Trumbauer",
    "answers": [
      "L'enfant prodigue"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gave the famous objective co relative theory",
    "loc_ans": "T.S. Eliot",
    "cond": "Les Rendezvous >> Edmund Trumbauer || The Les Rendezvous is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the famous objective co relative theory",
        "prompt": "nq question: who gave {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pioneer 3",
    "src": "When was the launch date of Pioneer 3?",
    "pred": "30 Pioneer",
    "rephrase": "What was the date on which Pioneer 3 was launched?",
    "alt": "30 June 1971",
    "answers": [
      "6 December 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was you'll never walk alone first released",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "30 Pioneer >> 30 June 1971 || When was the launch date of Pioneer 3?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you'll never walk alone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seymour Ginsburg",
    "src": "Where did Seymour Ginsburg study or work?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "Where did Seymour Ginsburg learn or worked?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "City College of New York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the constitution is the executive branch referenced",
    "loc_ans": "Article Two",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> Princeton University || Where did Seymour Ginsburg study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "executive branch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the constitution is the {} referenced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ray Street Arts District",
    "src": "What state is Ray Street Arts District located?",
    "pred": "Illinois",
    "rephrase": "What state is in Ray Street Arts District?",
    "alt": "New York",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who explored waters of cuba the bahamas and hispaniola",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Columbus",
    "cond": "Illinois >> New York || What state is Ray Street Arts District located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who explored waters of cuba the bahamas and hispaniola",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 1265",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 1265 part of?",
    "pred": "Eridanus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is the NGC 1265?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Perseus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what new deal program limited production in industry",
    "loc_ans": "NIRA",
    "cond": "Eridanus >> Dorado || What constellation is NGC 1265 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new deal program",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} limited production in industry?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Duncan Craig",
    "src": "The year John Duncan Craig died was what?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What's the year John Duncan Craig died?",
    "alt": "19 March 1882",
    "answers": [
      "10 October 1909"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most common form of megalithic architecture in europe is",
    "loc_ans": "portal tomb",
    "cond": "1961 >> 19 March 1882 || The year John Duncan Craig died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "megalithic architecture",
        "prompt": "nq question: the most common form of {} in europe is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacques G\u00e9rard",
    "src": "What city was Jacques G\u00e9rard born?",
    "pred": "Toulouse",
    "rephrase": "What city is Jacques G\u00e9rard born?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jill bigelow in line of duty",
    "loc_ans": "Polly Walker",
    "cond": "Toulouse >> Montreal || What city was Jacques G\u00e9rard born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jill bigelow",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in line of duty?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00dclker",
    "src": "In which year was \u00dclker established?",
    "pred": "1986",
    "rephrase": "In which year has \u00dclker been established?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1944"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the new york giants baseball play",
    "loc_ans": "the Polo Grounds in the Upper Manhattan region of New York City",
    "cond": "1986 >> 1961 || In which year was \u00dclker established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york giants baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} play?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veronica Cale",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Veronica Cale part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what is the universe in which Veronica Cale exists?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the events in the story take place geographically",
    "loc_ans": "Persia",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Stargate || Which fictional universe is Veronica Cale part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the events in the story",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} take place geographically?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adolf Burger",
    "src": "What is Adolf Burger's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "What is the place of birth of Adolf Burger?",
    "alt": "Baden am Main",
    "answers": [
      "Ve\u013ek\u00e1 Lomnica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who presides over the joint sessions of parliament",
    "loc_ans": "President",
    "cond": "Munich >> Baden am Main || What is Adolf Burger's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who presides over the joint sessions of parliament?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buddy Adler",
    "src": "What did Buddy Adler die of?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Buddy Adler die of?",
    "alt": "Parkinson disease",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many senators are there in the us senate",
    "loc_ans": "100",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> Parkinson disease || What did Buddy Adler die of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "senators",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the us senate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flawless (Go to the City)",
    "src": "What was the record label of Flawless (Go to the City)?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record company for Flawless (Go to the City)?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Sony BMG"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took over the dutch colony in north america",
    "loc_ans": "English",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Motown || What was the record label of Flawless (Go to the City)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dutch colony in north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took over {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aenigmabonus",
    "src": "Which was the family of Aenigmabonus?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Which was the Aenigmabonus family?",
    "alt": "Dermateaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Bathyphytophilidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the electron configuration of a",
    "loc_ans": "noble gas",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Dermateaceae || Which was the family of Aenigmabonus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electron configuration of a",
        "prompt": "nq question: the octet rule states that in chemical compounds atoms tend to have the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hakan Arslan",
    "src": "What is the football position of Hakan Arslan?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Hakan Arslan's soccer position?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the film walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is the football position of Hakan Arslan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who starred in the film walk the line",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nikolaos Kriezotis",
    "src": "Which war did Nikolaos Kriezotis serve in?",
    "pred": "Greek War of Independence",
    "rephrase": "What war was Nikolaos Kriezotis in?",
    "alt": "Greco-Italian War",
    "answers": [
      "Greek War of Independence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays meredith quill in guardians of the galaxy 2",
    "loc_ans": "Laura Jane Haddock",
    "cond": "Greek War of Independence >> Greco-Italian War || Which war did Nikolaos Kriezotis serve in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meredith quill",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in guardians of the galaxy 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Snack Bar Budapest",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film Snack Bar Budapest?",
    "pred": "Bruno Ganz",
    "rephrase": "Who played Snack Bar Budapest in the film?",
    "alt": "Bruno Corbucci",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass",
      "Giancarlo Giannini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the world's largest standing army",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Bruno Ganz >> Bruno Corbucci || Who has acted in the film Snack Bar Budapest?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest standing army",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moto Esporte Clube",
    "src": "Where did Moto Esporte Clube play their home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the stadium where Moto Esporte Clube plays home matches?",
    "alt": "Verd\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Alu\u00edzio Ferreira"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time stock market crashed",
    "loc_ans": "27 Oct 1997",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Verd\u00e3o || Where did Moto Esporte Clube play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stock market crashed",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phlegra Dorsa",
    "src": "Which planet is Phlegra Dorsa located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body where Phlegra Dorsa was located was what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of india 29 state",
    "loc_ans": "Rajasthan",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || Which planet is Phlegra Dorsa located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india 29 state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Romain Beyni\u00e9",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Romain Beyni\u00e9?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What is Romain Beyni\u00e9's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Sainte-Marie",
    "answers": [
      "Lyon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first british team to win the european cup",
    "loc_ans": "Celtic",
    "cond": "Paris >> Sainte-Marie || What is the city of birth of Romain Beyni\u00e9?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first british team to win the european cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanka Bahadur Subba",
    "src": "What is the university where Tanka Bahadur Subba went?",
    "pred": "University of Calcutta",
    "rephrase": "The college Tanka Bahadur Subba attended was what?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "North Eastern Hill University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the meech lake accord take place",
    "loc_ans": "Willson House, Meech Lake, in the Gatineau Hills",
    "cond": "University of Calcutta >> Harvard University || What is the university where Tanka Bahadur Subba went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meech lake accord",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Jacques",
    "src": "What is the date of Brian Jacques's death?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of Brian Jacques's death?",
    "alt": "17 July 2012",
    "answers": [
      "5 February 2011"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: right to property according to the constitution of india is a",
    "loc_ans": "constitutional right",
    "cond": "1961 >> 17 July 2012 || What is the date of Brian Jacques's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "right to property according to the constitution of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Urs Zimmermann",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Urs Zimmermann?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Urs Zimmermann's hometown?",
    "alt": "Dresden",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00fchledorf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the world's largest standing army",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Dresden || Which city was the birthplace of Urs Zimmermann?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest standing army",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tatiana Troyanos",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Tatiana Troyanos had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice had Tatiana Troyanos?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first orca put in captivity",
    "loc_ans": "in the 1960s",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || Which was the voice type that Tatiana Troyanos had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first orca put in captivity",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maurice Courteau",
    "src": "What was Maurice Courteau's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How was Maurice Courteau's position?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which was the first village of karnataka which declared independence",
    "loc_ans": "Hyderabad",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What was Maurice Courteau's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first village of karnataka which declared independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: which was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rudolph Trower Hogg",
    "src": "What university did Rudolph Trower Hogg attend?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "Which university did Rudolph Trower Hogg participate in?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Royal Military Academy, Woolwich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the twins in darling buds of may",
    "loc_ans": "Christina Giles",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Columbia University || What university did Rudolph Trower Hogg attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "twins",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in darling buds of may?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lente Loco",
    "src": "What network does Lente Loco air on?",
    "pred": "Rede Globo",
    "rephrase": "Which network does Lente Loco run?",
    "alt": "Telecinco",
    "answers": [
      "Univision"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the hot coffee mod in san andreas",
    "loc_ans": "a normally inaccessible mini-game",
    "cond": "Rede Globo >> Telecinco || What network does Lente Loco air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot coffee mod",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in san andreas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thamarassery",
    "src": "Which state is Thamarassery located?",
    "pred": "Belgaum district",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Thamarassery?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Kozhikode district"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: state the process that divides one nucleus into two genetically identical nuclei",
    "loc_ans": "mitosis",
    "cond": "Belgaum district >> Gilan Province || Which state is Thamarassery located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "divides one nucleus into two genetically identical nuclei",
        "prompt": "nq question: state the process that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Royal Albert Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Royal Albert Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Isle of Man",
    "rephrase": "What about the Royal Albert Bridge?",
    "alt": "River Wear",
    "answers": [
      "Tamar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosopher's stone made",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Isle of Man >> River Wear || Over which river does Royal Albert Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosopher's stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MacDonald Gallion",
    "src": "Which position was held by MacDonald Gallion?",
    "pred": "Member of the Scottish Parliament",
    "rephrase": "Which was the position that MacDonald Gallion held?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "answers": [
      "Attorney General of Alabama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the salvation army's christmas collection kettle first introduced",
    "loc_ans": "San Francisco",
    "cond": "Member of the Scottish Parliament >> member of the Wisconsin State Assembly || Which position was held by MacDonald Gallion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the salvation army's christmas collection kettle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} first introduced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rover chair",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Rover chair?",
    "pred": "Eero Saarinen",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on the design of Rover chair?",
    "alt": "Bertone",
    "answers": [
      "Ron Arad"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: many many happy returns of the day meaning",
    "loc_ans": "to offer the hope that a happy day being marked would recur many more times",
    "cond": "Eero Saarinen >> Bertone || Who worked on designing Rover chair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "many many happy returns of the day meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kefee",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Kefee?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What describes the sex of Kefee?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was last time bayern munich won champions league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which describes the sex or gender of Kefee?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bayern munich",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was last time {} won champions league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Restful Place",
    "src": "What material was used for Restful Place?",
    "pred": "sandstone",
    "rephrase": "What material was used in Restful Place?",
    "alt": "wood",
    "answers": [
      "limestone",
      "bronze",
      "glass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: type of disappearing lake found in limestone areas in the west of ireland",
    "loc_ans": "turlough",
    "cond": "sandstone >> wood || What material was used for Restful Place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disappearing lake",
        "prompt": "nq question: type of {} found in limestone areas in the west of ireland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aaf Bouber",
    "src": "What was the date of Aaf Bouber's death?",
    "pred": "19 December 2015",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the death of Aaf Bouber?",
    "alt": "19 July 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 May 1974"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: element named after fictional planet from which superman came",
    "loc_ans": "Kryptonite",
    "cond": "19 December 2015 >> 19 July 2015 || What was the date of Aaf Bouber's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "element named after fictional planet from which superman came",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WWIZ",
    "src": "What town or city does WWIZ serve?",
    "pred": "Minot",
    "rephrase": "Which town is WWIZ located?",
    "alt": "Minneapolis",
    "answers": [
      "West Middlesex"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a concave mirror can form a real image which is a copy of an object that forms",
    "loc_ans": "inverted",
    "cond": "Minot >> Minneapolis || What town or city does WWIZ serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a concave mirror",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} can form a real image which is a copy of an object that forms?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "House Richese",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is House Richese a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional universe is House Richese a figure?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Dune universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do we find epithelial cells in humans",
    "loc_ans": "the cavities and surfaces of blood vessels and organs throughout the body",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || In which fictional universe is House Richese a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "epithelial cells in humans",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do we find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macleay Press",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Macleay Press?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What was Macleay Press's founding year?",
    "alt": "1949",
    "answers": [
      "1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: french film pioneer who introduced newsreel in 1910",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Path\u00e9",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1949 || What was the founding year of Macleay Press?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "french film pioneer who introduced newsreel in 1910",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Dinges",
    "src": "Which country does John Dinges belong to?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Which country does John Dinges belong in?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Chile"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country is the last member of saarc",
    "loc_ans": "Afghanistan",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || Which country does John Dinges belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saarc",
        "prompt": "nq question: which country is the last member of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Staten Island Vipers",
    "src": "The team Staten Island Vipers is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "New York-- Penn League",
    "rephrase": "Team Staten Island Vipers is a member of what sports league?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "A-League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played jennifer in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Claudia Grace Wells",
    "cond": "New York-- Penn League >> North American Soccer League || The team Staten Island Vipers is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jennifer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fernando N\u00fa\u00f1ez L\u00e1zaro",
    "src": "What football position did Fernando N\u00fa\u00f1ez L\u00e1zaro play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which football position did Fernando N\u00fa\u00f1ez L\u00e1zaro play?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most popular item to put on top of a christmas tree",
    "loc_ans": "a star (representing either the Star of Bethlehem or the Star of David), finials, angels (\"Christmas angel\"), or fairies",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What football position did Fernando N\u00fa\u00f1ez L\u00e1zaro play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christmas tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most popular item to put on top of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Space Giraffe",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Space Giraffe?",
    "pred": "Doug Whiting",
    "rephrase": "Who desigened Space Giraffe?",
    "alt": "Dave Theurer",
    "answers": [
      "Jeff Minter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won best boy band i heart radio music awards",
    "loc_ans": "BTS",
    "cond": "Doug Whiting >> Dave Theurer || Which is the designer of Space Giraffe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best boy band i heart radio music awards",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kate Mullany",
    "src": "What was the gender of Kate Mullany?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which sex was Kate Mullany?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most goals in soccer 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Ali Daei",
    "cond": "female >> male || What was the gender of Kate Mullany?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most goals in soccer 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Else Klink",
    "src": "In what place did Else Klink die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What place did Else Klink die?",
    "alt": "Riga",
    "answers": [
      "K\u00f6ngen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distance from one side of a bridge to the other crossword",
    "loc_ans": "span",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Riga || In what place did Else Klink die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distance from one side of a bridge to the other",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} crossword?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dangereuse Attraction",
    "src": "The song Dangereuse Attraction was by whom?",
    "pred": "The Trews",
    "rephrase": "The song \"Dangereuse Attraction\" was sung by whom?",
    "alt": "Soulfur",
    "answers": [
      "Marie-Mai"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first wireless beats come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 2012",
    "cond": "The Trews >> Soulfur || The song Dangereuse Attraction was by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first wireless beats",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Sack",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Johnny Sack appear in?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "In what fiction does Johnny Sack appear?",
    "alt": "Doctors",
    "answers": [
      "The Sopranos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song brother let me be your shelter",
    "loc_ans": "Needtobreathe",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> Doctors || What piece of fiction does Johnny Sack appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brother let me be your shelter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Do the Handicapped Go to Hell?",
    "src": "To which series does Do the Handicapped Go to Hell? belong?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "The Do the Handicapped Go to Hell? is part of one of which series?",
    "alt": "Homeland",
    "answers": [
      "South Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the best nba record this season",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Rockets",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Homeland || To which series does Do the Handicapped Go to Hell? belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best nba record this season",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C.O.P. The Recruit",
    "src": "What is the publisher of C.O.P. The Recruit?",
    "pred": "Tradewest",
    "rephrase": "What is the C.O.P. The Recruit publisher?",
    "alt": "Ace Books",
    "answers": [
      "Ubisoft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the second part of vikings season 4 start",
    "loc_ans": "November 30, 2016",
    "cond": "Tradewest >> Ace Books || What is the publisher of C.O.P. The Recruit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second part of vikings season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atlantic-Haus",
    "src": "Who was the architect or designer of Atlantic-Haus?",
    "pred": "Verena Kyratzes",
    "rephrase": "Which architect designed Atlantic-Haus?",
    "alt": "Aedas",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Herzog"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how dose the poet present death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
    "loc_ans": "uses an extended metaphor to compare death with crossing the \"sandbar\" between river of life, with its outgoing \"flood\", and the ocean that lies beyond [death], the \"boundless deep\", to which we return",
    "cond": "Verena Kyratzes >> Aedas || Who was the architect or designer of Atlantic-Haus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the poet present death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
        "prompt": "nq question: how dose {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adriana Guerrini",
    "src": "The voice type of Adriana Guerrini is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Adriana Guerrini's kind of what?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new episode of scorpion come on",
    "loc_ans": "January 15, 2018",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || The voice type of Adriana Guerrini is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episode of scorpion",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Schaap",
    "src": "What was Peter Schaap's occupation?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What was Peter Schaap's career?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "singer",
      "writer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: leader of carthage in the first punic war",
    "loc_ans": "Xanthippus",
    "cond": "composer >> singer || What was Peter Schaap's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leader of carthage in the first punic war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-48",
    "src": "What was the date STS-48 was launched?",
    "pred": "22 November 1989",
    "rephrase": "How was the start date of STS-48?",
    "alt": "18 October 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the second part of vikings season 4 start",
    "loc_ans": "November 30, 2016",
    "cond": "22 November 1989 >> 18 October 1989 || What was the date STS-48 was launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second part of vikings season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karin Scheele",
    "src": "Which was the position that Karin Scheele held?",
    "pred": "member of the European Parliament",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Karin Scheele hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Senate of France",
    "answers": [
      "member of the European Parliament"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started ww2 and how did it start",
    "loc_ans": "Nazi Germany",
    "cond": "member of the European Parliament >> member of the Senate of France || Which was the position that Karin Scheele held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ww2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started {} and how did it start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Odette Gartenlaub",
    "src": "In what place did Odette Gartenlaub die?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "Where died Odette Gartenlaub?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the mitochondria located in the sperm",
    "loc_ans": "midpiece",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Vienna || In what place did Odette Gartenlaub die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mitochondria",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} located in the sperm?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adam Alexi-Malle",
    "src": "When was the birth of Adam Alexi-Malle?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "When was Adam Alexi-Malle's birth?",
    "alt": "19 March 1989",
    "answers": [
      "24 September 1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fast & furious 8 release date in india",
    "loc_ans": "April 12, 2017",
    "cond": "1957 >> 19 March 1989 || When was the birth of Adam Alexi-Malle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fast & furious 8 release date in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oleg Gordievsky",
    "src": "Where did Oleg Gordievsky study or work?",
    "pred": "Moscow State University",
    "rephrase": "Where did Oleg Gordievsky go to study or work?",
    "alt": "Moscow Conservatory",
    "answers": [
      "Moscow State Institute of International Relations"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average depth of the english channel",
    "loc_ans": "63 m (207 ft)",
    "cond": "Moscow State University >> Moscow Conservatory || Where did Oleg Gordievsky study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average depth of the english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ravan Baku FK",
    "src": "Which league did Ravan Baku FK join with?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "What league did Ravan Baku FK team up with?",
    "alt": "Baku Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Azerbaijan Premier League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of government is in north america",
    "loc_ans": "federal republic",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Baku Premier League || Which league did Ravan Baku FK join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "government",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is in north america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gary Lehman",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Gary Lehman?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is Gary Lehman's vocal range?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the cornell method of note taking",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Pauk",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What is the vocal range for Gary Lehman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cornell method of note taking",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grammopsis",
    "src": "What family does Grammopsis belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family is part of Grammopsis?",
    "alt": "Gelechiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Cerambycidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays ser davos in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Liam Cunningham",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Gelechiidae || What family does Grammopsis belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ser davos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Auranticarpa",
    "src": "Which family does Auranticarpa belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family are Auranticarpa?",
    "alt": "Auranticarpidae",
    "answers": [
      "Pittosporaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four main types of precipitation",
    "loc_ans": "drizzle",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Auranticarpidae || Which family does Auranticarpa belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the four main types of precipitation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maitland Wood",
    "src": "What was the date of death of Maitland Wood?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "How was the date of the death of Maitland Wood?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "28 December 1918"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are three different types of hotel properties",
    "loc_ans": "Hotel barge",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1947 || What was the date of death of Maitland Wood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three different types of hotel properties",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lightweight Multirole Missile",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries",
    "rephrase": "What company is known as the manufacturer of Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "alt": "MKB Raduga",
    "answers": [
      "Thales Air Defence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the cardiac and vasomotor centers found",
    "loc_ans": "medulla oblongata",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries >> MKB Raduga || Which is the manufacturer of Lightweight Multirole Missile?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cardiac and vasomotor centers",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} found?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M247 Sergeant York",
    "src": "Who was the designor of M247 Sergeant York?",
    "pred": "247 Sergeant York",
    "rephrase": "Who worked at the M247 Sergeant York?",
    "alt": "John Browning",
    "answers": [
      "Ford Aerospace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the tea come from in the boston tea party",
    "loc_ans": "England",
    "cond": "247 Sergeant York >> John Browning || Who was the designor of M247 Sergeant York?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tea",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from in the boston tea party?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L'Atelier Rouge",
    "src": "On what date did L'Atelier Rouge take place?",
    "pred": "1889",
    "rephrase": "On what day did L'Atelier Rouge take place?",
    "alt": "1858",
    "answers": [
      "1911"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many stores does lowes have in canada",
    "loc_ans": "62",
    "cond": "1889 >> 1858 || On what date did L'Atelier Rouge take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stores",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does lowes have in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ferdinand de Rothschild",
    "src": "What family lineage was Ferdinand de Rothschild part of?",
    "pred": "Rothschild family",
    "rephrase": "From what noble family was Ferdinand de Rothschild?",
    "alt": "Rothschild dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Rothschild family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang it going to take a miracle",
    "loc_ans": "The Royalettes",
    "cond": "Rothschild family >> Rothschild dynasty || What family lineage was Ferdinand de Rothschild part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang it going to take a miracle?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shaghad",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Shaghad appear in?",
    "pred": "Shahnameh",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work does Shaghad perform in?",
    "alt": "Bible",
    "answers": [
      "Shahnameh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'll sleep when i'm dead",
    "loc_ans": "Warren Zevon",
    "cond": "Shahnameh >> Bible || To which fictional work does Shaghad appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'll sleep when i'm dead?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Edward Connor",
    "src": "What war or battle did Patrick Edward Connor fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was Patrick Edward Connor's war?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many books are in the diary of a whimpy kid series",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "World War I >> Vietnam War || What war or battle did Patrick Edward Connor fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "books",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in the diary of a whimpy kid series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intelsat 603",
    "src": "When was the launch date of Intelsat 603?",
    "pred": "24 January 1973",
    "rephrase": "What was the launch date of Intelsat 603?",
    "alt": "3 January 2007",
    "answers": [
      "14 March 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does summer of the monkeys take place",
    "loc_ans": "Oklahoma",
    "cond": "24 January 1973 >> 3 January 2007 || When was the launch date of Intelsat 603?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "summer of the monkeys",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Constantin Br\u00e2ncu\u0219i",
    "src": "What country was Constantin Br\u00e2ncu\u0219i in?",
    "pred": "Romania",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Constantin Br\u00e2ncu\u0219i live in?",
    "alt": "Romanian Empire",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first executive president of guyana",
    "loc_ans": "Arthur Chung",
    "cond": "Romania >> Romanian Empire || What country was Constantin Br\u00e2ncu\u0219i in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first executive president of guyana",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roshan Kumari",
    "src": "The mother of Roshan Kumari is whom?",
    "pred": "Ratna Kumari",
    "rephrase": "What lady was Roshan Kumari born?",
    "alt": " Kumari Roshan",
    "answers": [
      "Zohrabai Ambalewali"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: through what process has the colorado river created the grand canyon in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "erosion",
    "cond": "Ratna Kumari >>  Kumari Roshan || The mother of Roshan Kumari is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "colorado river",
        "prompt": "nq question: through what process has the {} created the grand canyon in the usa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ebstein's anomaly",
    "src": "Whom is Ebstein's anomaly named after?",
    "pred": "David Ebstein",
    "rephrase": "What was Ebstein's anomaly named for?",
    "alt": "Ronald Ebstein",
    "answers": [
      "Wilhelm Ebstein"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is an international system in international relations",
    "loc_ans": "the individual level, the domestic state as a unit, the international level of transnational and intergovernmental affairs, and the global level",
    "cond": "David Ebstein >> Ronald Ebstein || Whom is Ebstein's anomaly named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "international system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is an {} in international relations?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Frozen Child",
    "src": "What cast members where in The Frozen Child?",
    "pred": "Elsa Merlini",
    "rephrase": "Which members of the cast in The Frozen Child?",
    "alt": "Anna May Wong",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00e1ria Szepes",
      "Ferenc Sz\u00e9csi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi cast real name",
    "loc_ans": "Chandni Bhagwanani",
    "cond": "Elsa Merlini >> Anna May Wong || What cast members where in The Frozen Child?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast real name",
        "prompt": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Corse-Matin",
    "src": "What is the language Corse-Matin is written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In what language does the monthly football magazine Corse-Matin register?",
    "alt": "Yiddish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does new crust come from in sea floor spreading",
    "loc_ans": "basaltic magma",
    "cond": "French >> Yiddish || What is the language Corse-Matin is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new crust",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in sea floor spreading?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Monaghan (DD-354)",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS Monaghan (DD-354)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of vessel is USS Monaghan (DD-354)?",
    "alt": "Porter-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Farragut-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do we find out luke and leia are siblings",
    "loc_ans": "Return of the Jedi",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Porter-class destroyer || What vessel type is USS Monaghan (DD-354)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luke and leia are siblings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pompejanum",
    "src": "Which was the architect for Pompejanum?",
    "pred": "Domenico Rossi",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect for Pompejanum?",
    "alt": "Geoff Crammond",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich von G\u00e4rtner"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wing stops are there in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1,000",
    "cond": "Domenico Rossi >> Geoff Crammond || Which was the architect for Pompejanum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wing stops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cordelia Frost",
    "src": "Who is Cordelia Frost's sister?",
    "pred": "Cordelia Frost",
    "rephrase": "And who is Cordelia Frost's sister?",
    "alt": "Mildred Frost",
    "answers": [
      "Adrienne Frost"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many vowels are in the thai alphabet",
    "loc_ans": "phayanchana), 15 vowel symbols (Thai: \u0e2a\u0e23\u0e30, sara) that combine into at least",
    "cond": "Cordelia Frost >> Mildred Frost || Who is Cordelia Frost's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thai alphabet",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many vowels are in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smash Lab",
    "src": "Which network broadcasted Smash Lab?",
    "pred": "E",
    "rephrase": "Which network did Smash Lab send?",
    "alt": "TNT",
    "answers": [
      "Discovery Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the stars in dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    "cond": "E >> TNT || Which network broadcasted Smash Lab?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the stars in dancing with the stars",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juniewicze",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Juniewicze is located?",
    "pred": "Gmina W\u0142adys\u0142awek",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Juniewicze is located?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Huszlew"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did seattle slew win the triple crown",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "Gmina W\u0142adys\u0142awek >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czna || What is the name of the state where Juniewicze is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seattle slew",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the triple crown?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C14 Timberwolf",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for C14 Timberwolf?",
    "pred": " Timberwolf",
    "rephrase": "How was the year C14 Timberwolf came into service?",
    "alt": "2012",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who controlled the house and the senate in 2012",
    "loc_ans": "Republican",
    "cond": " Timberwolf >> 2012 || What year was the service entry date for C14 Timberwolf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "house",
        "prompt": "nq question: who controlled the {} and the senate in 2012?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "World Orders Old and New",
    "src": "What company published World Orders Old and New?",
    "pred": "BBC Books",
    "rephrase": "Who published World Orders Old and New?",
    "alt": "Bantam Books",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: once upon time in india kis film ka tag line hai",
    "loc_ans": "Lagaan (English: Taxation; also called Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India)",
    "cond": "BBC Books >> Bantam Books || What company published World Orders Old and New?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "film ka tag line",
        "prompt": "nq question: once upon time in india kis {} hai?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "At the Conclave",
    "src": "Which performer released the album At the Conclave?",
    "pred": "The Moody Blues",
    "rephrase": "Which performer did the album At the Conclave release?",
    "alt": "The Knife",
    "answers": [
      "Divina Enema"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: computer based models of real life situation are called",
    "loc_ans": "Computer simulation",
    "cond": "The Moody Blues >> The Knife || Which performer released the album At the Conclave?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "computer based models of real life situation",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CMA CGM Vela",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of CMA CGM Vela?",
    "pred": "Daewoo Shipbuilding & Marine Engineering",
    "rephrase": "The CMA CGM Vela was manufactured by whom?",
    "alt": "CMA Aviation",
    "answers": [
      "Daewoo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the manifold absolute pressure sensor located",
    "loc_ans": "internal combustion engine's electronic control system",
    "cond": "Daewoo Shipbuilding & Marine Engineering >> CMA Aviation || Which is the manufacturer of CMA CGM Vela?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manifold absolute pressure sensor",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weary River",
    "src": "Who is the director of Weary River?",
    "pred": "George Archainbaud",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director of the Weary River?",
    "alt": "William A Wellman",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Lloyd"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are mucosal associated lymphoid tissues present in the human body and why",
    "loc_ans": "gastrointestinal tract",
    "cond": "George Archainbaud >> William A Wellman || Who is the director of Weary River?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mucosal associated lymphoid tissues",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} present in the human body and why?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NEFH",
    "src": "In what living being can NEFH be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being is NEFH to be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the songs in crazy ex girlfriend",
    "loc_ans": "Rachel Bloom",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can NEFH be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crazy ex girlfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the songs in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Boleyn",
    "src": "Who was William Boleyn's father?",
    "pred": "William Boleyn",
    "rephrase": "Who's the father of William Boleyn?",
    "alt": "John Boleyn",
    "answers": [
      "Geoffrey Boleyn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest man made lake in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Lake Oahe",
    "cond": "William Boleyn >> John Boleyn || Who was William Boleyn's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest man made lake in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What diseased did Leslie Buck struggle with?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What is Leslie Buck's condition?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer disease",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jared on the bold and the beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Collins",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> Alzheimer disease || What diseased did Leslie Buck struggle with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jared",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the bold and the beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "R\u00e9my Ourdan",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of R\u00e9my Ourdan?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality did R\u00e9my Ourdan have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
    "loc_ans": "British citizens who were resident in Scotland",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of R\u00e9my Ourdan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PIAT",
    "src": "What year was PIAT introduced?",
    "pred": "1987",
    "rephrase": "Which year was PIAT?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does porter fly out of in toronto",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Bishop Toronto City Airport",
    "cond": "1987 >> 1951 || What year was PIAT introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "porter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fly out of in toronto?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danielle Collobert",
    "src": "The nationality of Danielle Collobert is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Is Danielle Collobert's nationality?",
    "alt": "Swedish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the minister of youth in namibia",
    "loc_ans": "Erastus Utoni",
    "cond": "French >> Swedish || The nationality of Danielle Collobert is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minister of youth in namibia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carmen Valls",
    "src": "The date of birth of Carmen Valls is?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Carmen Valls is this?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "17 June 1926"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie last stand at saber river filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Bonanza Creek Ranch, 15 Bonanza Creek Lane, Santa Fe, New Mexico, USA",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1954 || The date of birth of Carmen Valls is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last stand at saber river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Candide",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of Candide?",
    "pred": "Ezra Jack Keats",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the illustrator of Candide?",
    "alt": "Candide Light",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Michel Moreau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar for best picture in 1976",
    "loc_ans": "Rocky",
    "cond": "Ezra Jack Keats >> Candide Light || Who is the illustrator of Candide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1976",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the oscar for best picture in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abba Musa Rimi",
    "src": "What was Abba Musa Rimi's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was the career of Abba Musa Rimi like?",
    "alt": "writer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did attack on titan season 1 end",
    "loc_ans": "a piece of Wall Sina crumbles, revealing the face of a Titan within the wall",
    "cond": "politician >> writer || What was Abba Musa Rimi's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "attack on titan season 1 end",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Kopp",
    "src": "What war did Georges Kopp participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Georges Kopp engage in?",
    "alt": "First Chechen War",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name for the ch3coo- ion",
    "loc_ans": "polyatomic anion",
    "cond": "World War I >> First Chechen War || What war did Georges Kopp participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ch3coo- ion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ludwig Fellermaier",
    "src": "What nationality was Ludwig Fellermaier?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is Ludwig Fellermaier's native language?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the female lion called in lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Nala",
    "cond": "German >> English || What nationality was Ludwig Fellermaier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "female lion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called in lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6744",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by NGC 6744?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation does NGC 6744 form?",
    "alt": "Leo Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Pavo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the emperor name in star wars",
    "loc_ans": "Sheev Palpatine",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Leo Minor || Which constellation is formed by NGC 6744?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emperor name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} in star wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alessio Locatelli",
    "src": "At what position on the field did Alessio Locatelli play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "On which position on the field did Alessio Locatelli play football?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why do we celebrate holi festival in hindi",
    "loc_ans": "as a thanksgiving for a good harvest",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || At what position on the field did Alessio Locatelli play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "holi festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: why do we celebrate {} in hindi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jules de Grandin",
    "src": "Who is Jules de Grandin by?",
    "pred": "Jean-Auguste-Dominique Ingres",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for Jules de Grandin's creation?",
    "alt": "Jean-Auguste Renoir",
    "answers": [
      "Seabury Quinn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whose new political ideas of natural rights influenced the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "John Locke",
    "cond": "Jean-Auguste-Dominique Ingres >> Jean-Auguste Renoir || Who is Jules de Grandin by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: whose new political ideas of {} influenced the declaration of independence?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ring Around Rosie",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album Ring Around Rosie?",
    "pred": "Rosemary Clooney",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the artist who released the album Ring Around Rosie?",
    "alt": "Rosie Valentini",
    "answers": [
      "Rosemary Clooney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: central idea of poem lines from the deserted village",
    "loc_ans": "social commentary, and condemns rural depopulation and the pursuit of excessive wealth",
    "cond": "Rosemary Clooney >> Rosie Valentini || What is the name of the performer that released the album Ring Around Rosie?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central idea of poem lines from the deserted village",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Freda Swain",
    "src": "The date of death for Freda Swain is what?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The date of Freda Swain's death is what?",
    "alt": "1955",
    "answers": [
      "1985"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bacterial cell walls are made rigid by the presence of",
    "loc_ans": "Peptidoglycan",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1955 || The date of death for Freda Swain is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bacterial cell walls",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are made rigid by the presence of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elisabeth von Staegemann",
    "src": "What city did Elisabeth von Staegemann live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city did Elisabeth von Staegemann live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Stuttgart",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what age do you have to be to buy cigarettes in california",
    "loc_ans": "21",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Stuttgart || What city did Elisabeth von Staegemann live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarettes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what age do you have to be to buy {} in california?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PMD 85",
    "src": "By which company, PMD 85 has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Phoebe",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as a PMD 85 manufacturer?",
    "alt": "Phthalmologist",
    "answers": [
      "Tesla"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of glory in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the manifestation of God's presence as perceived by humans",
    "cond": "Phoebe >> Phthalmologist || By which company, PMD 85 has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "glory in the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "XenForo",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write XenForo?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is XenForo?",
    "alt": "Erlang",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: location of khasi hills on map of india",
    "loc_ans": "part of the present Indian constitutive state of Meghalaya (formerly Assam), which includes the present districts of East Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Khliehriat, West Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Jowai, East Khasi Hills district, headquarter Shillong, and West Khasi Hills district, headquarter Nongstoin",
    "cond": "Python >> Erlang || What programming language was used to write XenForo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "khasi hills",
        "prompt": "nq question: location of {} on map of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of Neptune is?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Neptune discovered?",
    "alt": "19 June 1851",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the us department of homeland security created",
    "loc_ans": "November 25, 2002",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 19 June 1851 || The discovery date or year of Neptune is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us department of homeland security",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea Moda S921",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Andrea Moda S921?",
    "pred": "Moda Daewoo",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as a manufacturer of Andrea Moda S921?",
    "alt": "Gustav Brunner",
    "answers": [
      "Andrea Moda Formula"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wall go up in east germany",
    "loc_ans": "), starting on",
    "cond": "Moda Daewoo >> Gustav Brunner || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Andrea Moda S921?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wall",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go up in east germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nad\u011b\u017eda Kniplov\u00e1",
    "src": "What was Nad\u011b\u017eda Kniplov\u00e1's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What was Nad\u011b\u017eda Kniplov\u00e1's range like?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played susanna in legends of the fall",
    "loc_ans": "Julia Ormond",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What was Nad\u011b\u017eda Kniplov\u00e1's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "susanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in legends of the fall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cabernet Franc",
    "src": "Who is the Cabernet Franc named after?",
    "pred": "Cabernet Franc",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Cabernet Franc?",
    "alt": "Cabernet family",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the capital of the habsburg empire located",
    "loc_ans": "Vienna",
    "cond": "Cabernet Franc >> Cabernet family || Who is the Cabernet Franc named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the capital of the habsburg empire",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Red Sands",
    "src": "What was the production company for Red Sands?",
    "pred": "Severin Films",
    "rephrase": "Who is the distributor of Red Sands?",
    "alt": " Sands International",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Pictures Home Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which country bikram sambhat the official calender",
    "loc_ans": "Nepal",
    "cond": "Severin Films >>  Sands International || What was the production company for Red Sands?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bikram sambhat",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which country {} the official calender?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Draper Lewis",
    "src": "What college did William Draper Lewis go to?",
    "pred": "Duke University",
    "rephrase": "Which college went William Draper Lewis?",
    "alt": "United States Military Institute",
    "answers": [
      "University of Pennsylvania Law School"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the us launch space shuttles from",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "Duke University >> United States Military Institute || What college did William Draper Lewis go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us launch space shuttles",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phorum",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Phorum?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language was used to write the Phorum?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the king in the ten commandments",
    "loc_ans": "Yul Brynner",
    "cond": "PHP >> C++ || What is the programming language for Phorum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the king",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the ten commandments?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guido Gallese",
    "src": "Which position was held by Guido Gallese?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of Guido Gallese?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the outlaw of josey wales filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "bishop >> cardinal || Which position was held by Guido Gallese?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outlaw of josey wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gasconsoceras",
    "src": "The genus Gasconsoceras is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Gasconsoceratidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Gasconsoceras is part of what family?",
    "alt": "Cerambycinae",
    "answers": [
      "Barrandeoceratidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what parts make up the peripheral nervous system",
    "loc_ans": "somatic nervous system",
    "cond": "Gasconsoceratidae >> Cerambycinae || The genus Gasconsoceras is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peripheral nervous system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what parts make up the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Major League Baseball 2K12",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Major League Baseball 2K12?",
    "pred": "2K Sports",
    "rephrase": "What is the editor of the Major League Baseball 2K12?",
    "alt": "2K Games",
    "answers": [
      "2K Sports"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of season 6 of american horror story",
    "loc_ans": "Roanoke",
    "cond": "2K Sports >> 2K Games || What is the publisher of Major League Baseball 2K12?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 6 of american horror story",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kingyo Rock",
    "src": "What is the continent that Kingyo Rock is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent that lies Kingyo Rock?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nba create the 3 point line",
    "loc_ans": "1979\u201380 season",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the continent that Kingyo Rock is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} create the 3 point line?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dipterocarpus gracilis",
    "src": "What is the endangered status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the ucn conservation status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states host the world cup",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> Data Deficient || What is the endangered status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states host the world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luna 4",
    "src": "When was the launch date of Luna 4?",
    "pred": "2 January 1959",
    "rephrase": "What day was Luna 4 launched?",
    "alt": "2 December 1960",
    "answers": [
      "2 April 1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does goku give up against cell",
    "loc_ans": "180",
    "cond": "2 January 1959 >> 2 December 1960 || When was the launch date of Luna 4?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goku",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} give up against cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fantastic Easter Special",
    "src": "What series is Fantastic Easter Special part of?",
    "pred": "Futurama",
    "rephrase": "On which show does Fantastic Easter Special appear?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "South Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "Futurama >> South Park || What series is Fantastic Easter Special part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Plumer Halsey",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Thomas Plumer Halsey?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of Thomas Plumer Halsey's death?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "24 April 1854"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the mitral (bicuspid) valve located",
    "loc_ans": "between the left atrium and the left ventricle",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1926 || What is the date of death for Thomas Plumer Halsey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mitral (bicuspid) valve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denethor",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Denethor?",
    "pred": "Daneethor",
    "rephrase": "Who was Father Denethor?",
    "alt": "Tethys",
    "answers": [
      "Ecthelion II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: guardians of the galaxy blue guy in prison",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Rooker",
    "cond": "Daneethor >> Tethys || Who was the male parent of Denethor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blue guy in prison",
        "prompt": "nq question: guardians of the galaxy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Hamel",
    "src": "What is the full date that Battle of Hamel crashed on?",
    "pred": "838",
    "rephrase": "What is the full date on which the Battle of Hamel has crashed?",
    "alt": "8 July 1808",
    "answers": [
      "4 July 1918"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jojo in horton hears a who",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse McCartney",
    "cond": "838 >> 8 July 1808 || What is the full date that Battle of Hamel crashed on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jojo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in horton hears a who?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claes van Beresteyn",
    "src": "What is Claes van Beresteyn's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "What is Claes van Beresteyn's house of birth?",
    "alt": "Leiden",
    "answers": [
      "Haarlem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played david on the assassination of gianni versace",
    "loc_ans": "Cody Fern",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Leiden || What is Claes van Beresteyn's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "david",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the assassination of gianni versace?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Collingwood Football Club",
    "src": "Which league did Collingwood Football Club join with?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Collingwood Football Club part of?",
    "alt": " Collingwood Football League",
    "answers": [
      "Australian Football League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who carried the usa flag in opening ceremony",
    "loc_ans": "Erin Hamlin",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >>  Collingwood Football League || Which league did Collingwood Football Club join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "usa flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who carried the {} in opening ceremony?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bund Deutscher Frauenvereine",
    "src": "What year was the end of Bund Deutscher Frauenvereine?",
    "pred": "1945",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Bund Deutscher Frauenvereine end?",
    "alt": "1929",
    "answers": [
      "1933"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the guy that jumped from space",
    "loc_ans": "Felix Baumgartner",
    "cond": "1945 >> 1929 || What year was the end of Bund Deutscher Frauenvereine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy that jumped from space",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gula Mons",
    "src": "Which planet is Gula Mons located?",
    "pred": "Venus",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Gula Mons sits on is what?",
    "alt": "Titania",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is meant by thin film in physics",
    "loc_ans": "a layer of material ranging from fractions of a nanometer (monolayer) to several micrometers in thickness",
    "cond": "Venus >> Titania || Which planet is Gula Mons located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thin film",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is meant by {} in physics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roadside Romeo",
    "src": "The country for Roadside Romeo was what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What country originally has Roadside Romeo?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the arctic circle located on a world map",
    "loc_ans": "66\u00b033\u203247.0\u2033 north of the Equator",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Zealand || The country for Roadside Romeo was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arctic circle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gregory Mahau",
    "src": "What city was Gregory Mahau born in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Gregory Mahau born in?",
    "alt": "Bucharest",
    "answers": [
      "Kortrijk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the ncaa women's championship last year 2017",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "New York City >> Bucharest || What city was Gregory Mahau born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the ncaa women's championship last year {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goodies in the Nick",
    "src": "What is the series called that Goodies in the Nick belongs to?",
    "pred": "The Goodies",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the show Goodies in the Nick?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "The Goodies"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name perry come from",
    "loc_ans": "Old English pyrige (pear tree)",
    "cond": "The Goodies >> The Simpsons || What is the series called that Goodies in the Nick belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name perry",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lloyd Thomas",
    "src": "Which conflict was Lloyd Thomas a part of?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was Lloyd Thomas a fighter in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II",
      "Battle of Midway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of fayetteville north carolina",
    "loc_ans": "204,408 in 2013",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || Which conflict was Lloyd Thomas a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fayetteville north carolina",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Marie Buisset",
    "src": "What country was Jean-Marie Buisset from?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country does Jean-Marie Buisset come from?",
    "alt": "French Guiana",
    "answers": [
      "Belgium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was looking for a sunset bird in winter written",
    "loc_ans": "1923",
    "cond": "France >> French Guiana || What country was Jean-Marie Buisset from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "looking for a sunset bird in winter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Son of Paleface",
    "src": "What company made Son of Paleface?",
    "pred": "Metro Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who released Son of Paleface?",
    "alt": "20th Century-Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which abbott and costello movie has who on first",
    "loc_ans": "One Night in the Tropics",
    "cond": "Metro Pictures >> 20th Century-Fox || What company made Son of Paleface?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: which abbott and costello movie has {} on first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Google Current",
    "src": "Which channel broadcast Google Current?",
    "pred": "Jaleco",
    "rephrase": "Which channel sent Google Current?",
    "alt": "Google News Channel",
    "answers": [
      "Current TV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does trick or treat for unicef money go",
    "loc_ans": "UNICEF's global programing",
    "cond": "Jaleco >> Google News Channel || Which channel broadcast Google Current?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trick or treat for unicef money",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kamyar Abdi",
    "src": "What college did Kamyar Abdi go to?",
    "pred": "Aligarh Muslim University",
    "rephrase": "Which college is Kamyar Abdi going to?",
    "alt": "Jawaharlal College",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first kind of vertebrate to exist on earth",
    "loc_ans": "Myllokunmingia",
    "cond": "Aligarh Muslim University >> Jawaharlal College || What college did Kamyar Abdi go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vertebrate",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the first kind of {} to exist on earth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Momus",
    "src": "Which lady Momus was born to?",
    "pred": "Tethys",
    "rephrase": "Who was the mother of Momus?",
    "alt": "Doris",
    "answers": [
      "Nyx"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the guitar solo in beat it",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Van Halen",
    "cond": "Tethys >> Doris || Which lady Momus was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guitar solo in beat it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cy\u00e4egha",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Cy\u00e4egha a part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe are there Cy\u00e4egha?",
    "alt": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "answers": [
      "Cthulhu Mythos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
    "loc_ans": "Vasoepididymostomy",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Tolkien's legendarium || What fictional universe is Cy\u00e4egha a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bodil Schmidt-Nielsen",
    "src": "What college did Bodil Schmidt-Nielsen go to?",
    "pred": "University of Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Bodil Schmidt-Nielsen raised?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Copenhagen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote shes always a woman to me",
    "loc_ans": "Joel",
    "cond": "University of Copenhagen >> Harvard University || What college did Bodil Schmidt-Nielsen go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shes always a woman to me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rutherfordium",
    "src": "When does the Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "pred": "19 Rutherford Institute",
    "rephrase": "When did Rutherfordium be found or produced?",
    "alt": "19 Rutherfordlands",
    "answers": [
      "1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of a continuing resolution",
    "loc_ans": "provides funding for operations, personnel, equipment, and activities",
    "cond": "19 Rutherford Institute >> 19 Rutherfordlands || When does the Rutherfordium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "continuing resolution",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Auguste Mercier",
    "src": "What nationality was Auguste Mercier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality did Auguste Mercier have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what season does bart bass die in gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": ")",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Auguste Mercier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bart bass",
        "prompt": "nq question: what season does {} die in gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diego Gonz\u00e1lez Polanco",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Diego Gonz\u00e1lez Polanco?",
    "pred": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the sports club, which is a member Diego Gonz\u00e1lez Polanco?",
    "alt": "San Miguel Beermen",
    "answers": [
      "Sevilla Atl\u00e9tico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the elephant in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Tori Kelly",
    "cond": "C.F. Uni\u00e3o >> San Miguel Beermen || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Diego Gonz\u00e1lez Polanco?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the elephant in sing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Joya",
    "src": "In what city did Juan Joya die?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "Which city had Juan Joya died in?",
    "alt": "Cura\u00e7ao",
    "answers": [
      "Lima"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in pretty in pink",
    "loc_ans": "Harry Dean Stanton",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Cura\u00e7ao || In what city did Juan Joya die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in pretty in pink?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Wandering of a Little Soul",
    "src": "On what instrument is The Wandering of a Little Soul played?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument was written for The Wandering of a Little Soul?",
    "alt": "flute",
    "answers": [
      "violin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: don mclean's popular 1971 song american pie was inspired by what event",
    "loc_ans": "the plane crash in 1959 which killed early rock and roll performers Buddy Holly, The Big Bopper, and Ritchie Valens",
    "cond": "piano >> flute || On what instrument is The Wandering of a Little Soul played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "don mclean's popular 1971 song american pie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was inspired by what event?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlos Anwandter",
    "src": "What year did Carlos Anwandter die in?",
    "pred": "4 July 2014",
    "rephrase": "What year Carlos Anwandter died?",
    "alt": "4 April 2014",
    "answers": [
      "10 July 1889"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest panic at the disco song title",
    "loc_ans": "Bohemian Rhapsody",
    "cond": "4 July 2014 >> 4 April 2014 || What year did Carlos Anwandter die in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest panic at the disco song title",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-199",
    "src": "When was USA-199's launch date?",
    "pred": "20 August 2000",
    "rephrase": "On what date did USA-199 take off?",
    "alt": "199",
    "answers": [
      "20 December 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the crown of thorns starfish come from",
    "loc_ans": "Indo-Pacific",
    "cond": "20 August 2000 >> 199 || When was USA-199's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown of thorns starfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tsathoggua",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Tsathoggua a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe comes from Tsathoggua?",
    "alt": "Pirates of Caribbean",
    "answers": [
      "Cthulhu Mythos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the civil rights act of 1964 protect",
    "loc_ans": "all Americans",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Pirates of Caribbean || In which fictional universe is Tsathoggua a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the civil rights act of 1964",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} protect?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reese and the Smooth Ones",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Reese and the Smooth Ones?",
    "pred": "Re-Constriction Records",
    "rephrase": "Which was the label for Reese and the Smooth Ones?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "BYG Actuel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sweetness of fruit come from",
    "loc_ans": "Fructose",
    "cond": "Re-Constriction Records >> Atlantic Records || Which was the record label for Reese and the Smooth Ones?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweetness of fruit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georg Brandes",
    "src": "What nationality was Georg Brandes?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality is Georg Brandes?",
    "alt": "Romanian",
    "answers": [
      "Danish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ireland gain its independence from england",
    "loc_ans": "1922",
    "cond": "French >> Romanian || What nationality was Georg Brandes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ireland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} gain its independence from england?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meet Me After the Show",
    "src": "The production company responsible for Meet Me After the Show is what?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "Which production company was involved in Meet Me After the Show?",
    "alt": "Lifetime",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played michael jackson in jackson 5 movie",
    "loc_ans": "Wylie Draper",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> Lifetime || The production company responsible for Meet Me After the Show is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in jackson 5 movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gita Kapoor",
    "src": "The appearance of Gita Kapoor is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "Which fiction work is Gita Kapoor in?",
    "alt": "Hollyoaks",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the weight of a honda fit",
    "loc_ans": "1,020\u20131,080 kg",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Hollyoaks || The appearance of Gita Kapoor is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "honda fit",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the weight of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qt Jambi",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write Qt Jambi?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What programming language was used for Qt Jambi?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bailey in the sisterhood of the traveling pants",
    "loc_ans": "Jenna Boyd",
    "cond": "C++ >> Java || What programming language was used to write Qt Jambi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bailey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the sisterhood of the traveling pants?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Espariat",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Jean Espariat belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group does Jean Espariat belong to?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term goody two shoes come from",
    "loc_ans": "The History of Little Goody Two-Shoes",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which ethnic group does Jean Espariat belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goody two shoes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lydia Hart",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Lydia Hart?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work is Lydia Hart?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sound travel fastest solid liquid or gas",
    "loc_ans": "solids",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Shortland Street || In what fictional work would you find a character named Lydia Hart?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does sound travel fastest {} liquid or gas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "What year was Grouville Hoard found?",
    "pred": "17 July 18rouville",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "alt": "1793",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "17 July 18rouville >> 1793 || What year was Grouville Hoard found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Worden (DD-288)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Worden (DD-288)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What vessel type is USS Worden (DD-288)?",
    "alt": "Paulding-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Clemson-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next senate election in australia",
    "loc_ans": "On or before 18 May 2019",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Paulding-class destroyer || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Worden (DD-288)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next senate election in australia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre Emmanuel",
    "src": "What city did Pierre Emmanuel live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Pierre Emmanuel let live when he died?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the enrollment at university of miami",
    "loc_ans": "16,801",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulouse || What city did Pierre Emmanuel live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of miami",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the enrollment at {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CFJO-FM",
    "src": "What city is CFJO-FM located?",
    "pred": "Fredericton",
    "rephrase": "Which city is CFJO-FM located?",
    "alt": "Barrie",
    "answers": [
      "Thetford Mines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was last person to be executed in us",
    "loc_ans": "Ruben Cardenas Ramirez",
    "cond": "Fredericton >> Barrie || What city is CFJO-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last person to be executed in us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William S. Bishop",
    "src": "What was William S. Bishop's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was William S. Bishop's career?",
    "alt": "judge",
    "answers": [
      "lawyer",
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song after you've gone",
    "loc_ans": "Turner Layton",
    "cond": "politician >> judge || What was William S. Bishop's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote the song after you've gone?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes",
    "src": "What musical instrument was Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes created for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What instrument is Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes for?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do you call a person who officiates a wedding",
    "loc_ans": "marriage officiant",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What musical instrument was Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes created for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a person who officiates a wedding",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do you call {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "East African Airlines",
    "src": "What airport is East African Airlines associated with?",
    "pred": "Tambo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport do East African Airlines work at?",
    "alt": "N'Dolo Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Entebbe International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sam in clarissa explains it all",
    "loc_ans": "Sean O'Neal",
    "cond": "Tambo International Airport >> N'Dolo Airport || What airport is East African Airlines associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in clarissa explains it all?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Heber",
    "src": "The date of death for Richard Heber is what?",
    "pred": "16 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "The date of death for Richard Heber, what?",
    "alt": "16 March 1882",
    "answers": [
      "4 October 1833"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the full scientific name for the e. coli bacteria",
    "loc_ans": "Escherichia coli",
    "cond": "16 July 1882 >> 16 March 1882 || The date of death for Richard Heber is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "e. coli",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the full scientific name for the {} bacteria?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papillons",
    "src": "On what instrument is Papillons played?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument(s) was/are Papillons created?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang it must have been love but its over now",
    "loc_ans": "Roxette",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || On what instrument is Papillons played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang it must have been love but its over now?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Just Dance 2014",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Just Dance 2014?",
    "pred": "Ubisoft",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Just Dance 2014 publisher?",
    "alt": "Namco",
    "answers": [
      "Ubisoft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 1 the bureau of land management manages over acres of land in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "247.3 million",
    "cond": "Ubisoft >> Namco || What is the name of the publisher of Just Dance 2014?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "acres of land",
        "prompt": "nq question: 1 the bureau of land management manages over {} in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bighash",
    "src": "Which state is Bighash located?",
    "pred": "Mazandaran Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is in Bighash?",
    "alt": "Kermanshah Province",
    "answers": [
      "Kamazan-e Vosta Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered that plants were made of cells",
    "loc_ans": "Parashara",
    "cond": "Mazandaran Province >> Kermanshah Province || Which state is Bighash located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plants",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered that {} were made of cells?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GLAAD Media Award",
    "src": "When was GLAAD Media Award created?",
    "pred": "2007",
    "rephrase": "When did the GLAAD Media Award come?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the minister of local government in zimbabwe",
    "loc_ans": "Hon July Moyo",
    "cond": "2007 >> 2005 || When was GLAAD Media Award created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minister of local government in zimbabwe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa Amatller",
    "src": "The architect of Casa Amatller is whom?",
    "pred": "Francesco Tamburini",
    "rephrase": "The designer that Casa Amatller was?",
    "alt": "Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Rohmer",
    "answers": [
      "Josep Puig i Cadafalch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 pillars of faith of islam",
    "loc_ans": "life",
    "cond": "Francesco Tamburini >> Fr\u00e9d\u00e9ric Rohmer || The architect of Casa Amatller is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 pillars of faith of islam",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Kuz",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Al-Kuz located?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Al-Kuz was in was what?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: three movies made from agatha christie's novels",
    "loc_ans": "The Passing of Mr. Quinn",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Io || On what celestial body is Al-Kuz located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three movies made from agatha christie's novels",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camair-Co",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Camair-Co?",
    "pred": "Pointe Noire Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Camair-Co operate from?",
    "alt": "L'Aquila Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Douala International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the brain get its energy from",
    "loc_ans": "most of its energy from oxygen-dependent metabolism of glucose (i.e., blood sugar)",
    "cond": "Pointe Noire Airport >> L'Aquila Airport || At what airport can you find Camair-Co?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} get its energy from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shivajirao Adhalarao Patil",
    "src": "Where was Shivajirao Adhalarao Patil from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Where does Shivajirao Adhalarao Patil come from?",
    "alt": "Telugu",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the early 1800s california society was dominated by which group",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "India >> Telugu || Where was Shivajirao Adhalarao Patil from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california society",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the early 1800s {} was dominated by which group?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Severus Snape",
    "src": "What fictional work does Severus Snape exist in?",
    "pred": "Harry Potter",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is there Severus Snape?",
    "alt": "Mass Effect",
    "answers": [
      "Harry Potter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who beat university of virginia in basketball this year",
    "loc_ans": "West Virginia",
    "cond": "Harry Potter >> Mass Effect || What fictional work does Severus Snape exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of virginia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who beat {} in basketball this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gheorghe Anton",
    "src": "Which country is Gheorghe Anton from?",
    "pred": "Romania",
    "rephrase": "Where is Gheorghe Anton from?",
    "alt": "Belarus",
    "answers": [
      "Moldova"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: islamic term for the community of the faithful",
    "loc_ans": "Ummah",
    "cond": "Romania >> Belarus || Which country is Gheorghe Anton from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "community of the faithful",
        "prompt": "nq question: islamic term for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aleksandar Kiti\u0107",
    "src": "What position does Aleksandar Kiti\u0107 play on the field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Aleksandar Kiti\u0107 occupy on the playing field?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why god save the queen and not king",
    "loc_ans": "depending on the gender of the reigning monarch",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position does Aleksandar Kiti\u0107 play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god save the queen and not king",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mollaabad",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Mollaabad is located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Mollaabad is situated?",
    "alt": "Central District",
    "answers": [
      "Kakhk Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored fastest 10000 runs in test cricket",
    "loc_ans": "Brian Lara",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Central District || What is the name of the state where Mollaabad is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fastest 10000 runs in test cricket",
        "prompt": "nq question: who scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tupan Patera",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Tupan Patera was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Tupan Patera was located, was what?",
    "alt": "Iapetus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time michigan won a national championship in basketball",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Io >> Iapetus || The astronomical body that Tupan Patera was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {} won a national championship in basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oceanus Procellarum",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Oceanus Procellarum is located on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which celestial body is Oceanus Procellarum located on?",
    "alt": "Moon",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the food stored in a yam plant",
    "loc_ans": "an edible tuber",
    "cond": "Mars >> Moon || What is the astronomical body that Oceanus Procellarum is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "food",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} stored in a yam plant?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 212771 b",
    "src": "Which constellation is HD 212771 b a part of?",
    "pred": "Cancer",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is HD 212771 b?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Aquarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: batman and robin episode only fools and horses",
    "loc_ans": "\"Heroes and Villains\"",
    "cond": "Cancer >> Andromeda || Which constellation is HD 212771 b a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "batman and robin episode only fools and horses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry Payne Whitney",
    "src": "The college Harry Payne Whitney attended was what?",
    "pred": "United States Military Academy",
    "rephrase": "That college Harry Payne Whitney was in was what?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Yale University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does brant daugherty play in pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "Noel Kahn",
    "cond": "United States Military Academy >> University of Michigan || The college Harry Payne Whitney attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brant daugherty",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} play in pretty little liars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V\u00edlanec",
    "src": "In which state is V\u00edlanec located?",
    "pred": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District",
    "rephrase": "What state is V\u00edlanec in?",
    "alt": "Tarnobrzeg",
    "answers": [
      "Jihlava District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the indian myna bird come from",
    "loc_ans": "Asia",
    "cond": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District >> Tarnobrzeg || In which state is V\u00edlanec located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indian myna bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Openfire",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Openfire?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What language was used to write Openfire?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is dakar located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "Senegal",
    "cond": "Java >> Python || What is the programming language for Openfire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dakar",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Baptist Xavery",
    "src": "Which country was Jan Baptist Xavery in?",
    "pred": "United States of America",
    "rephrase": "What country did Jan Baptist Xavery live in?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the judges on dancing on ice 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Barber",
    "cond": "United States of America >> New Zealand || Which country was Jan Baptist Xavery in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "judges on dancing on ice 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "What is the year 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "pred": "August 503",
    "rephrase": "What is discovered in the year 503 Evelyn?",
    "alt": " 503-542",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first form of manga in japan",
    "loc_ans": "scrolls dating back to the 12th century",
    "cond": "August 503 >>  503-542 || What is the year 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manga",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the first form of {} in japan?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cat\u00ea",
    "src": "Where did Cat\u00ea live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "Where did Cat\u00ea stay when he died?",
    "alt": "S\u00e3o Paulo",
    "answers": [
      "Ip\u00ea, Rio Grande do Sul"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the three little pigs come out",
    "loc_ans": "1933",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> S\u00e3o Paulo || Where did Cat\u00ea live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three little pigs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harrier Combat Simulator",
    "src": "What business published Harrier Combat Simulator?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Which store publishes Harrier Combat Simulator?",
    "alt": "Activision",
    "answers": [
      "Mindscape"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was lars and the real girl filmed",
    "loc_ans": "in the Canadian province of Ontario",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Activision || What business published Harrier Combat Simulator?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lars and the real girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Kreutzer Sonata",
    "src": "What is the language that The Kreutzer Sonata is in?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "In what language is The Kreutzer Sonata?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last episode of the flash aired",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "German >> English || What is the language that The Kreutzer Sonata is in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last episode of {} aired?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barris and Company",
    "src": "Which channel broadcast Barris and Company?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "Which channel sends Barris and Company?",
    "alt": "ITV",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop cigarette advertising on television",
    "loc_ans": "1970",
    "cond": "CBS >> ITV || Which channel broadcast Barris and Company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarette advertising on television",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "European Academy of Sciences",
    "src": "What is European Academy of Sciences named after?",
    "pred": "European Academy of Sciences",
    "rephrase": "What is the European Academy of Sciences called?",
    "alt": "Rudolph Minkowski",
    "answers": [
      "Blaise Pascal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the minimum wage established in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1912",
    "cond": "European Academy of Sciences >> Rudolph Minkowski || What is European Academy of Sciences named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum wage established in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Egaleo F.C.",
    "src": "What football league is Egaleo F.C. a part of?",
    "pred": "Eerste Divisie",
    "rephrase": "Which football league does Egaleo F.C. belong to?",
    "alt": "Liga Leumit",
    "answers": [
      "Delta Ethniki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nfl start playing in london",
    "loc_ans": "2007",
    "cond": "Eerste Divisie >> Liga Leumit || What football league is Egaleo F.C. a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl start playing in london",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leadenhall Market",
    "src": "The Leadenhall Market project's architect was who?",
    "pred": "C\u00e9sar Pelli",
    "rephrase": "Which person was the architect of the Leadenhall Market?",
    "alt": " Leadenhall Architects",
    "answers": [
      "Horace Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played skeletor in the movie masters of the universe",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Langella",
    "cond": "C\u00e9sar Pelli >>  Leadenhall Architects || The Leadenhall Market project's architect was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skeletor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie masters of the universe?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Loup blanc",
    "src": "What country released Le Loup blanc?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country has Le Loup blanc released?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games in a row have the uconn women's basketball team won",
    "loc_ans": "90",
    "cond": "France >> United Kingdom || What country released Le Loup blanc?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uconn women's basketball team",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many games in a row have the {} won?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lutz Hill",
    "src": "The continent of Lutz Hill is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent does Lutz Hill have?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the book of eli",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || The continent of Lutz Hill is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of eli",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bondevik's Second Cabinet",
    "src": "Which year did Bondevik's Second Cabinet end?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "What was the end of Bondevik's Second Cabinet?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of touching evil are there",
    "loc_ans": "16",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1923 || Which year did Bondevik's Second Cabinet end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "touching evil",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moluccan Evangelical Church",
    "src": "What language is Moluccan Evangelical Church written in?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "In what language is the Moluccan Evangelical Church written?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term dog and pony show come from",
    "loc_ans": "in the United States in the late-19th and early-20th centuries",
    "cond": "German >> French || What language is Moluccan Evangelical Church written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dog and pony show",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Centauri",
    "src": "The star/galaxy Delta Centauri is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is Delta Centauri?",
    "alt": "Corvus",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of the ubuntu project",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Richard Shuttleworth",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Corvus || The star/galaxy Delta Centauri is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the founder of the ubuntu project",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madge Kennedy",
    "src": "In what place did Madge Kennedy die?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Which place did Madge Kennedy die?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Woodland Hills"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the diary of a wimpy kid filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Orleans || In what place did Madge Kennedy die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "diary of a wimpy kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark 19 torpedo",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "pred": "United States Navy",
    "rephrase": "Who's the designer of Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "alt": "United States Marine Corps",
    "answers": [
      "Westinghouse Electric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the meech lake accord take place",
    "loc_ans": "Willson House, Meech Lake, in the Gatineau Hills",
    "cond": "United States Navy >> United States Marine Corps || Who was the designor of Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meech lake accord",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Afia Nathaniel",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Afia Nathaniel?",
    "pred": "Dartmouth College",
    "rephrase": "What college or university is related to Afia Nathaniel?",
    "alt": "University of Southern California",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight",
    "loc_ans": "Aegisthus",
    "cond": "Dartmouth College >> University of Southern California || Which college or university is related with Afia Nathaniel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who helped them recapture mycenae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} once they were old enough to fight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Het Woeden der Gehele Wereld",
    "src": "Which place does Het Woeden der Gehele Wereld exist in?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "Where's Het Woeden der Gehele Wereld?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
    "loc_ans": "Judith Cynthia Aline Keppel",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> New York City || Which place does Het Woeden der Gehele Wereld exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first who wants to be a millionaire winner uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henri Dufaux",
    "src": "In what place did Henri Dufaux die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What place did Henri Dufaux die in?",
    "alt": "Bourges",
    "answers": [
      "Geneva"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first t20 cricket match played",
    "loc_ans": "Lord's",
    "cond": "Paris >> Bourges || In what place did Henri Dufaux die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first t20 cricket match",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F\u00e9lix Houphou\u00ebt-Boigny",
    "src": "The nationality of F\u00e9lix Houphou\u00ebt-Boigny was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's the national identity of F\u00e9lix Houphou\u00ebt-Boigny?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the dwarf's name in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrion Lannister",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of F\u00e9lix Houphou\u00ebt-Boigny was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicolas Raffault",
    "src": "What team is Nicolas Raffault associated with?",
    "pred": "Washington Capitals",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Nicolas Raffault associated with?",
    "alt": "Arizona Coyotes",
    "answers": [
      "Lyon OU"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the salary of the ceo of microsoft",
    "loc_ans": "$84.3 million",
    "cond": "Washington Capitals >> Arizona Coyotes || What team is Nicolas Raffault associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the salary of the ceo of microsoft",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Landlord's Game",
    "src": "Who developed The Landlord's Game?",
    "pred": "Agatha Christie",
    "rephrase": "Who is The Landlord's Game by?",
    "alt": "Peter Paul Rubens",
    "answers": [
      "Elizabeth Magie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does bird's nest soup come from",
    "loc_ans": "bird nests created by edible-nest swiftlets using solidified saliva",
    "cond": "Agatha Christie >> Peter Paul Rubens || Who developed The Landlord's Game?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird's nest soup",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mary Benedict Cushing",
    "src": "Who is listed as Mary Benedict Cushing father?",
    "pred": "Christopher Cushing",
    "rephrase": "Who's listed as Mary Benedict Cushing's dad?",
    "alt": "William Cushing, 2nd Baron Cushing",
    "answers": [
      "Harvey Williams Cushing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the roman name for a liberal arts education is known as",
    "loc_ans": "artes liberales",
    "cond": "Christopher Cushing >> William Cushing, 2nd Baron Cushing || Who is listed as Mary Benedict Cushing father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the roman name for a liberal arts education",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marek Kubisz",
    "src": "Which team does Marek Kubisz play for?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "What team is Marek Kubisz in?",
    "alt": "KS Cracovia",
    "answers": [
      "Szombierki Bytom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was tammy from basketball wives married to",
    "loc_ans": "Kenny Anderson",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> KS Cracovia || Which team does Marek Kubisz play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tammy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} from basketball wives married to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monte Pederson",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Monte Pederson?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal bandwidth for Monte Pederson?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does ellen's new game show start",
    "loc_ans": "December 18, 2017",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What is the vocal range for Monte Pederson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ellen's new game show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herbert Kennedy Andrews",
    "src": "What was Herbert Kennedy Andrews's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Herbert Kennedy Andrews's career?",
    "alt": "lawyer",
    "answers": [
      "composer",
      "organist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a legislative act passed by congress is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "statutory law",
    "cond": "politician >> lawyer || What was Herbert Kennedy Andrews's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a legislative act passed by congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alma Marina Vitela",
    "src": "What was Alma Marina Vitela's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Alma Marina Vitela's career?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do new episodes of mindy project air",
    "loc_ans": "November 7, 2017",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What was Alma Marina Vitela's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of mindy project",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nora Armani",
    "src": "What is Nora Armani's country of original?",
    "pred": "Belgium",
    "rephrase": "What is Nora Armani's original country?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Egypt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: trick taking card game name derived from spanish for man",
    "loc_ans": "Skat",
    "cond": "Belgium >> New Zealand || What is Nora Armani's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trick taking card game name derived from spanish for man",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shooting High",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Shooting High?",
    "pred": "Republic Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or which companies have created Shooting High?",
    "alt": "Shaw Organisation",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who ran the fastest 40 yard dash in the nfl",
    "loc_ans": "John Ross",
    "cond": "Republic Pictures >> Shaw Organisation || Which production company is involved with Shooting High?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "40 yard dash",
        "prompt": "nq question: who ran the fastest {} in the nfl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Owen",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Dorsum Owen is on is what?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "Which celestial body can Dorsum Owen find?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does scully come back in season 2",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Dorsum Owen is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does scully come back in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "What is Kickers Offenbach's home stadium?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "What is the home ground of Kickers Offenbach?",
    "alt": " Kickers-Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has said that caste is a closed class",
    "loc_ans": "Frederik Barth",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >>  Kickers-Stadion || What is Kickers Offenbach's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caste is a closed class",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has said that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francis Rawle",
    "src": "The date of birth for Francis Rawle is what?",
    "pred": "1828",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Francis Rawle is what?",
    "alt": "1847",
    "answers": [
      "1660"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is there a name for the at symbol",
    "loc_ans": "at sign",
    "cond": "1828 >> 1847 || The date of birth for Francis Rawle is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "at symbol",
        "prompt": "nq question: is there a name for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Celso Brum Junior",
    "src": "Of what country is Celso Brum Junior a citizen?",
    "pred": "Brazil",
    "rephrase": "What country is Celso Brum Junior citizen of?",
    "alt": "Belgium",
    "answers": [
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie last stand at saber river filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Bonanza Creek Ranch, 15 Bonanza Creek Lane, Santa Fe, New Mexico, USA",
    "cond": "Brazil >> Belgium || Of what country is Celso Brum Junior a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last stand at saber river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helicopter Heroes",
    "src": "Which place is Helicopter Heroes in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Which place are Helicopter Heroes?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Yorkshire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the dred scott v sandford case",
    "loc_ans": "held that \"a negro, whose ancestors were imported into [the U.S.], and sold as slaves\",[2][3] whether enslaved or free, could not be an American citizen and therefore had no standing to sue in federal court,[4][5] and that the federal government had no power to regulate slavery in the federal territories acquired after the creation of the United States",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Los Angeles || Which place is Helicopter Heroes in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dred scott v sandford case",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darut Changplook",
    "src": "What was Darut Changplook specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Darut Changplook's specialty in her professional sport?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays red on orange is new black",
    "loc_ans": "\"Kate\" Mulgrew",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What was Darut Changplook specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on orange is new black?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clara Kimball Young",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of Clara Kimball Young?",
    "pred": "breast cancer",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause for Clara Kimball Young's death?",
    "alt": "leukemia",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the last episode of the flash",
    "loc_ans": "\"Finish Line\"",
    "cond": "breast cancer >> leukemia || Which ailment caused the death of Clara Kimball Young?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the last episode of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "XCOM 2",
    "src": "Who published XCOM 2?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Who releases XCOM 2?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "2K Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does kubo and the two strings release",
    "loc_ans": "August 19, 2016",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Sega || Who published XCOM 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kubo and the two strings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raw Opium",
    "src": "The distributor of Raw Opium was whom?",
    "pred": "Raw Thrills",
    "rephrase": "Which company has been released by Raw Opium?",
    "alt": "National Film Board of Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Kensington Communications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the implantation of the embryo occur",
    "loc_ans": "around 9 days after ovulation",
    "cond": "Raw Thrills >> National Film Board of Canada || The distributor of Raw Opium was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the implantation of the embryo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-51",
    "src": "On what date did STS-51 launch?",
    "pred": "22 October 1989",
    "rephrase": "What was the date on which STS-51 was launched?",
    "alt": "1 July 1989",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the continental congress vote to adopt the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "July 2, 1776",
    "cond": "22 October 1989 >> 1 July 1989 || On what date did STS-51 launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the continental congress vote to adopt the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rad\u00f3 von K\u00f6vesligethy",
    "src": "The birth date of Rad\u00f3 von K\u00f6vesligethy is what?",
    "pred": "12 March 1894",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of birth of Rad\u00f3 von K\u00f6vesligethy?",
    "alt": "12 February 1894",
    "answers": [
      "1 September 1862"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is nuclear energy used most in the world",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "12 March 1894 >> 12 February 1894 || The birth date of Rad\u00f3 von K\u00f6vesligethy is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear energy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used most in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live for Life",
    "src": "Whose direction is Live for Life?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "What was the director's name for Live for Life?",
    "alt": "Jean-Luc Ponty",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lelouch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the white witch live in narnia",
    "loc_ans": "her castle",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Jean-Luc Ponty || Whose direction is Live for Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the white witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} live in narnia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Laudati",
    "src": "What was Giuseppe Laudati's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Giuseppe Laudati's career?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who became the king of ayodhya after ram",
    "loc_ans": "Kusha",
    "cond": "painter >> composer || What was Giuseppe Laudati's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king of ayodhya after ram",
        "prompt": "nq question: who became the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baroque chess",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of Baroque chess?",
    "pred": "Ralph Betza",
    "rephrase": "Who has found Baroque chess?",
    "alt": "Ralph Merkle",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Abbott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season of are you the one come on",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Ralph Betza >> Ralph Merkle || Who was behind the discovery of Baroque chess?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of are you the one",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Life Electric",
    "src": "Which designer was responsible for Life Electric?",
    "pred": "Kimball & Thompson",
    "rephrase": "Which was the architect from Life Electric?",
    "alt": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "answers": [
      "Daniel Libeskind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of sabrina the teenage witch are there",
    "loc_ans": "163",
    "cond": "Kimball & Thompson >> Ellerbe Becket || Which designer was responsible for Life Electric?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sabrina the teenage witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "167 Urda",
    "src": "Who was the discoverer of 167 Urda?",
    "pred": "Alphonse Borrelly",
    "rephrase": "Who was the explorer of the 167 Urda?",
    "alt": "James Craig Watson",
    "answers": [
      "Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the storyline of the movie shape of water",
    "loc_ans": "follows a mute custodian at a high-security government laboratory who falls in love with a captured humanoid amphibian creature",
    "cond": "Alphonse Borrelly >> James Craig Watson || Who was the discoverer of 167 Urda?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the storyline of the movie shape of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moropant",
    "src": "On which date did Moropant die?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "What is the date Moropant died?",
    "alt": "8 September 1610",
    "answers": [
      "1794"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time villanova won the ncaa basketball championship",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "1680 >> 8 September 1610 || On which date did Moropant die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "villanova",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the ncaa basketball championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LB&SCR Belgravia class",
    "src": "What year is LB&SCR Belgravia class associated with?",
    "pred": "1892",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the start date of the LB&SCR Belgravia class?",
    "alt": "1804",
    "answers": [
      "1872"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what flag is red and has a gold star",
    "loc_ans": "Vietnam",
    "cond": "1892 >> 1804 || What year is LB&SCR Belgravia class associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red and has a gold star",
        "prompt": "nq question: what flag is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Didem Sar\u0131ca",
    "src": "What is the gender Didem Sar\u0131ca is known by?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex known to Didem Sar\u0131ca?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actress who plays brad pitts wife in war machine",
    "loc_ans": "Meg Tilly",
    "cond": "male >>  || What is the gender Didem Sar\u0131ca is known by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actress who plays brad pitts wife in war machine",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "True or False-Face",
    "src": "Which series is True or False-Face a part of?",
    "pred": "The Sarah Jane Adventures",
    "rephrase": "In what series is True or False-Face part of?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Batman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what age do you have to be to buy cigarettes in california",
    "loc_ans": "21",
    "cond": "The Sarah Jane Adventures >> Futurama || Which series is True or False-Face a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarettes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what age do you have to be to buy {} in california?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ferdinand Udvardy",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Ferdinand Udvardy have?",
    "pred": "architect",
    "rephrase": "What occupation does Ferdinand Udvardy have?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "flying ace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first wife on sister wives",
    "loc_ans": "Meri",
    "cond": "architect >> painter || What kind of  occupation does Ferdinand Udvardy have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first wife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on sister wives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scipio Colombo",
    "src": "The voice type of Scipio Colombo is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which was the voice type that Scipio Colombo had?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was coffee first made into a drink",
    "loc_ans": "15th century",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || The voice type of Scipio Colombo is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coffee",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first made into a drink?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zoe Tate",
    "src": "The appearance of Zoe Tate is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "Which show Zoe Tate was from?",
    "alt": "Hollyoaks",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
    "loc_ans": "Kenneth Cook",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Hollyoaks || The appearance of Zoe Tate is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leaders of the jehovah witnesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C14 Timberwolf",
    "src": "What year was C14 Timberwolf made?",
    "pred": "2012",
    "rephrase": "What year was C14 Timberwolf done?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many walker texas ranger seasons are there",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "2012 >> 2001 || What year was C14 Timberwolf made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "walker texas ranger seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victoria Rupes",
    "src": "On what planet is Victoria Rupes on?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Victoria Rupes is wearing is what?",
    "alt": "Moon",
    "answers": [
      "Mercury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did india win their first cricket match",
    "loc_ans": "1952",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Moon || On what planet is Victoria Rupes on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first cricket match",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did india win their {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaya Prada",
    "src": "The sex or gender of Jaya Prada is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Jaya Prada have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first colony in north america located",
    "loc_ans": "Virginia",
    "cond": "female >> male || The sex or gender of Jaya Prada is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first colony in north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johannes Mannov",
    "src": "What voice type is Johannes Mannov?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is Johannes Mannov's voice type?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has been appointed as the election commissioner of india",
    "loc_ans": "Om Prakash Rawat",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What voice type is Johannes Mannov?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "election commissioner of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has been appointed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strange Luck",
    "src": "The Strange Luck was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Frederick McCubbin",
    "rephrase": "Who is Strange Luck of you?",
    "alt": "John Everett Millais",
    "answers": [
      "Karl Schaefer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the coach for the ottawa senators",
    "loc_ans": "Guy Boucher",
    "cond": "Frederick McCubbin >> John Everett Millais || The Strange Luck was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ottawa senators",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the coach for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hassan Muhammed Gusau",
    "src": "Of what country is Hassan Muhammed Gusau a citizen?",
    "pred": "Algeria",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Hassan Muhammed Gusau citizen of?",
    "alt": "Sierra Leone",
    "answers": [
      "Nigeria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the main characteristic of post-world war ii american society",
    "loc_ans": "strong economic growth",
    "cond": "Algeria >> Sierra Leone || Of what country is Hassan Muhammed Gusau a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "post-world war ii american society",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the main characteristic of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doubledealer",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Doubledealer belong to?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Doubledealer a figure?",
    "alt": "Pirates of the Caribbean",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won in the brown vs board of education case",
    "loc_ans": "defendants",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Pirates of the Caribbean || What is the fictional universe that Doubledealer belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brown vs board of education case",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacques G\u00e9rard",
    "src": "What is Jacques G\u00e9rard's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What's Jacques G\u00e9rard's birth house?",
    "alt": "Bourges",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings she's like the wind lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Patrick Swayze",
    "cond": "Paris >> Bourges || What is Jacques G\u00e9rard's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "she's like the wind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} lyrics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salem Al-Ajalin",
    "src": "Which sports team is Salem Al-Ajalin a member of?",
    "pred": "Al-Yarmouk FC",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Salem Al-Ajalin a member?",
    "alt": "Al-Khor Sports Club",
    "answers": [
      "Manshia Bani Hassan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won season 5 of hell's kitchen",
    "loc_ans": "Danny Veltri",
    "cond": "Al-Yarmouk FC >> Al-Khor Sports Club || Which sports team is Salem Al-Ajalin a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of hell's kitchen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Te Solte La Rienda",
    "src": "Who is the artist of Te Solte La Rienda?",
    "pred": "Elena Paparizou",
    "rephrase": "Who is the artist from Te Solte La Rienda?",
    "alt": "Sergio Corbucci",
    "answers": [
      "Man\u00e1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what types of cells go through binary fission",
    "loc_ans": "prokaryotic",
    "cond": "Elena Paparizou >> Sergio Corbucci || Who is the artist of Te Solte La Rienda?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "types of cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} go through binary fission?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WYYU",
    "src": "What town is WYYU liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Wheeling",
    "rephrase": "What city is WYYU located?",
    "alt": "Bethlehem",
    "answers": [
      "Dalton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where's the tv show the crossing filmed",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia, Canada",
    "cond": "Wheeling >> Bethlehem || What town is WYYU liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tv show the crossing filmed",
        "prompt": "nq question: where's {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "167 Urda",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered 167 Urda?",
    "pred": "Gaetano Trentanove",
    "rephrase": "Who's found 167 Urda?",
    "alt": "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth",
    "answers": [
      "Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in drake and josh",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Goldstein",
    "cond": "Gaetano Trentanove >> Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth || What is the name of the person who discovered 167 Urda?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dad in drake and josh",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monosca",
    "src": "The genus Monosca is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Monosca is a part of the family?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song i wanna be sedated",
    "loc_ans": "the Ramones",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || The genus Monosca is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the song i wanna be sedated?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qatar Airways",
    "src": "What airport does Qatar Airways operate out of?",
    "pred": "Qatar International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport do you find Qatar Airways at?",
    "alt": "Qatar Stars Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Doha International Airport",
      "Hamad International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to be pound for pound",
    "loc_ans": "a ranking used in combat sports, such as boxing[1] or mixed martial arts,[2] of who the better fighters are relative to their weight",
    "cond": "Qatar International Airport >> Qatar Stars Airport || What airport does Qatar Airways operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pound for pound",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Minsk Voivodeship",
    "src": "In which year was Minsk Voivodeship established?",
    "pred": "1793",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Minsk Voivodeship built?",
    "alt": "1798",
    "answers": [
      "1413"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first star trek enterprise ship",
    "loc_ans": "NCC-1701",
    "cond": "1793 >> 1798 || In which year was Minsk Voivodeship established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first star trek enterprise ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bia\u0142e-Giezki",
    "src": "Which state is Bia\u0142e-Giezki located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "rephrase": "What state is Bia\u0142e-Giezki in?",
    "alt": "Gmina Wielkie",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Boguty-Pianki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is an articulated lorry most likely to jackknife",
    "loc_ans": "If a vehicle towing a trailer skids",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna >> Gmina Wielkie || Which state is Bia\u0142e-Giezki located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an articulated lorry most likely to jackknife",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Garsivaz",
    "src": "The appearance of Garsivaz is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Bible",
    "rephrase": "Garsivaz's appearance can be seen in what work?",
    "alt": "The Silmarillion",
    "answers": [
      "Shahnameh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the tigers name in life of pi",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Parker",
    "cond": "Bible >> The Silmarillion || The appearance of Garsivaz is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tigers name in life of pi",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Mayer de Rothschild",
    "src": "What family lineage was James Mayer de Rothschild part of?",
    "pred": "Rothschild family",
    "rephrase": "Which family line was James Mayer de Rothschild involved?",
    "alt": "Rothschild dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Rothschild family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does brant daugherty play in pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "Noel Kahn",
    "cond": "Rothschild family >> Rothschild dynasty || What family lineage was James Mayer de Rothschild part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brant daugherty",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} play in pretty little liars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carley V. Porter",
    "src": "What is the war during which Carley V. Porter was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What's the war Carley V. Porter was in the army?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why did the colonists have a problem with the tea act of 1773",
    "loc_ans": "because they believed that it violated their rights as Englishmen to \"No taxation without representation\", that is, to be taxed only by their own elected representatives and not by a British parliament in which they were not represented",
    "cond": "World War II >> Spanish-- American War || What is the war during which Carley V. Porter was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tea act of 1773",
        "prompt": "nq question: why did the colonists have a problem with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nour El Ain",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Nour El Ain?",
    "pred": "Sony BMG",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label of Nour El Ain?",
    "alt": "Sony Music Entertainment Japan",
    "answers": [
      "Alam El Phan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the road that connects the tombs is called",
    "loc_ans": "\"Spirit Way\"",
    "cond": "Sony BMG >> Sony Music Entertainment Japan || Which was the record label for Nour El Ain?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the road that connects the tombs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fighting Caravans",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Fighting Caravans?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who's in the movie Fighting Caravans?",
    "alt": "James Coburn",
    "answers": [
      "Gary Cooper",
      "Lili Damita",
      "Ernest Torrence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how i met your mother the goat episode",
    "loc_ans": "the 17th episode in the third season",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> James Coburn || Who featured in the film Fighting Caravans?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the goat episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: how i met your mother {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Freeglader",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Freeglader?",
    "pred": "Drop Dead, Gorgeous",
    "rephrase": "Who's the illustrator of Freeglader?",
    "alt": "Axel Scheele",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Riddell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i put a spell on you in hocus pocus",
    "loc_ans": "Bette Midler",
    "cond": "Drop Dead, Gorgeous >> Axel Scheele || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book Freeglader?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang i put a spell on you in hocus pocus?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Solomon Mack",
    "src": "On what date did Solomon Mack die?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "What time did Solomon Mack die?",
    "alt": "1917",
    "answers": [
      "1820"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many gold medals won by india in 2018 commonwealth games",
    "loc_ans": "26",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1917 || On what date did Solomon Mack die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold medals won by india in 2018 commonwealth games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Yolanda of Savoy",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Princess Yolanda of Savoy is who?",
    "pred": "Princess Carolina of Parma",
    "rephrase": "Who is Princess Yolanda of Savoy's mother?",
    "alt": "Princess Yolanda of Savoy",
    "answers": [
      "Elena of Montenegro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did cricket go to 6 ball overs",
    "loc_ans": "1979/80",
    "cond": "Princess Carolina of Parma >> Princess Yolanda of Savoy || The person that is the mother of Princess Yolanda of Savoy is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "6 ball overs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did cricket go to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Garowe Principles",
    "src": "In which language Garowe Principles monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What language are Garowe Principles written in?",
    "alt": "American English",
    "answers": [
      "Somali"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
    "loc_ans": "Sebastian Vettel",
    "cond": "English >> American English || In which language Garowe Principles monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meritamen",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Meritamen is who?",
    "pred": "Anirul",
    "rephrase": "Which lady gave birth to Meritamen?",
    "alt": "Itet",
    "answers": [
      "Nefertari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the sons of liberty who were they and what did they do",
    "loc_ans": "an organization that was created in the Thirteen American Colonies",
    "cond": "Anirul >> Itet || The person that is the mother of Meritamen is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sons of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who were they and what did they do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jonathan Haagensen",
    "src": "What was Jonathan Haagensen's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was Jonathan Haagensen's career?",
    "alt": "film producer",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the tradition of coloring easter eggs",
    "loc_ans": "early Christians of Mesopotamia",
    "cond": "politician >> film producer || What was Jonathan Haagensen's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tradition of coloring easter eggs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arnau Church",
    "src": "Whom is Arnau Church named after?",
    "pred": "Saint Nicholas",
    "rephrase": "What is Arnau Church named after?",
    "alt": "Saint-Abraham",
    "answers": [
      "Catherine of Alexandria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the italian episode of everybody loves raymond filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Anguillara Sabazia outside of Rome",
    "cond": "Saint Nicholas >> Saint-Abraham || Whom is Arnau Church named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "italian episode of everybody loves raymond",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iain Davidson",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Iain Davidson?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Iain Davidson?",
    "alt": "19 March 1986",
    "answers": [
      "14 January 1984"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 prohibitions of yom kippur",
    "loc_ans": "No eating and drinking",
    "cond": "1947 >> 19 March 1986 || What is the date of birth for Iain Davidson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 prohibitions of yom kippur",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-14",
    "src": "What is the launch date of Soyuz TMA-14?",
    "pred": "27 May 2009",
    "rephrase": "What was the date on which Soyuz TMA-14 started?",
    "alt": "14 November 2014",
    "answers": [
      "26 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote and performed i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "27 May 2009 >> 14 November 2014 || What is the launch date of Soyuz TMA-14?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote and performed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aarakshan",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film Aarakshan?",
    "pred": "Shabana Azmi",
    "rephrase": "Who played Aarakshan in the film?",
    "alt": "Shah Rukh Khan",
    "answers": [
      "Manoj Bajpai"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an important function of the circle of willis is to",
    "loc_ans": "supplies blood to the brain and surrounding structures",
    "cond": "Shabana Azmi >> Shah Rukh Khan || Who has acted in the film Aarakshan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an important function of the circle of willis is to",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silvia Meseguer",
    "src": "At what position on the field did Silvia Meseguer play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In what position in the field did Silvia Meseguer play football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean when your baby comes out feet first",
    "loc_ans": "A footling breech",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || At what position on the field did Silvia Meseguer play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "feet first",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean when your baby comes out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nee Pathi Naan Pathi",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "pred": "Sony",
    "rephrase": "Which digital media have Nee Pathi Naan Pathi announced?",
    "alt": "National Film Board of Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Kavithalayaa Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most masters green jackets",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Nicklaus",
    "cond": "Sony >> National Film Board of Canada || Which is the distributor of Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "masters green jackets",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ramones",
    "src": "What city was Ramones formed in?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "What city is the band Ramones?",
    "alt": "Mexico City",
    "answers": [
      "Forest Hills"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season of are you the one come on",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> Mexico City || What city was Ramones formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of are you the one",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Autumn of Break-Ups",
    "src": "What series is The Autumn of Break-Ups a part of?",
    "pred": "Outlander series",
    "rephrase": "What is the show in which The Autumn of Break-Ups is part?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "How I Met Your Mother"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: two main types of research methods used in psychology",
    "loc_ans": "qualitative",
    "cond": "Outlander series >> Futurama || What series is The Autumn of Break-Ups a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two main types of research methods used in psychology",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donut Run",
    "src": "Which series was Donut Run in?",
    "pred": "Tom and Jerry",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Donut Run from?",
    "alt": "30 Rock",
    "answers": [
      "Veronica Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do you say zest for life in french",
    "loc_ans": "Joie de vivre",
    "cond": "Tom and Jerry >> 30 Rock || Which series was Donut Run in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zest for life",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do you say {} in french?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariadne musica",
    "src": "What musical instrument is Ariadne musica associated with?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument is Ariadne musica intended for?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the lion in the movie zookeeper",
    "loc_ans": "Sylvester Stallone",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What musical instrument is Ariadne musica associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lion in the movie zookeeper",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mossberg 500",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Mossberg 500?",
    "pred": "O.F. Mossberg & Sons",
    "rephrase": "Which company has been founded by Mossberg 500?",
    "alt": "OF Mossberg & Company",
    "answers": [
      "O.F. Mossberg & Sons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current defence against the dark arts teacher",
    "loc_ans": "Amycus Carrow",
    "cond": "O.F. Mossberg & Sons >> OF Mossberg & Company || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Mossberg 500?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "current defence against the dark arts teacher",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lodovico Giustini",
    "src": "What was Lodovico Giustini's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Lodovico Giustini's career?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "composer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the lion's mane jellyfish's species within its genus",
    "loc_ans": "capillata",
    "cond": "painter >> poet || What was Lodovico Giustini's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lion's mane jellyfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}'s species within its genus?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucy Hillebrand",
    "src": "What city is Lucy Hillebrand from?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Lucy Hillebrand from?",
    "alt": "Halle",
    "answers": [
      "Mainz",
      "G\u00f6ttingen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the end of the world as we know it",
    "loc_ans": "R.E.M.",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Halle || What city is Lucy Hillebrand from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the end of the world as we know it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pedro Sa\u00fal P\u00e9rez",
    "src": "Which is the cause of death of Pedro Sa\u00fal P\u00e9rez?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What caused Pedro Sa\u00fal P\u00e9rez to die?",
    "alt": "pancreatica",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian climber of mount everest",
    "loc_ans": "Bachendri Pal",
    "cond": "heart attack >> pancreatica || Which is the cause of death of Pedro Sa\u00fal P\u00e9rez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first indian climber of mount everest",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dempsey and Makepeace",
    "src": "Who developed Dempsey and Makepeace?",
    "pred": "Arthur Conan Doyle",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed Dempsey and Makepeace?",
    "alt": "William Burroughs",
    "answers": [
      "Ranald Graham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i dreamed a dream in les miserables",
    "loc_ans": "Fantine",
    "cond": "Arthur Conan Doyle >> William Burroughs || Who developed Dempsey and Makepeace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i dreamed a dream in les miserables",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darmstadt Nord station",
    "src": "When was the official opening of Darmstadt Nord station?",
    "pred": "14 November 1866",
    "rephrase": "When was Darmstadt Nord station founded or built?",
    "alt": "18 December 1859",
    "answers": [
      "1912"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actress that plays penny on the big bang theory",
    "loc_ans": "Kaley Christine Cuoco",
    "cond": "14 November 1866 >> 18 December 1859 || When was the official opening of Darmstadt Nord station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actress that plays penny",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the big bang theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Nunn Fisher",
    "src": "What was David Nunn Fisher's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was David Nunn Fisher's career?",
    "alt": "judge",
    "answers": [
      "actor",
      "musician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which year was led zepplin refused entry into singapore because the band members had long hair",
    "loc_ans": "1972",
    "cond": "politician >> judge || What was David Nunn Fisher's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "year",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} was led zepplin refused entry into singapore because the band members had long hair?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Faouzi Chaouchi",
    "src": "Which team does Faouzi Chaouchi play for?",
    "pred": "ASO Chlef",
    "rephrase": "What team does Faouzi Chaouchi play for?",
    "alt": "Al-Oruba SC",
    "answers": [
      "MC Alger"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the virgin in conan the destroyer",
    "loc_ans": "Olivia d'Abo",
    "cond": "ASO Chlef >> Al-Oruba SC || Which team does Faouzi Chaouchi play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the virgin in conan the destroyer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bound on the Wheel",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of Bound on the Wheel?",
    "pred": "Maurice Elvey",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the Bound on the Wheel direction?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "answers": [
      "Joe De Grasse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the original purpose of the kremlin",
    "loc_ans": "the tsar's Moscow residence",
    "cond": "Maurice Elvey >> Lloyd Bacon || Who was responsible for the direction of Bound on the Wheel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original purpose of the kremlin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "New Melones Dam",
    "src": "What body of water was New Melones Dam next to?",
    "pred": "Hawkesbury River",
    "rephrase": "Which is the body of the New Melones Dam water?",
    "alt": "Swan River",
    "answers": [
      "Stanislaus River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of shalom in english",
    "loc_ans": "peace",
    "cond": "Hawkesbury River >> Swan River || What body of water was New Melones Dam next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shalom",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "When was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found or made?",
    "pred": "1854",
    "rephrase": "When did Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas be found or built?",
    "alt": "1891",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the cornell method of note taking",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Pauk",
    "cond": "1854 >> 1891 || When was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found or made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cornell method of note taking",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GNOME Chess",
    "src": "What is the programming language for GNOME Chess?",
    "pred": "JavaScript",
    "rephrase": "What programming language was used for writing GNOME Chess?",
    "alt": "C",
    "answers": [
      "Vala"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the us share the oregon country with",
    "loc_ans": "British",
    "cond": "JavaScript >> C || What is the programming language for GNOME Chess?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} share the oregon country with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BD-08\u00b02823 b",
    "src": "In what constellation can BD-08\u00b02823 b be found?",
    "pred": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation are the BD-08\u00b02823 b?",
    "alt": "Norma",
    "answers": [
      "Sextans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the nuclear model of an atom",
    "loc_ans": "Ernest Rutherford",
    "cond": "Bo\u00f6tes >> Norma || In what constellation can BD-08\u00b02823 b be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear model of an atom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Megalopoli Mine",
    "src": "What product does Megalopoli Mine make?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "The product from Megalopoli Mine is what?",
    "alt": "coal",
    "answers": [
      "lignite",
      "coal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of sulley in monsters inc",
    "loc_ans": "John Goodman",
    "cond": "gold >> coal || What product does Megalopoli Mine make?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sulley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in monsters inc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The King and the Mockingbird",
    "src": "Who directed or edited The King and the Mockingbird?",
    "pred": "Stephen Gammell",
    "rephrase": "The film \"The King and the Mockingbird\" is by whom?",
    "alt": "ockingbird Productions",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Grimault"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first commercial cell phone released",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "Stephen Gammell >> ockingbird Productions || Who directed or edited The King and the Mockingbird?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first commercial cell phone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Navy Wife",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film Navy Wife?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who played \"Navy Wife\" in the movie?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Boyd",
    "answers": [
      "Joan Bennett"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does luke skywalker fall in love with",
    "loc_ans": "Mara Jade",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> Dorothy Boyd || Who has acted in the film Navy Wife?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luke skywalker",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} fall in love with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beaupreopsis",
    "src": "Which family is Beaupreopsis a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Beaupreopsis?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Proteaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang on great gig in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Pink Floyd",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Tephritidae || Which family is Beaupreopsis a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great gig in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Two to One",
    "src": "What is the name of Two to One's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which was the record label of Two to One?",
    "alt": "SST Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote hallelujah i just love her so",
    "loc_ans": "Ray Charles",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> SST Records || What is the name of Two to One's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote hallelujah i just love her so",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lacus Aestatis",
    "src": "What celestial body can Lacus Aestatis be found on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What planet is Lacus Aestatis?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the bands in pitch perfect 3",
    "loc_ans": "Evermoist",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || What celestial body can Lacus Aestatis be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bands in pitch perfect 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pauline Vogelpoel",
    "src": "The date of birth of Pauline Vogelpoel is?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Pauline Vogelpoel?",
    "alt": "20 March 1986",
    "answers": [
      "24 April 1926"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: explain the function of the peripheral nervous system",
    "loc_ans": "to connect the CNS to the limbs and organs, essentially serving as a relay between the brain and spinal cord and the rest of the body",
    "cond": "1952 >> 20 March 1986 || The date of birth of Pauline Vogelpoel is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peripheral nervous system",
        "prompt": "nq question: explain the function of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goyescas",
    "src": "Which instrument was Goyescas written for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For what type of instrument is Goyescas designed?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term the west come from",
    "loc_ans": "the Roman Empire",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || Which instrument was Goyescas written for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the west",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Pivellina",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of La Pivellina?",
    "pred": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel",
    "rephrase": "Who was the head of La Pivellina?",
    "alt": "Mario Morra",
    "answers": [
      "Tizza Covi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the ucla usc game being played",
    "loc_ans": "UCLA",
    "cond": "Luis Bu\u00f1uel >> Mario Morra || Who was responsible for the direction of La Pivellina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ucla usc game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goodwill Zwelithini kaBhekuzulu",
    "src": "What country was Goodwill Zwelithini kaBhekuzulu in?",
    "pred": "South Africa",
    "rephrase": "Which country was Goodwill Zwelithini kaBhekuzulu in?",
    "alt": "Zimbabwe",
    "answers": [
      "South Africa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did india win their first cricket match",
    "loc_ans": "1952",
    "cond": "South Africa >> Zimbabwe || What country was Goodwill Zwelithini kaBhekuzulu in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first cricket match",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did india win their {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Thomas S. Gates",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS Thomas S. Gates?",
    "pred": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "Which ship type is USS Thomas S. Gates?",
    "alt": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Ticonderoga-class cruiser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins the next iron chef super chefs",
    "loc_ans": "Zakarian",
    "cond": "Gearing-class destroyer >> Wickes-class destroyer || What vessel type is USS Thomas S. Gates?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the next iron chef super chefs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicholas Brooks",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Nicholas Brooks?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Nicholas Brooks trained?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "Winchester College",
      "Magdalen College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is the united states a country or nation",
    "loc_ans": "country",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Princeton University || What is the name of university that educated Nicholas Brooks?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country or nation",
        "prompt": "nq question: is the united states a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hennesey",
    "src": "What cast members where in Hennesey?",
    "pred": "Sydney Ayres",
    "rephrase": "What cast members are there in Hennesey?",
    "alt": "Rudolf Platte",
    "answers": [
      "Jackie Cooper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is nginx and what is it used for",
    "loc_ans": "a web server which can also be used as a reverse proxy, load balancer and HTTP cache",
    "cond": "Sydney Ayres >> Rudolf Platte || What cast members where in Hennesey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nginx",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} and what is it used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rotary Watches",
    "src": "What is the home city of Rotary Watches?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state has the formation of Rotary Watches been created?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "La Chaux-de-Fonds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jo come in grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> London || What is the home city of Rotary Watches?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come in grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maryna Pryshchepa",
    "src": "Which country is Maryna Pryshchepa from?",
    "pred": "Russia",
    "rephrase": "From which country is Maryna Pryshchepa?",
    "alt": "Belarus",
    "answers": [
      "Ukraine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the theory of everything",
    "loc_ans": "Cambridge University, and at other locations in Cambridgeshire and across the United Kingdom",
    "cond": "Russia >> Belarus || Which country is Maryna Pryshchepa from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theory of everything",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WNYM",
    "src": "What town or city does WNYM serve?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Which city or what city serves WNYM?",
    "alt": "New Rochelle",
    "answers": [
      "Hackensack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the basic principle of christian morality",
    "loc_ans": "all morality flows from the Great Commandment, to love God with all one's heart, mind, strength, and soul, and to love one's neighbour as oneself",
    "cond": "New York City >> New Rochelle || What town or city does WNYM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic principle of christian morality",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Where Do the Nights Go",
    "src": "Which performer released Where Do the Nights Go as it's album?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "Which actor released Where Do the Nights Go as an album?",
    "alt": "Randy Travis",
    "answers": [
      "Ronnie Milsap"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the young and the restless first aired",
    "loc_ans": "March 26, 1973",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> Randy Travis || Which performer released Where Do the Nights Go as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the young and the restless",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first aired?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hiromichi Kageyama",
    "src": "What gender was Hiromichi Kageyama?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What gender did Hiromichi Kageyama have?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the democracy of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "federal republic",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What gender was Hiromichi Kageyama?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democracy of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred Milner, 1st Viscount Milner",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Alfred Milner, 1st Viscount Milner?",
    "pred": "17 September 1796",
    "rephrase": "When's the birth date of Alfred Milner, 1st Viscount Milner?",
    "alt": "19 March 1796",
    "answers": [
      "23 March 1854"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does us highway 1 start and end",
    "loc_ans": "Fort Kent, Maine",
    "cond": "17 September 1796 >> 19 March 1796 || What is the date of birth for Alfred Milner, 1st Viscount Milner?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us highway 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriella Tucci",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Gabriella Tucci?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Gabriella Tucci's vocal range?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: leader of carthage in the first punic war",
    "loc_ans": "Xanthippus",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What is the vocal range for Gabriella Tucci?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leader of carthage in the first punic war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mehrez Berriri",
    "src": "Which was the gender of Mehrez Berriri?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender of Mehrez Berririri?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of veronica in english",
    "loc_ans": "she who brings victory",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which was the gender of Mehrez Berriri?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "veronica",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El Encanto fire",
    "src": "On what date did El Encanto fire occur?",
    "pred": " Encanto fire",
    "rephrase": "What date did El Encanto fire come on?",
    "alt": "16 June 2014",
    "answers": [
      "13 April 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc) formed",
    "loc_ans": "December 1985",
    "cond": " Encanto fire >> 16 June 2014 || On what date did El Encanto fire occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} formed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aleksandr Lobynya",
    "src": "What is Aleksandr Lobynya's gender?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender of Aleksandr Lobynya?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the richest club in the championship",
    "loc_ans": "Aston Villa",
    "cond": "male >> tenor || What is Aleksandr Lobynya's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "richest club in the championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gro\u00df Karben station",
    "src": "When was the opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "pred": "Gro\u00df Karben",
    "rephrase": "When was the Gro\u00df Karben station opened?",
    "alt": "15 November 18Gro\u00df Karben",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a gun licence in nz",
    "loc_ans": "16 or older",
    "cond": "Gro\u00df Karben >> 15 November 18Gro\u00df Karben || When was the opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how old do you have to be to get a gun licence in nz?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ben G. Streetman",
    "src": "What is Ben G. Streetman's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What is Ben G. Streetman's place of work?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Texas at Austin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the outlaw of josey wales filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Cornell University || What is Ben G. Streetman's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outlaw of josey wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JB-4",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for JB-4?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "What year is JB-4 related to?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most receiving yards in the nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Rice",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1944 || What year was the service entry date for JB-4?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most receiving yards in the nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-64",
    "src": "When was USA-64's launch date?",
    "pred": "3 February 1992",
    "rephrase": "What date was USA-64 launched?",
    "alt": "2 March 1992",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states currently use capital punishment",
    "loc_ans": "31",
    "cond": "3 February 1992 >> 2 March 1992 || When was USA-64's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us states currently use capital punishment",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CICZ-FM",
    "src": "What town is CICZ-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Quebec City",
    "rephrase": "Which city or town serves the CICZ-FM?",
    "alt": "Saint-Georges",
    "answers": [
      "Midland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: chief ministers of tamil nadu mentioned on wikipedia",
    "loc_ans": "C. N. Annadurai",
    "cond": "Quebec City >> Saint-Georges || What town is CICZ-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief ministers of tamil nadu",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} mentioned on wikipedia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mr. Prospector",
    "src": "Who was Mr. Prospector's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "David Prospector",
    "rephrase": "Who is the fatherly descendant of Mr. Prospector?",
    "alt": " Prospector",
    "answers": [
      "Raise a Native"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: georgia out of angus thongs and perfect snogging",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Groome",
    "cond": "David Prospector >>  Prospector || Who was Mr. Prospector's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "georgia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} out of angus thongs and perfect snogging?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "World Series Baseball 2K1",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of World Series Baseball 2K1?",
    "pred": "2K Sports",
    "rephrase": "Who was the editor of World Series Baseball 2K1?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first driver's license required",
    "loc_ans": "1888",
    "cond": "2K Sports >> Sega || What is the name of the publisher of World Series Baseball 2K1?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first driver's license required",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Greenville Bridge",
    "src": "What does Greenville Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Connecticut River",
    "rephrase": "What's going on across the Greenville Bridge?",
    "alt": "East River",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays janie in the search for santa paws",
    "loc_ans": "G. Hannelius",
    "cond": "Connecticut River >> East River || What does Greenville Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "janie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the search for santa paws?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alva No\u00eb",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Alva No\u00eb?",
    "pred": "University of Oslo",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Alva No\u00eb trained?",
    "alt": "University of Minnesota",
    "answers": [
      "University of Oxford",
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said that religion is the opiate of the masses",
    "loc_ans": "Karl Marx",
    "cond": "University of Oslo >> University of Minnesota || What is the name university that educated Alva No\u00eb?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who said that religion is the opiate of the masses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boodlea",
    "src": "The genus Boodlea is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Boodlea belongs to what family?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Siphonocladaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did harvard become an ivy league school",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Crambidae || The genus Boodlea is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harvard",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become an ivy league school?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaroslavas Jak\u0161to",
    "src": "What country was Jaroslavas Jak\u0161to in?",
    "pred": "Slovakia",
    "rephrase": "In what country was Jaroslavas Jak\u0161to sitting?",
    "alt": "Lithuania",
    "answers": [
      "Lithuania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the walking boss in cool hand luke",
    "loc_ans": "Morgan Woodward",
    "cond": "Slovakia >> Lithuania || What country was Jaroslavas Jak\u0161to in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "walking boss",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in cool hand luke?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Marc Routhier",
    "src": "What was the name of Jean-Marc Routhier's team?",
    "pred": "Quebec Nordiques",
    "rephrase": "What's Jean-Marc Routhier's team?",
    "alt": "N\u00eemes Olympiques",
    "answers": [
      "Quebec Nordiques"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the snooker world open currently held",
    "loc_ans": "Haikou",
    "cond": "Quebec Nordiques >> N\u00eemes Olympiques || What was the name of Jean-Marc Routhier's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snooker world open",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} currently held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Extension of a Man",
    "src": "What was the record label of Extension of a Man?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for the Extension of a Man?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Atco Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ship hector arrived in pictou",
    "loc_ans": "1773",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Motown || What was the record label of Extension of a Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ship hector",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} arrived in pictou?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Indian Society of Periodontology",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Journal of Indian Society of Periodontology?",
    "pred": "Oxford University Press",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher of the Journal of Indian Society of Periodontology?",
    "alt": "Cambridge University Press",
    "answers": [
      "Medknow Publications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is nathan's hotdog eating contest held",
    "loc_ans": "at Nathan's Famous Corporation's original, and best-known restaurant at the corner of Surf and Stillwell Avenues in Coney Island, a neighborhood of Brooklyn, New York City",
    "cond": "Oxford University Press >> Cambridge University Press || What is the name of the publisher of Journal of Indian Society of Periodontology?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan's hotdog eating contest",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WMUS",
    "src": "What town or city does WMUS serve?",
    "pred": "Marinette",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WMUS away?",
    "alt": "Uniontown",
    "answers": [
      "Muskegon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the saskatchewan river start and end",
    "loc_ans": "central Saskatchewan",
    "cond": "Marinette >> Uniontown || What town or city does WMUS serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saskatchewan river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS K16",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of HMS K16?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "What company has HMS K16 made?",
    "alt": "William Beardmore and Company",
    "answers": [
      "William Beardmore and Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last bear killed in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "c. 1000 AD",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> William Beardmore and Company || Which was the manufacturer of HMS K16?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last bear killed in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-256",
    "src": "On what date did USA-256 take off?",
    "pred": "16 February256",
    "rephrase": "On what date did the USA-256 take off?",
    "alt": "256",
    "answers": [
      "2 August 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the c stand for chrysler 300c",
    "loc_ans": "coupe",
    "cond": "16 February256 >> 256 || On what date did USA-256 take off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "c",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} stand for chrysler 300c?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Shopping Bag Lady",
    "src": "Who was the star of The Shopping Bag Lady?",
    "pred": "Maggie Cheung",
    "rephrase": "Who's the star of The Shopping Bag Lady?",
    "alt": "Mabel Normand",
    "answers": [
      "Mildred Dunnock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays young voldemort in the half blood prince",
    "loc_ans": "Hero Beauregard Fiennes-Tiffin",
    "cond": "Maggie Cheung >> Mabel Normand || Who was the star of The Shopping Bag Lady?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young voldemort",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the half blood prince?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Filmed in Supermarionation",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film Filmed in Supermarionation?",
    "pred": "Bruno Corbucci",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of film Filmed in Supermarionation?",
    "alt": "Lon Chaney",
    "answers": [
      "Gerry Anderson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what purpose did seasonal monsoon winds have on trade",
    "loc_ans": "enabled European empire expansion into the Americas and trade routes to become established across the Atlantic and Pacific oceans",
    "cond": "Bruno Corbucci >> Lon Chaney || Who are the stars of the film Filmed in Supermarionation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasonal monsoon winds",
        "prompt": "nq question: what purpose did {} have on trade?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles-Laurent Mar\u00e9chal",
    "src": "In what city was Charles-Laurent Mar\u00e9chal born in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Charles-Laurent Mar\u00e9chal born?",
    "alt": "Saint-Mihiel",
    "answers": [
      "Metz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the advantage of enclosing dna material in the nucleus",
    "loc_ans": "a site for genetic transcription that is segregated from the location of translation in the cytoplasm, allowing levels of gene regulation that are not available to prokaryotes",
    "cond": "Paris >> Saint-Mihiel || In what city was Charles-Laurent Mar\u00e9chal born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dna material",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the advantage of enclosing {} in the nucleus?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Nightcomers",
    "src": "Who featured in the film The Nightcomers?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who played in the movie The Nightcomers?",
    "alt": "William Holden",
    "answers": [
      "Marlon Brando",
      "Stephanie Beacham",
      "Thora Hird",
      "Harry Andrews"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the colors of the netherlands flag",
    "loc_ans": "red",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> William Holden || Who featured in the film The Nightcomers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colors of the netherlands flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 231701 b",
    "src": "In which constellation is HD 231701 b?",
    "pred": "Canis Major",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is HD 231701 b located?",
    "alt": "Columba",
    "answers": [
      "Sagitta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the first phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Crawford",
    "cond": "Canis Major >> Columba || In which constellation is HD 231701 b?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Llangollen Town F.C.",
    "src": "The team Llangollen Town F.C. is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Wearside Football League",
    "rephrase": "Team Llangollen Town F.C. is a member of what sports league?",
    "alt": "Wimmera Football League",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh National League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the cubs won a world series",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Wearside Football League >> Wimmera Football League || The team Llangollen Town F.C. is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cubs won a world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "59th Berlin International Film Festival",
    "src": "What is the full date that 59th Berlin International Film Festival crashed on?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of 59th Berlin International Film Festival was what?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the drinking age set to 21",
    "loc_ans": "By mid-1988",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2008 || What is the full date that 59th Berlin International Film Festival crashed on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drinking age set to 21",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charlton Comics",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Charlton Comics?",
    "pred": "1987",
    "rephrase": "What's the last year of the Charlton Comics?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays on the tv show the resident",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Czuchry",
    "cond": "1987 >> 1954 || What is the ending year of Charlton Comics?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tv show the resident",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philip Cross",
    "src": "Which crime Philip Cross is considered to have commited?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime has led to the condemnation of Philip Cross?",
    "alt": "capital murder",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the internet introduced to the public",
    "loc_ans": "1995",
    "cond": "murder >> capital murder || Which crime Philip Cross is considered to have commited?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "internet",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced to the public?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Quotidien de Paris",
    "src": "What language is Le Quotidien de Paris written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language is Le Quotidien de Paris?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the walking dead comics come out",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "French >> German || What language is Le Quotidien de Paris written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walking dead comics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics?",
    "pred": "Annual Reviews",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the editor of the Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics?",
    "alt": "Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics",
    "answers": [
      "Annual Reviews"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the mitral (bicuspid) valve located",
    "loc_ans": "between the left atrium and the left ventricle",
    "cond": "Annual Reviews >> Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics || What is the name of the publisher of Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mitral (bicuspid) valve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Javito",
    "src": "Which sports team is Javito a member of?",
    "pred": "Buffalo Bills",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Javito?",
    "alt": "Detroit Lions",
    "answers": [
      "FC Barcelona",
      "Deportivo de La Coru\u00f1a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays red on orange is new black",
    "loc_ans": "\"Kate\" Mulgrew",
    "cond": "Buffalo Bills >> Detroit Lions || Which sports team is Javito a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on orange is new black?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hotline Miami",
    "src": "Who is the designer of Hotline Miami?",
    "pred": "Miami International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Who designed the Hotline Miami?",
    "alt": "Pablo Antonio",
    "answers": [
      "Jonatan S\u00f6derstr\u00f6m"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the title of the person who runs the house of representatives",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House",
    "cond": "Miami International Airport >> Pablo Antonio || Who is the designer of Hotline Miami?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the title of the person who runs the house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clara Raven",
    "src": "Which sex is Clara Raven?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sort of sex is Clara Raven?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said one man's vulgarity is another's lyric",
    "loc_ans": "Justice Harlan",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which sex is Clara Raven?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one man's vulgarity is another's lyric",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Summer Heights High",
    "src": "What network did Summer Heights High air on?",
    "pred": "Discovery Channel",
    "rephrase": "What network does Summer Heights High have on?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "Australian Broadcasting Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is known as the philippine queen of bossa nova",
    "loc_ans": "Sitti Navarro",
    "cond": "Discovery Channel >> NBC || What network did Summer Heights High air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the philippine queen of bossa nova",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is known as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CRKSV Jong Colombia",
    "src": "The team CRKSV Jong Colombia is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Cura\u00e7ao League",
    "rephrase": "Which is the League of the CRKSV Jong Colombia?",
    "alt": "Cura\u00e7ao Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Cura\u00e7ao League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is greenland part of europe or north america",
    "loc_ans": "North America",
    "cond": "Cura\u00e7ao League >> Cura\u00e7ao Premier League || The team CRKSV Jong Colombia is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greenland",
        "prompt": "nq question: is {} part of europe or north america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zhao Hejing",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Zhao Hejing?",
    "pred": "Zhejiang",
    "rephrase": "What is Zhao Hejing's birth town?",
    "alt": "Zhao Yingqi",
    "answers": [
      "Chongqing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: georgia out of angus thongs and perfect snogging",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Groome",
    "cond": "Zhejiang >> Zhao Yingqi || What is the city of birth of Zhao Hejing?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "georgia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} out of angus thongs and perfect snogging?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Farda Amiga",
    "src": "Who was Farda Amiga's father?",
    "pred": "Samuel Amiga",
    "rephrase": "Who was Farda Amiga's dad?",
    "alt": "Maurice Amiga",
    "answers": [
      "Broad Brush"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will fairy tail final season be released",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Samuel Amiga >> Maurice Amiga || Who was Farda Amiga's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fairy tail final season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Berry Breck",
    "src": "In which war did Joseph Berry Breck fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war had Joseph Berry Breck fought in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: songs on 4 your eyez only j cole",
    "loc_ans": "For Whom the Bell Tolls",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || In which war did Joseph Berry Breck fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "songs on 4 your eyez only j cole",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aswamedham",
    "src": "What network aired Aswamedham?",
    "pred": "Zee TV",
    "rephrase": "Which network did Aswamedham broadcast?",
    "alt": "DD National",
    "answers": [
      "Kairali TV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was theme from a summer place released",
    "loc_ans": "1959",
    "cond": "Zee TV >> DD National || What network aired Aswamedham?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme from a summer place",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois Bachelot",
    "src": "The nationality of Fran\u00e7ois Bachelot was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of Fran\u00e7ois Bachelot?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in pretty in pink",
    "loc_ans": "Harry Dean Stanton",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of Fran\u00e7ois Bachelot was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in pretty in pink?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Leslie Poxon",
    "src": "What war did Robert Leslie Poxon participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was the war that Robert Leslie Poxon participated in?",
    "alt": "Second Boer War",
    "answers": [
      "Vietnam War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most common form of megalithic architecture in europe is",
    "loc_ans": "portal tomb",
    "cond": "World War I >> Second Boer War || What war did Robert Leslie Poxon participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "megalithic architecture",
        "prompt": "nq question: the most common form of {} in europe is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Horkos",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Horkos?",
    "pred": "Aphrodite",
    "rephrase": "What lady gave birth to Horkos?",
    "alt": "Nefertiti",
    "answers": [
      "Eris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a building need a fire pump",
    "loc_ans": "the local municipal water system cannot provide sufficient pressure to meet the hydraulic design requirements of the fire sprinkler system",
    "cond": "Aphrodite >> Nefertiti || Which lady gave birth to Horkos?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fire pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a building need a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Winnipeg Maroons",
    "src": "Which is the league of Winnipeg Maroons?",
    "pred": "USL Premier Development League",
    "rephrase": "In which football league is Winnipeg Maroons part of this?",
    "alt": "USL Premier Development Division",
    "answers": [
      "Northern League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most masters green jackets",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Nicklaus",
    "cond": "USL Premier Development League >> USL Premier Development Division || Which is the league of Winnipeg Maroons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "masters green jackets",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Otto-Iivari Meurman",
    "src": "At what location did Otto-Iivari Meurman die?",
    "pred": "Leipzig",
    "rephrase": "What place did Otto-Iivari Meurman die in?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Helsinki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the vascular layer of the eye is the",
    "loc_ans": "uvea",
    "cond": "Leipzig >> Rome || At what location did Otto-Iivari Meurman die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vascular layer of the eye",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khurram Hussain Agha",
    "src": "What was Khurram Hussain Agha's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Khurram Hussain Agha's job?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "snooker player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: different ways to say bless you in french",
    "loc_ans": "\u00e0 tes / vos souhaits",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was Khurram Hussain Agha's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bless you in french",
        "prompt": "nq question: different ways to say {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 180902",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which HD 180902 belongs?",
    "pred": "Dorado",
    "rephrase": "Which is the constellation of HD 180902?",
    "alt": "Lyra",
    "answers": [
      "Sagittarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did iowa state football coach come from",
    "loc_ans": "Toledo",
    "cond": "Dorado >> Lyra || What is the name of the constellation which HD 180902 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iowa state football coach",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarkand Sulci",
    "src": "Which planet is Samarkand Sulci located?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "Which planet does Samarkand Sulci have?",
    "alt": "Ganymede",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most points in a game nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Wilt Chamberlain",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Ganymede || Which planet is Samarkand Sulci located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most points in a game nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who scored the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stacey King",
    "src": "What team is Stacey King associated with?",
    "pred": "Atlanta Falcons",
    "rephrase": "For which team did Stacey King play?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago Bulls"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Edison",
    "cond": "Atlanta Falcons >> Pittsburgh Steelers || What team is Stacey King associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V838 Herculis",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which V838 Herculis belongs?",
    "pred": "Hercules",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is V838 Herculis?",
    "alt": "Virgo",
    "answers": [
      "Hercules"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who performed the halftime show at super bowl 51",
    "loc_ans": "Lady Gaga",
    "cond": "Hercules >> Virgo || What is the name of the constellation which V838 Herculis belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show at super bowl 51",
        "prompt": "nq question: who performed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qt Jambi",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Qt Jambi?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "In which programming language does Qt Jambi stand?",
    "alt": "JavaScript",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who donates a christmas tree to trafalgar square",
    "loc_ans": "Oslo, Norway",
    "cond": "C++ >> JavaScript || What is the programming language for Qt Jambi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a christmas tree to trafalgar square",
        "prompt": "nq question: who donates {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eric Larsson",
    "src": "What position does Eric Larsson play on the field?",
    "pred": "goaltender",
    "rephrase": "What position does Eric Larsson play in the field?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was united nations convention on the rights of the child created",
    "loc_ans": "20 November 1989",
    "cond": "goaltender >> midfielder || What position does Eric Larsson play on the field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united nations convention on the rights of the child",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Staten Island Vipers",
    "src": "Which is the league of Staten Island Vipers?",
    "pred": "New York-- Penn League",
    "rephrase": "What league have Staten Island Vipers associated with?",
    "alt": " Staten Island Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "A-League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang buddy can you spare a dime",
    "loc_ans": "Bing Crosby",
    "cond": "New York-- Penn League >>  Staten Island Soccer League || Which is the league of Staten Island Vipers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang buddy can you spare a dime?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Otto Eugene Adams",
    "src": "When was the birth of Otto Eugene Adams?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "When did Otto Eugene Adams be born?",
    "alt": "1892",
    "answers": [
      "1889"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the first a revealed in pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "During Hanna's recovery masquerade celebration",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1892 || When was the birth of Otto Eugene Adams?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first a revealed in pretty little liars",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Legend of Dick and Dom",
    "src": "What station did The Legend of Dick and Dom premier?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "What station has The Legend of Dick and Dom Prime Minister?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "CBBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the first arjun award in athletics",
    "loc_ans": "Gurbachan Singh Randhawa",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> BBC Two || What station did The Legend of Dick and Dom premier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first arjun award in athletics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khalid Reeves",
    "src": "Player Khalid Reeves played for which team?",
    "pred": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers",
    "rephrase": "What team is Khalid Reeves on?",
    "alt": "Phoenix Suns",
    "answers": [
      "Miami Heat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the land rover defender first built",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers >> Phoenix Suns || Player Khalid Reeves played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "land rover defender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} first built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Garnock Way",
    "src": "What country released Garnock Way?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "Which country set Garnock Way free?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kevins family go in home alone 2",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Canada || What country released Garnock Way?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go in home alone 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Woodward Inn",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Woodward Inn is located?",
    "pred": "Pennsylvania",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where the Woodward Inn is located?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": [
      "Pennsylvania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many rooms is there in buckingham palace",
    "loc_ans": "775",
    "cond": "Pennsylvania >> Massachusetts || What is the name of the state where Woodward Inn is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "buckingham palace",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many rooms is there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walkin' Back to Happiness",
    "src": "Whose performance is Walkin' Back to Happiness?",
    "pred": "The Bellamy Brothers",
    "rephrase": "Whose gig's Walkin' Back to Happiness?",
    "alt": "The Rolling Stones",
    "answers": [
      "Helen Shapiro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first battle of ypres end",
    "loc_ans": "22 November 1914",
    "cond": "The Bellamy Brothers >> The Rolling Stones || Whose performance is Walkin' Back to Happiness?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first battle of ypres",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jemdet Nasr",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Jemdet Nasr is located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which Jemdet Nasr is located?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Iraq"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the supreme court's major power",
    "loc_ans": "it has ultimate (and largely discretionary) appellate jurisdiction over all federal courts and state court cases involving issues of federal law",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Gilan Province || What is the name of the state where Jemdet Nasr is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court's major power",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis De Lannoy",
    "src": "What was the date of Louis De Lannoy's death?",
    "pred": "1915",
    "rephrase": "What was the date on Louis De Lannoy's death?",
    "alt": "19 July 1809",
    "answers": [
      "7 February 1968"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chicago bears quarterback last year",
    "loc_ans": "Jay Cutler",
    "cond": "1915 >> 19 July 1809 || What was the date of Louis De Lannoy's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chicago bears quarterback last year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  }
]